[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.42,0:00:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on! Come on! Let's do this!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.42,0:00:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.47,0:00:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go! Go! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.13,0:00:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和鲁伯特五周年结婚纪念日那天 买下了这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rupert and I bought this on our fifth anniversary.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.17,0:00:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有品味\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, you have exquisite taste.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.59,0:00:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.55,0:00:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是霍克尼的作品 少说也得价值一百万英镑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it's a Hockney. It must be worth a million pounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.97,0:01:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有道理 你应该直接收下的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good point. You should've said yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.06,0:01:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放到拍卖那堆里 -好的 女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Auction pile, please. -Right away, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.31,0:01:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（瑞贝卡韦尔顿离婚后 成为AFC里士满新主人）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.57,0:01:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（男的得到了一个脑残女 女的得到了一群笨男人）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.52,0:01:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 曼尼恩女士…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, Mrs. Mannion--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.94,0:01:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 韦尔顿女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me. Ms. Welton.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.53,0:01:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔治来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.66,0:01:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然他来了 人在哪呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he's here, why isn't he here?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.32,0:01:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 有道理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Good point.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.54,0:01:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.12,0:01:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-希金斯小子 -差点被你得逞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Higgy boy. -Good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.91,0:01:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我喜欢你这里的装潢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. I love what you've done to the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.92,0:01:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己布置的吗 还是找了个基佬帮你弄的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you do it yourself or get some poof to help you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.00,0:01:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你的头发我也想问同样的问题 请坐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could ask the same of your hair. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.72,0:01:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真是一点不吃亏 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's a cheeky one, isn't she?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.84,0:01:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 亲爱的 是这样 我马上得去训练了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, love. Listen, I've got training in a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.18,0:01:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你有什么事要一吐为快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So whatever it is you need to get off your impressive chest,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.81,0:01:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-尽管说吧 -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-let me have it. -Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.56,0:01:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被开除了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're fired.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.64,0:01:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.10,0:01:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我要买断你剩下的合同 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I'll be buying out the remainder of your contract. So...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.19,0:01:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wish you the best of luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.57,0:01:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开除凭什么呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fired? What the fuck for?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.24,0:02:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实原因还挺多的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I suppose I could go for any number of reasons, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.74,0:02:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比方说 你无意中流露的厌女倾向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your casual misogyny, for one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.41,0:02:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么 -我知道这是个高级词汇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What? -I know, it's a big word.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.33,0:02:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问你的女儿就知道什么意思了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ask one of your daughters what it means.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.04,0:02:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是因为你的表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or perhaps it's your performance,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.71,0:02:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致这支队伍本季度又是成绩平平\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}having led this team through yet another remarkably average season.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.71,0:02:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是因为你执意要穿这种短裤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or maybe it's because you insist on wearing those tiny shorts
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.38,0:02:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强迫我看到你其中一个蛋蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that force me to see one of your testicles.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.43,0:02:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一个也露出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And there's the other one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.34,0:02:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利亚姆和诺尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Liam and Noel.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.05,0:02:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过跟绿洲乐队可差远了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Though, perhaps not an oasis.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.60,0:02:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说 乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still, if I'm being completely honest, George,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.27,0:02:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被开除是因为现在我是老板 而我不喜欢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you're fired because I'm the owner now, and I don't like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.10,0:02:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 赶紧滚吧 死胖子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now do piss off, you fat twat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.53,0:02:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 希金斯小子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Higgy boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.07,0:02:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得哪种情况更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you think's worse?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.57,0:02:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老公出轨 还是全世界都知道 只有你被蒙在鼓里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your husband cheating on you or being the last to know?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.70,0:02:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人能给我拿盘沙拉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there someone that could pop out and fetch me a salad?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.62,0:02:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要加葡萄干 拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing with raisins in it, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.09,0:02:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.88,0:02:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那新经理人怎么安置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, what to do as far as new managers go?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.34,0:03:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要我准备一份候选人名单吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shall I prepare a list of candidates?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.97,0:03:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没这个必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. That won't be necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.85,0:03:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（体育中心频道）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.77,0:03:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大西洋的另一边传来一些意外的新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a bit of surprising news from the other side of the Atlantic.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.81,0:03:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,AFC里士满宣布新经理人选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}AFC Richmond announced the hiring of their new manager,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.69,0:03:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名叫悉奥多“泰德”拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one Theodore "Ted" Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.03,0:03:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近 这位拉索教练带领 威奇塔州立大学割麦者队第二组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Recently, it was Coach Lasso leading the Division II Wichita State Shockers
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.49,0:03:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首度获得橄榄球全国冠军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to their first ever national title in American football.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.41,0:03:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为主教练 他第一季度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He took the Shockers from a garbage program
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.99,0:03:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就带领割麦者队这支垃圾球队 一路抵达“应许之地”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all the way to the promised land in his very first season as head coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.00,0:03:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对我们很多人而言 我们不是这样记住泰德拉索的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But for a lot of us, that's not how Ted Lasso found his way into our hearts,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.08,0:03:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在电视上看到的是另一番景象\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}certainly not into our living rooms.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.67,0:03:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我脑海中挥之不去的画面…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For me, it'll always be Ted...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.55,0:03:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是泰德和球队一起庆祝胜利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}celebrating a moment of joy with his team
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.55,0:03:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只有亲眼看到才能理解\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in a way that you really have to see to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.84,0:03:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至 即便是亲眼目睹…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then, even when you see it...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.60,0:03:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不敢说我们真的理解这种行为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't necessarily know that understanding is what we're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.60,0:03:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 泰德 放飞自我吧 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right on, Ted. Do your thing, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.19,0:03:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你在这项最美丽的运动中一直好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And good luck with the most beautiful game.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.02,0:03:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do us proud.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.32,0:03:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 美国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, 'Murica.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.28,0:03:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（卫生间）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.53,0:04:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（杰克凯鲁亚克 《达摩流浪者》）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.50,0:04:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 老兄 这是你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi, mate. This you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.58,0:04:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我相信是的 -天啊你是个传奇人物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I believe it is, yeah. -Oh, man! Legend.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.29,0:04:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能来个“群拍”吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I get an ussie?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.96,0:04:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's dope.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.30,0:04:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们那儿 我们称之为“自拍”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, back where I'm from, we call those selfies.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.38,0:04:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但并不是只有“我自己” 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, it's not "myself," yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.72,0:04:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是“一群人” 所以叫“群拍”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's "us," innit? "Ussie."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.47,0:04:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.97,0:04:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太帅了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wicked.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.43,0:04:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你训练足球队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You coaching football.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.89,0:04:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 你是个传奇人物 这年头会做这种蠢事的人不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mate, you are a legend for doing something so stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.43,0:04:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒谬了 他们会杀了你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, it's mental. They're gonna fucking murder you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.65,0:04:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话我之前听过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, you know, I've heard that tune before.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.06,0:04:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还在这呢 活蹦乱跳的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But here I am, still dancing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.77,0:04:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-传奇人物 -是啊 很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Legend. -Yeah. Nice meeting you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.53,0:04:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在看什么又是关于足球的书\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you reading? Another soccer book.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.28,0:04:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你是知识的海绵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, you are a sponge.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.20,0:04:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 给我讲一个我不知道的趣事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Hit me with a fun fact.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.29,0:04:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不说“越界” 他们说“出界”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They don't say "out of bounds." They say "into touch."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.00,0:04:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我之后能把这个词用在句子里 你给我五块钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, you owe me five bucks if I sneak that into a sentence later.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.83,0:04:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-成交 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You're on. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.88,0:05:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好 我们稍候会将机舱调暗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good evening. We'll be dimming the cabin shortly.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.13,0:05:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好睡一觉吧 不然倒时差会要了我们的命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We should get some sleep. The jet lag will kill us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.42,0:05:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.10,0:05:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这么做是不是疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are we nuts for doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.35,0:05:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 这很疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, this is nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.60,0:05:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但接受挑战和骑马很像 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, but taking on a challenge is a lot like riding a horse, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.39,0:05:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你觉得很舒适\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're comfortable while you're doing it,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.06,0:05:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可能是做得不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}probably doing it wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.65,0:05:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了 晚安 教练 -晚安 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay, good night, Coach. -Night, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.03,0:05:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, hey, hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.74,0:05:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果梦到对方了 咱俩就玩个游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we see each other in our dreams, let's goof around a little bit,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.20,0:05:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-假装互相不认识 -没问题 陌生人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-pretend like we don't know each other. -You got it, stranger.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.62,0:05:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.41,0:06:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你完全没睡吗 -一点没睡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You didn't sleep at all? -Not a wink.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.57,0:06:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的脑子一直在想事情 停不下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. My brain just kept on cooking.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.83,0:06:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始 我打算不睡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At first, I was thinking about not sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.79,0:06:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我在思考我打算不睡这件事 再之后…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I was thinking about thinking about not sleeping. And that--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.50,0:06:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没完没了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's never good.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.92,0:06:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然之间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next thing you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.00,0:06:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空乘给你递上了热乎的巧克力曲奇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they're handing out warm chocolate chip cookies
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.88,0:06:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞机马上就降落了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the plane's landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.25,0:06:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没看到曲奇啊 你把我那份也吃了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't get a cookie. Did you eat mine?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.42,0:06:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个不是重点 我觉得那是来接我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not part of the story. I think this is us right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.30,0:06:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, how ya doin'?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.55,0:06:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我叫泰德 你是 -奥利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-My name's Ted. What's yours? -Ollie.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.05,0:06:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-奥利 好的 -我帮你们拿行李吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ollie. All right. -Let me get your bags.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.60,0:06:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用 奥利 我们打的包 我们自己拿就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no, Ollie. We packed 'em, we'll carry 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.06,0:06:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们想找个地方歇歇脚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Love to make a little pit stop though.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.06,0:06:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.11,0:06:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 不错嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.48,0:06:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 我有一种感觉 我们已经不在堪萨斯了 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, I got a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前在堪萨斯以外的地方 我从没说过这种话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never actually said that when not in Kansas before.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.78,0:06:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-挺好的 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That's kinda nice. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.66,0:06:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你迁就我们 奥利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, thanks for indulging us, Ollie.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.54,0:06:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备好了我们随时出发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ready to boogie whenever you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.00,0:06:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那是塔桥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. That's Tower Bridge.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.58,0:07:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 不是伦敦塔桥 因为这座桥还好好立着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Not the London Bridge, 'cause this one's still up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.50,0:07:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,AFC里士满
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.09,0:07:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道足球是怎么发明的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know how they came up with soccer?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.01,0:07:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是维多利亚时代的校长们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, these Victorian-era headmasters,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.68,0:07:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让男孩们停止手淫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all they wanted to do was get the boys to stop masturbating.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.51,0:07:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就发明了一种禁止男孩用手的运动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So they invented a sport where the boys wouldn't use their hands at all,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.27,0:07:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们以为这样有用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they thought that might do the trick.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.14,0:07:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定是否真的有用 但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure if it worked, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.70,0:07:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不一样 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Feels different, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.66,0:07:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是一样的草地 但是不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, the same, but different.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.41,0:07:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-比喻 -你知道的 宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Metaphor. -You know it, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.50,0:07:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.67,0:07:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi! Excuse me!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.79,0:07:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi! Hello!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.09,0:07:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Off! Off!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.51,0:07:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要踩草坪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop touching the grass!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.17,0:07:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开离开球场不要踩草坪拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get off! Get off the pitch! Stop touching the grass! Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.97,0:07:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -你们是什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yep, yep, yep. Yeah. -Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.39,0:07:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泰德拉索 这位是彼尔德教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm Ted Lasso. This is Coach Beard here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.39,0:07:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊 您是新来的经理 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Oh, God. You're the new manager. -Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.72,0:08:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-草你随便拔 -哦 不…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Take all the grass you want. -Oh, no--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.48,0:08:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚剪过 我可以去翻垃圾桶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just had it cut. I can go through the garbage.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.81,0:08:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我给你再弄点来 -没关系 不用了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I can get you some more. -That's all right. No need.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.40,0:08:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.73,0:08:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.28,0:08:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不过 还是不踩比较好 -好的 当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Still, we got to get off the grass. -Yeah, yeah. Absolutely.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.57,0:08:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要道歉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we apologize?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.49,0:08:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起 草草 -对不起 草草\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sorry about that, grass. -Sorry, grass.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该和一个叫瑞贝卡韦尔顿的人见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, we're supposed to meet with a Rebecca Welton.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.16,0:08:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我就是要带你们去见她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's where I'm taking you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.49,0:08:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这家伙 多超前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at this guy. One step ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.00,0:08:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你叫什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, what's your name, by the way?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.00,0:08:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我吗 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Me? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.17,0:08:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人问过我的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one ever asks my name.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.97,0:08:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备好了就告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, whenever you're ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.22,0:08:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫内森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, it's Nathan.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.76,0:08:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内森我喜欢这个名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nathan! I love that name.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.30,0:08:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 喜欢你们家的热狗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, love your hot dogs.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.10,0:08:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我听懂了这个梗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. No, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.18,0:08:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好 你们这里也有内森热狗吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good, good. Y'all got Nathan's hot dogs here?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.68,0:08:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.77,0:08:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.98,0:08:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这孩子 喜欢他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love this kid. Love him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.73,0:08:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你介绍 大老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll introduce you. Big boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.94,0:08:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.49,0:08:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.83,0:09:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好吗我是泰德拉索 新来的教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, how y'all doing? I'm Ted Lasso, your new coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.33,0:09:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你一定就是韦尔顿女士 -别客气 叫我瑞贝卡就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You must be Ms. Welton. -Please, call me Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.80,0:09:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韦尔顿女士是我父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ms. Welton's my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.05,0:09:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是个笑话 我很喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If that's a joke, I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.72,0:09:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是 我等不及要跟你一起 打造这个笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If not, I cannot wait to unpack that with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.05,0:09:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是彼尔德教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This here is Coach Beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.14,0:09:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于和你们见面了 真是太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is so good to finally meet you both face-to-face.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.35,0:09:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Higgins?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.27,0:09:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 这是希金斯 我们目前的通讯总监\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. This is Higgins, our current director of communications.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.98,0:09:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Current?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能带彼尔德教练 去办一下证件、住房信息…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could you take Coach Beard and get him their IDs, housing information...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.73,0:09:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何他们需要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, anything they need.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.32,0:09:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-无线网密码、湿巾 -加湿器 早都想到了 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Wi-Fi password, wet wipes. -Humidifier. Way ahead of you, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.19,0:09:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.70,0:09:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请坐吧 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Please, take a seat. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.41,0:09:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要喝点什么吗 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Can I get you something to drink? -Yes, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.37,0:09:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在飞机上没怎么睡 所以什么都行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Didn't get much sleep on the plane, so anything you got,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.41,0:09:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点咖啡因的刺激就能精神不少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a little boost of caffeine, should do the trick.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.33,0:09:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩卡奇诺、星冰乐…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, mochaccino, Frappuccino...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.25,0:09:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便什么咖啡 只要我能尝到咖啡的味道就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any coffee thing, as long as I can't taste a hint of coffee, is good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.09,0:09:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢茶吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do you take your tea?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.80,0:09:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常我会直接送回前台\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, usually I take it right back to the counter
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.84,0:09:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为肯定是有人搞错了 但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause someone's made a horrible mistake. But...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.88,0:09:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入乡随俗 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when in Rome, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.84,0:10:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Look at that. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.23,0:10:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.31,0:10:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直觉得茶喝起来就像是热的刷锅水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I always figured that tea was just gonna taste like hot brown water.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.35,0:10:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.61,0:10:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是对的 没错 太难喝了 还是算了 谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was right. Yeah, it's horrible. No, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.40,0:10:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到英国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Welcome to England.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.74,0:10:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊“习惯就好了 混蛋” 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. "Get used to it, sucker." Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.32,0:10:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要参观一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, would you like a tour?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.24,0:10:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很想看看艾比路 -我是说参观俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'd love to see Abbey Road. -Of the club.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.70,0:10:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 从这里开始也不错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, let's start there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.87,0:10:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个大厅展示了俱乐部漫长而平凡的历史\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, this hall represents the club's long, albeit modest, history.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.96,0:10:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一场比赛是在1897年\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The first match was played in 1897.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.87,0:10:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争期间 我们的体育馆 被作为临时医院使用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}During the war, our stadium was used as a makeshift hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.13,0:10:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 一些本地人声称\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, some of the locals claim
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.67,0:10:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们仍能看到死去的士兵 在球场上闲逛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they still see fallen soldiers wandering around the pitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.76,0:10:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真瘆人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's spooky.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.22,0:10:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你相信鬼魂吗 泰德 -我信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Do you believe in ghosts, Ted? -I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.14,0:10:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但更重要的是 他们应该相信自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But more importantly, I think they need to believe in themselves. You know?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.43,0:10:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.35,0:10:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这面墙上展示的是之前的老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this is a wall of our previous owners.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.44,0:10:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 看看这家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. And now look at this fella up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.86,0:10:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（鲁伯特曼尼恩 始于1987年）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.77,0:10:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美女、香槟一应俱全 有没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How 'bout the girls and the champagne and everything?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.48,0:10:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看上去春风得意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He looks like a good time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.03,0:10:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我前夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's my ex-husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.32,0:11:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道 春风得意都不会长久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, good times aren't always a good time, I've found.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.28,0:11:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了那件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I heard about all that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.74,0:11:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How you holding up?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.20,0:11:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好 这一年确实不顺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, hasn't been the easiest year.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.66,0:11:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.83,0:11:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对了 我们需要你在媒体面前露个脸 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-So, we'll need you to speak to the press. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.17,0:11:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 等我睡上几晚好觉 我很乐意做这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, after a couple nights' good sleep, I'll be happy to do so.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.92,0:11:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉 我以为你早知道 他们已经在等你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry. I thought you knew. They're ready for you now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.51,0:11:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're what?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.80,0:11:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 闲言少叙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, without further ado,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.10,0:11:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎新任AFC里士满的球队经理 泰德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the new manager of AFC Richmond, Ted Lasso!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.52,0:11:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.86,0:11:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. How y'all doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.28,0:11:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.24,0:11:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德大神 哟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oluwa Ted, yo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.87,0:11:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看 我们的教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, our coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.20,0:11:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.29,0:11:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都给我安静 别逼我动手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I don't hear silence, I'm gonna start punching dicks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.00,0:11:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下 我先…嗓子有点干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One sec. Let me just-- Throat got a little dry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.88,0:12:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到是气泡水 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did not expect fizzy water there. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.88,0:12:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这傻蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at this twat!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.89,0:12:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的美国佬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fucking Yank!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.47,0:12:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那么 大家好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. So, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.47,0:12:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们直奔主题吧大家有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't we just jump right in? Anybody got any questions?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.60,0:12:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我应该料到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah, no. Should've saw that coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.81,0:12:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧 你们把手放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? You can put your hands down.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.86,0:12:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Real quick--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.07,0:12:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.23,0:12:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我先解释一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about I go ahead and address
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.61,0:12:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家最关心的问题吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the larger-than-average elephant in the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.99,0:12:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我从没有训练过任何级别的 你们称之为“足球”的运动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I have never coached the sport that you folks call football at any level.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.20,0:12:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.83,0:12:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.00,0:12:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天 关于足球我不知道的事 可以装满两个互联网\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Heck, you could fill two Internets with what I don't know about football.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.29,0:12:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要告诉大家我知道什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'll tell you what I do know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.63,0:12:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道AFC里士满 和我之前训练过的任何团队一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know that AFC Richmond, like any team I've ever coached,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.75,0:12:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会走到球场上 发挥出全部实力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is gonna go out there and give you everything they got
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.17,0:12:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-打满四小节比赛 -两个半场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-for all four quarters. -Halves.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.34,0:12:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-您说什么 -两个半场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What was that? -Two halves.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.34,0:12:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 对 抱歉 半场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Sorry. Halves, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.68,0:12:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会全力以赴打满两个半场 不论输赢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're gonna give you everything they got for two halves, win or lose.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.64,0:12:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是平局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or tie.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.81,0:12:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 你们这里还有平局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Y'all do ties here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.64,0:12:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我还需要一点时间适应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. That's going to take some getting used to for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.85,0:12:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在我们那里 如果你的目标是打平\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause back where I'm from, you try to end a game in a tie,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.77,0:13:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那基本上就是“末日景象”的第一个征兆了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}well, that might as well be the first sign of the apocalypse.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.70,0:13:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说 我很尊重各位媒体人士的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, look here. I respect what you folks in the media do.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.16,0:13:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的大门永远都对你们敞开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And my door is always gonna be open.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.08,0:13:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗你们什么都可以问 任何话题都不出界\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right? You can ask me anything. No topic will be into touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 最后一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, one final question.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.54,0:13:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二排的那位男士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about the fellow right there in the second row.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.58,0:13:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.21,0:13:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你的眼镜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I like your glasses.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.63,0:13:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.34,0:13:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是《独立报》的特伦特克里姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trent Crimm, The Independent.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.22,0:13:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想确认一下我理解得没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanna make sure I have this right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.09,0:13:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个从未踏足英国的美国人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're an American who's never set foot in England,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.47,0:13:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在运动方面的成就仅限于业余水平…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}whose athletic success has only come at the amateur level--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.52,0:13:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二梯队…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a second-tier one at that--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.64,0:13:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却被委以重任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and is now being charged with the leadership
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.69,0:13:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领导一个英超足球俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of a Premier League football club,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.31,0:13:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你显然对这种运动知之甚少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}despite clearly possessing very little knowledge of the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.53,0:13:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么问题吗 特伦特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got a question in there, Trent?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.86,0:13:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.53,0:13:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这他妈是在开玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is this a fucking joke?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.53,0:13:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 特伦特 -我爱记者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you, Trent! -I love journalists.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.04,0:13:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至都说不出 任何足球运动员的名字吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, can you even name any footballers?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.12,0:13:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有罗纳尔多 还有《像他自己一样踢球》里演的那位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, yeah, you got Ronaldo and the fellow that bends it like himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.37,0:13:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是贝克汉姆 以他为原型拍的电影 -你这笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fucking Beckham! Made a film on it! -You dickhead, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.59,0:14:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底哪来的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who the fuck are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.84,0:14:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道英超一个赛季有多少场比赛吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you know how many games are in a Premiership season?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.05,0:14:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太记得了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not off the top of my head, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.76,0:14:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人听得懂你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nobody can understand you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.09,0:14:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年联赛谁夺冠了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who won the league last year?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.60,0:14:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道这个问题的答案 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I actually don't know the answer to that. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.26,0:14:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“守门员”是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's a goalie?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.56,0:14:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一双米老鼠那样的大手 在网前…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The fella with the big Mickey Mouse hands and the-- by the net.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.10,0:14:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太可怕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is bleak.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.64,0:14:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚回美国去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to go back to America.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.86,0:14:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 不 是的 不 我…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah. No, yeah. No, no, I--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.70,0:14:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气泡太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bubbles!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.16,0:14:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的老天爷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fucking hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.58,0:14:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 请原谅我的同胞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good Lord. You must forgive my fellow countrymen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.29,0:14:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的几年里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somewhere over the last few years,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.17,0:14:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们似乎完全抛弃了礼仪和好客之道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we seem to have abandoned all sense of manners and hospitality.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.47,0:14:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 你们是野蛮人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My, my, aren't you a salty bunch?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.05,0:14:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我已经记不清上一次 发布室座无虚席是什么时候了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I can't remember the last time the press room was this full.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.56,0:14:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yet here you all are.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.60,0:14:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这并不是一个疯狂的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe you're not such a mad notion after all.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.39,0:15:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管到场的人数众多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And despite the number of you here,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.27,0:15:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个房间里没有一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there is not a single person in this room
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.27,0:15:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看里士满比赛的次数超过我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who has seen Richmond play more than I have.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.53,0:15:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在前任老板管理下的那些年里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And in all those years under the stewardship of the previous owner,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.45,0:15:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我目睹的是一次又一次的平庸表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've witnessed nothing but profound mediocrity.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.12,0:15:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说错了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.37,0:15:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点刻薄了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, it's a bit harsh.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.46,0:15:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说错了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.75,0:15:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.84,0:15:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索教练或许没有 令你们所有人满意的履历\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, Coach Lasso may not have the CV that you all find acceptable,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.71,0:15:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他身上有一件东西 是这个俱乐部所缺乏的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but he does have one thing this club doesn't:
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.01,0:15:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个千禧年的奖杯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a trophy from this millennium.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.26,0:15:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 不管你们喜欢与否 里士满要改变做事情的方式了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, like it or not, Richmond are changing the way we do things.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.97,0:15:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始 那个方式叫“拉索方式”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And from now on, that way is the "Lasso way."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.39,0:15:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们期待在下一场与水晶宫队的比赛上 与大家再会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We look forward to seeing you all at our next match with Crystal Palace.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.86,0:15:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.11,0:15:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴认识大家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice meeting y'all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.44,0:15:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉刚才喷到各位了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And sorry for spittin' on all your stuff up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.49,0:15:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.62,0:15:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他顶多能撑三周\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I give him three weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.41,0:15:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天 刚才的事真抱歉 我不知道怎么会这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, boy. I'm sorry about that. I don't know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.33,0:16:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 别管他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, don't you think about them for another second.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.67,0:16:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有工作要做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have a job to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.75,0:16:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而任务清单里又加了一项 “证明他们错了”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And proving them wrong, just been added to the list.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.92,0:16:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你…谢谢 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I appreciate that-- Thank you, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.75,0:16:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.09,0:16:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 没有气泡我就好好的 我可以开一整天记者会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See, I'm fine when there's no bubbles. You know, I can do that all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.89,0:16:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 如果可以的话 我想跟球队打个招呼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. You know, I'd love to say hi to the team, if I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.64,0:16:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练总是离不了球场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't keep a gaffer from his pitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.06,0:16:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以再说一遍 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can say that again. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.52,0:16:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再搞砸一次我就得卷铺盖走人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am 0 for 2 in that sentence.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.19,0:16:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韦尔顿女士 我之前还有些怀疑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ms. Welton, I was a bit skeptical,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.36,0:16:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但听到你刚才的发言 我为你的选择感到高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but after hearing you speak in there, I'm excited by your choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.65,0:16:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索教练正是我们需要的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach Lasso is just what we need.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.07,0:16:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是个十足的笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's an absolute wanker.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.45,0:16:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.37,0:16:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pardon?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.74,0:16:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望他惨败\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope he fails miserably.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.54,0:16:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我前夫这辈子真正热爱的只有一样东西 就是这家俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See, my ex-husband truly loved only one thing his entire life: this club.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.96,0:16:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而泰德拉索会帮助我将其彻底毁掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Ted Lasso is gonna help me burn it to the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.84,0:16:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我要折磨鲁伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I want to torture Rupert.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.72,0:16:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要让他感觉像是 被劈开的板球拍捅进菊花\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want him to feel like he's being fucked in the ass with a splintered cricket bat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.43,0:17:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进进出出 一遍又一遍 无限循环\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just in and out, over and over, in a constant loop.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.64,0:17:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像GIF一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like a GIF.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.94,0:17:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GIF不就是这样吗它们…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what GIFs do, isn't it? They're just...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.19,0:17:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周而复始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}endless.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.48,0:17:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.94,0:17:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有些人称之为“JIF”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Though some people pronounce it "JIF."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.28,0:17:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 希金斯 -不必客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you, Higgins. -Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.96,0:17:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我用一句话解释 这样影响比较深刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, let me use it in a sentence, so it sticks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.12,0:17:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“教练”说的是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The "gaffer"-- me--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.38,0:17:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-到“球场”去… -怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-is going out to the "pitch"-- -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.04,0:17:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…走上草地 看球队练习\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...the grass here-- to watch practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.59,0:17:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“训练” 他们把练习叫“训练”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Training." They call practice "training."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.51,0:17:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太多方言了 肯定会很辛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All this vernacular. Gonna be tough.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.59,0:17:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗我会撑住的 因为熟能生巧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? I'm gonna get it though. 'Cause training makes perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.22,0:17:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.80,0:17:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是之前那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's our man.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.85,0:17:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的老天爷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jesus, Mary and fuckface Joseph!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.10,0:17:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯住你要防守的人拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eyes on the man you're marking! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.40,0:17:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是谁 -罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Who is that? -Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.11,0:17:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长 典型的老派全能中场球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Team captain. Classic old-school box-to-box midfielder.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.11,0:17:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不如从前了 -但是 他是个传奇人物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Definitely lost a step. -But, you know, he's a legend.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.49,0:18:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了那场跟切尔西队的冠军联赛 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Won a Champions League with Chelsea, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.70,0:18:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-八年前的事了 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Eight years ago. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.37,0:18:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 哪里不对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.25,0:18:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个运动饮料太好喝了 年轻人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is a darn fine sports mix, young fella.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.71,0:18:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你尝了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, you try this?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.30,0:18:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能得到那家伙的肯定可不容易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That does not come lightly from that fella, I'll tell you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.55,0:18:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续加油 内森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You continue to impress, Nathan.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.31,0:18:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得我的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You remembered my name.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.60,0:18:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓我一跳你看到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Holy smokes! Did you see that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.27,0:18:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙就像是被黄瓜吓破胆的猫咪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That fella looked like a kitty cat when it gets spooked by a cucumber.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.36,0:18:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是谁 -杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Who the heck is that? -Jamie Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.48,0:18:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球队的得分王\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Top scorer on the team.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.15,0:18:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck off.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.86,0:18:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-内特 他怎么样 -谁 杰米吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Nate, what's he like? -Who, Jamie?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.82,0:18:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.20,0:18:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很擅长踢球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, at football.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.12,0:18:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我了解这种类型的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I know fellas like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.50,0:18:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆奥比桑亚 他是尼日利亚联盟的右后卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sam Obisanya. He's a right back defender outta the Nigerian league.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.29,0:18:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼日利亚非洲那个尼日利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nigeria? Like Africa?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.13,0:18:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有这里有来自世界各地的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So these fellas are from all over the place?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.00,0:18:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里有空档 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm open, boyo.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.17,0:18:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定是来自英国 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, he must be from England, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.67,0:18:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-威尔士 -那是另一个国家吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Wales. -Is that another country?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.26,0:19:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是也不是 -英国有多少个国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes and no. -How many countries are in this country?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.18,0:19:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-四个 -四个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Four. -Four.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.26,0:19:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很像现在的美国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's kinda like America these days.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.85,0:19:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.20,0:19:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢更衣室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do love a locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.70,0:19:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空气都是“潜力无限”的味道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Smells like potential.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.58,0:19:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是闻到了Axe牌身体喷雾的味道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And am I getting notes of Axe body spray?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.79,0:19:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻子真灵 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Spot on, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.42,0:19:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我想他们这里有别的叫法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I think they call it something else here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.47,0:19:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我说中了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ding, ding, ding.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.80,0:19:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“猞猁”牌的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynx.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.64,0:19:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢的丛林猫之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My favorite of the jungle cats.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.15,0:19:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来 看看你的脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come here. Look at your face. Look at your face.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, thanks, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.37,0:20:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吓人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeesh.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.83,0:20:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次我见到这么冰冷的眼神\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last time I saw eyes that cold,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.29,0:20:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是跟罗伊谢德对视的那双眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they were going head-to-head with Roy Scheider.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.37,0:20:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-《大白鲨》 -不是 《爵士春秋》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Jaws? -No, All That Jazz.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.42,0:20:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要说两句 伙计们 大家好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna say something. Howdy, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.38,0:20:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不必停下手头的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't stop what you're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.25,0:20:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泰德拉索 这是彼尔德教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My name's Ted Lasso. This here is Coach Beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.71,0:20:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们还没正式开始训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know we don't officially start quite yet,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.76,0:20:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我们想先过来跟大家认识一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but, you know, we just wanted to pop in, say howdy,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.18,0:20:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让大家知道我们多高兴能来到这里…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let you know how excited we are to be here--
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.14,0:20:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敲门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Knock, knock.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.35,0:20:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有衣衫不整的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is everyone in here decent?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.31,0:20:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟们 太令人失望了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boys, that's disappointing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.98,0:20:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死 我打扰你们了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, shit. Am I interrupting you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.02,0:20:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 没关系 有什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, that's okay. How can I help you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.65,0:20:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我是来找那家伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I'm here to pick up that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.45,0:20:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 抱歉 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Sorry, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.95,0:20:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们约好了 她要给我脱毛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She made me an appointment. I'm getting waxed.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.37,0:20:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对此兴趣不大 主要是粉丝要看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's more for the fans than it is for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.20,0:20:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是进球了 得脱掉上衣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Score a goal, gotta take my shirt off.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.91,0:20:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.87,0:20:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要 我可以留下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, I can stay if you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.38,0:20:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, that's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.46,0:20:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, cheers.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.96,0:21:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.38,0:21:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 宝贝 你先走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, kid, after you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.42,0:21:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么突然变得这么绅士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna be a gentleman now, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.30,0:21:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是绅士 宝贝 我是想看你屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, babe. Just gonna watch your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.39,0:21:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck off.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.76,0:21:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看着 哭去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Watch it and weep.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.65,0:21:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 感谢大家的宝贵时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anyhoo, thank you for your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.71,0:21:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（祝你好运 老爸）
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.39,0:21:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（成功金字塔）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.44,0:22:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 别睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach. You gotta stay up.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.99,0:22:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打起精神来 别上班时间睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, man. Don't be a sleep cop.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.29,0:22:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊嘿 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy! Hey, Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.87,0:22:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah? What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.71,0:22:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天看你训练挺有意思的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was real fun watching you out there today.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.00,0:22:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都愿意回应你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, the boys really respond to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.34,0:22:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我并不意外 你的职业生涯很精彩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't surprise me though. You've had a heck of a career.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.30,0:22:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.05,0:22:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想过会被该死的麦当劳训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Never thought it would end being coached by Ronald fucking McDonald.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.35,0:22:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就放任他这么称呼你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gonna let him call you that?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.52,0:22:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他不是说我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he was referring to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.90,0:22:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在生气呢 等我们把他争取过来再看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He thinks he's mad now, wait till we win him over.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.24,0:22:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他会气炸的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll be furious.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.82,0:22:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有胶带吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got any tape?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.21,0:23:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（相信）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.68,0:23:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（塔特）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.15,0:23:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那干嘛呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you doing in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.40,0:23:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死 对不起 你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, shit. I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.49,0:23:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 没事 我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, no, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.07,0:23:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不该笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I shouldn't laugh.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.32,0:23:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.95,0:23:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在为更衣室做一些调整\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I was just making some adjustments to the locker room here.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.58,0:23:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过好像贴歪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Though, I believe it's crooked.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.42,0:23:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才一直觉得是房间歪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now here I am thinking it was the room that was all outta whack.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.76,0:23:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你知道吗我觉得你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you know what? I think you're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.88,0:23:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么过来了杰米呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you doing back here? Where's Jamie?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.76,0:23:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他手机落在柜子里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He left his phone in his locker.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.35,0:23:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么不自己来取呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why didn't he come get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.01,0:23:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还在脱毛呢 没想到这么多毛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's still getting waxed. He's surprisingly furry.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.52,0:23:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像一边脱一边就长了回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The hair was, like, growing back while she was doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.10,0:24:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这有点扯了 -我可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Come on, now. -May I?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.02,0:24:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 请便 -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah, yeah. Help yourself. -Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.70,0:24:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边低一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lower it down on that side.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.49,0:24:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.58,0:24:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续 再移一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep going. Little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.66,0:24:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Teeny bit more.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.74,0:24:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停 完美\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop! That's perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.41,0:24:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 真不错 团队合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. How 'bout that? Nice teamwork.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.96,0:24:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘭 -好传统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Pow. Yeah. -Old-school.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.63,0:24:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对了 我叫基莉 -你好 我叫泰德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm Keeley, by the way. -Yeah. Hey, I'm Ted Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.17,0:24:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 你在推特上火了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I know. You're trending hard on Twitter right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.38,0:24:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How 'bout that.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.22,0:24:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你发推特吗 -不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Do you even tweet? -Nah.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.01,0:24:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的节奏口技还可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I do beatbox all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.81,0:24:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成年男人在我面前表演节奏口技 我从来不知道该作何反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never know how to react when a grown man beatboxes in front of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.90,0:24:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我希望你不要遇见比兹马吉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I hope you never run into Biz Markie.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.44,0:24:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.82,0:24:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你好奇了 想要去推特上搜索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, if you get curious and you start searching around on Twitter,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.78,0:24:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我建议你避开“里士满”这个标签\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would avoid #Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.41,0:24:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -或是“傻屌” 还有“混蛋”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. -Or wanker. Or dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.08,0:25:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I'll take your word for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.75,0:25:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到英国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Welcome to England.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.84,0:25:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 再次感谢你帮忙拿东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. Hey, and thanks again for the lift.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.89,0:25:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.93,0:25:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的车吗 内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, this you, Nate?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.64,0:25:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那辆天啊 当然不是 我可买不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That one? God, no. No, couldn't handle that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.60,0:25:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿色这辆才是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is me. Green one here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.18,0:25:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 放到后备箱里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. So, get that in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.64,0:25:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.73,0:25:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头一天就工作到这么晚啊 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Already burning the midnight oil, I see, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.44,0:25:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俗话说得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, as the man once said,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.73,0:25:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“越努力越幸运” 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"The harder you work, the luckier you get," huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.19,0:25:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斜着放\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}On the diagonal.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.28,0:25:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉 泰德 我们应该给你叫辆车的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My apologies, Ted. We should have ordered you a car.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.32,0:25:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no. That's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.74,0:25:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 两位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Night, y'all. -Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.37,0:25:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.45,0:25:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天吃的那些东西…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just that everything I've eaten today...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.54,0:25:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉都堵在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}feels like it's stuck right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.50,0:25:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got it. I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.80,0:25:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.88,0:25:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看上去人挺好的 我有点下不去手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He seems like such a nice man. I'm not sure I can do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.14,0:26:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很显然 要想计划成功\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously, for this to work,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.47,0:26:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要新任足球业务主任的全力支持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going to need the full support of my new director of football operations.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.85,0:26:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜升职加薪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm assuming that's a promotion and substantial pay rise
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.36,0:26:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你和你的家人都有好处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that would be of interest to you and your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.40,0:26:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 快看 这辆车的方向盘是隐形的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, look, this car's got an invisible steering wheel!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.70,0:26:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just kidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.74,0:26:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的朋友内特在按喇叭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's my man Nate here running the horn.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.53,0:26:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是充满惊喜 泰德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a godsend, Ted Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.25,0:26:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Takes one to know one.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.75,0:26:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.09,0:26:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I accept.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.38,0:26:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.47,0:26:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, and Higgins,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.22,0:26:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这次计划当中会有一些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know that there'll be elements to this little adventure
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.10,0:26:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你难以承受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that will weigh on you a bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.48,0:26:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我确信 相比这么年来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'm sure it won't be harder than it was
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.81,0:26:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你背着我为鲁伯特迎来送往那些女人 这要简单多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to sneak all Rupert's women in and out behind my back all those years.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.16,0:27:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你住这里 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is you, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.33,0:27:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 你一个人可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. All right. You good?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.63,0:27:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没事 你呢 -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm good. You good? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.30,0:27:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-晚安 教练 -晚安 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Night, Coach. -Good night, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.55,0:27:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I almost forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.30,0:27:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's this for?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.88,0:27:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-“出界” -好好睡一觉 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"Into touch." -Get some sleep, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.64,0:27:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.86,0:27:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（欢迎 蒂姆拉索教练）
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.10,0:28:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 小伙子 你还好吗 今天上学还顺利吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, big guy. How you doing? How was school today?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.94,0:28:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.94,0:28:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘了这事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.61,0:28:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我今天有点晕乎乎的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Yeah, I'm a little loopy today.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.86,0:28:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 你可以这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Yeah, you could say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.36,0:28:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系 我只是想听听你的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, that's okay. No. I just wanted to hear your voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.87,0:28:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 去做你自己的事吧 嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Yeah, go do your thing. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.49,0:28:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你妈妈在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, is your mom there?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.16,0:28:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢 小伙子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Thanks, big guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.33,0:28:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.04,0:28:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I love you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.25,0:28:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.76,0:28:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, how you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.77,0:28:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前一切都好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Well, you know, so far so good. You know?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.85,0:28:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还需要适应一下 对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna take some getting used to, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.27,0:28:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想一旦运转起来 会很顺利的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I think once we get going, it's gonna go all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.86,0:29:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 这话没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. No, that's true, that's true. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.32,0:29:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗其实这里条件挺好的 对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, you know what? It's actually pretty nice. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.16,0:29:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且小区也挺漂亮的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, and tell you what, they got a cute neighborhood too.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.91,0:29:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.00,0:29:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 你和小家伙应该一起过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, you and the little guy gotta get on over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.46,0:29:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲眼看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.63,0:29:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么不 我说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? No, what did I say?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.47,0:29:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我在做的事 我给你空间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But that's what I'm doing though. I'm giving you that space.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.76,0:29:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.85,0:29:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 也是给自己空间 没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, and myself. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.64,0:29:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.44,0:29:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. That's okay. Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.52,0:29:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.40,0:29:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.40,0:29:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系 你不必这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, that's okay. You don't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.62,0:29:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.50,0:29:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.96,0:29:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 晚安\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, now. Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.27,0:30:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死 我现在睡不着了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shoot. Now I can't sleep.
