[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.14,0:00:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.64,0:00:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好抱歉的 多亏了你 我们才能把另一辆车也修好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you dare apologize. Thanks to you, we can afford to get the other car fixed.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.98,0:00:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他 孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell him, boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.31,0:00:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见 爸爸 -没关系 爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Bye, Dad. -It's all right, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.36,0:00:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便啦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.65,0:00:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爱你 -我也爱你 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Love you. -Love you, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.44,0:00:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 告诉你老板 我希望她得心脏病\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And tell your boss I hope she gets heart disease.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.08,0:00:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好 泰德 -嘿 希金斯…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Morning, Ted. -Hey, Higgins--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.83,0:00:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is he dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.96,0:00:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的错 我不该盯着手机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, you know, it's my fault for staring at my phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.13,0:00:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是忍不住要查看我家人的航班\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just can't stop checking on my family's flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.21,0:00:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事我没跟太多人说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I haven't shared this with too many folks,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.05,0:00:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是米歇尔和我 我们的婚姻出了点问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but Michelle and I, we've been having some marital issues.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.76,0:00:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 如果你不想说的话 可以不说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, you really don't have to talk about this if you don't want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.80,0:00:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.43,0:01:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们试过夫妻疗法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tried couples therapy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.02,0:01:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我们不喜欢另外那对夫妻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Didn't like the other couple though.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.06,0:01:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能笑一笑感觉挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It feels good to laugh.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.11,0:01:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的心理医生给了我们一个暗语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, you know, our therapist gave us this code word to use.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.07,0:01:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们当中的任何一个人 说了“俄克拉荷马”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So if either of us says "Oklahoma,"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.19,0:01:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个人就必须说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the other one has to tell the God's honest truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.49,0:01:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 这很有帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, you know, it's pretty helpful.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.45,0:01:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那部电影再也无法直视了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did ruin the musical for me though.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.16,0:01:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我每次听到《噢 多么美妙的清晨》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So now every time I hear, "Oh, What a Beautiful Mornin',"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.20,0:01:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是…《带花边顶蓬的四轮马车》 或是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or... what-- "Surrey with the Fringe on Top," or--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.79,0:01:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-《我们跳舞吧》 -不 那是《国王与我》里的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"Shall We Dance?" -No, that's from King and I.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.67,0:01:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我只要一听到那些旋律响起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anyway, if I hear any of those tunes,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.80,0:01:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立刻就想到我妻子跟我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I immediately think about my wife telling me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.71,0:01:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我持续不断的乐观主义实在太过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that my constant optimism is too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.18,0:01:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在…你分享自己的感受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this... sharing of feelings
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.81,0:01:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我在宴会上向你吐露了我前夫的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is 'cause I opened up to you about my ex-husband at the gala.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.73,0:01:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.14,0:01:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下我可长记性了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, that's a lesson learned.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.60,0:01:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.85,0:01:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你内心深处肯定很高兴 我们能拉近距离 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I bet deep down you kinda dig we're getting so close, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.73,0:01:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-俄克拉荷马 -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Oklahoma? -I do not.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.26,0:02:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.80,0:02:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你起床了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You up?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.35,0:02:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.10,0:02:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Jamie here?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.86,0:02:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 你是基莉琼斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. You're Keeley Jones.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.90,0:02:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.44,0:02:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.32,0:02:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你不能生气 是你甩了我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. No. You can't get mad. You broke up with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.08,0:02:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,24小时前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like, 24 hours ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人男人应该单身多久呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long's a man meant to be alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.25,0:02:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该怎么做一个人洗澡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What am I supposed to do? Shower by myself?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.12,0:02:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我想说 我是你的头号粉丝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, can I just say, I'm your biggest fan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.08,0:02:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我关注你了你的照片墙 "图片分享" 一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I follow your Insta, your Snap, everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.09,0:02:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.50,0:02:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 杰米 我也要谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, Jamie, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.26,0:03:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次我跟别人分手 我都会花上好几个月 质疑我的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whenever I break up with someone, I spend months questioning it,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.88,0:03:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思考我是不是犯了一个大错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}wondering if I made a huge fucking mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.43,0:03:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你让我庆幸自己做了这个决定 而你只是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you have really helped me to feel good about this decision, just by...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.10,0:03:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做你自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}being you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.77,0:03:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.40,0:03:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.52,0:03:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说我让你庆幸做了那个决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You said I made you feel good about your decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.78,0:03:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 -你是认真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Did you mean it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.86,0:03:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -那不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes. -Well, then you're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.70,0:03:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢让别人感觉舒适\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I like to make people feel good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.24,0:03:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下拍宣传照你会去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still gonna be around for the promo shoot later?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.29,0:03:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你准备了好几周的宣传照吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The promo shoot that I've spent weeks setting up for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.54,0:03:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.92,0:03:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.01,0:03:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, yes, yes! Here!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.64,0:03:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Jamie! Jamie, Jamie!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.81,0:03:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 我没人防守 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie, I'm open. Jamie!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.19,0:03:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你干什么原本是能进的 -那可不一定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What are you doing? That was going in. -Well, we'll never know.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.60,0:03:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 我跟你说了多少次 要多传一次球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie, how many times I gotta tell you to make the extra pass?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.98,0:03:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 山姆那边比我家厨房的 花生酱罐子还要敞开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Sam was more open than the jar of peanut butter on my kitchen counter.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.78,0:04:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么他在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? What's he talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.90,0:04:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 你们不知道 我喜欢让花生酱罐子敞开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's right. Y'all don't know I like to keep the peanut butter open.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.45,0:04:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我每次走过的时候 就可以把手指伸进去挖一口吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That way, whenever I walk by, I can just stick my finger in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.99,0:04:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说实在的 这个主意真好 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's a fucking good idea, to be fair. -Yeah, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.25,0:04:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言归正传 如果山姆有空档的时候 你就要传球给他 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now look, when Sam is that open, you gotta pass to him, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.04,0:04:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么就算山姆有空档 他还是踢得很烂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But why? Even when Sam's open, Sam is still shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.33,0:04:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人叫我了 他说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I heard my name. What did he say?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.00,0:04:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没什么 -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Don't worry about it. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.84,0:04:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我们明天的比赛要团队合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Guys, we gotta play like a team tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.55,0:04:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我们肯定会输惨的 额外传球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Otherwise we're gonna get our butts kicked. Extra passes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.05,0:04:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要不断练习直到做好为止 去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna keep doing this until we get it right. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.76,0:04:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.23,0:04:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练习取消\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Practice is canceled.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.44,0:04:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段路程比他想象中远多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is a lot longer run than he thinks, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.07,0:04:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比喻贴切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Metaphor.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.41,0:04:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey! -Daddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.20,0:04:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你们会朝我奔过来 但是没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I kinda thought y'all would meet me halfway, but hey, that's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.74,0:04:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 小家伙 -直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, buddy! -Helicopter!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.79,0:04:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题 转两圈 怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got it. Two spins. How about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.96,0:04:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 你肯定会晕乎乎的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, you're gonna be a dizzy fella there.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.58,0:04:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-慢速版的直升机 -这还用说 来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Slower helicopter. -No way. Come on now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.63,0:05:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好想你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I missed you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.93,0:05:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起抱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Group hug.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.39,0:05:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿他挤进来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey! There he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.72,0:05:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 小伙子 看你都长多高了 怎么搞的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, big guy. Look how tall you got. What the heck?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.31,0:05:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看 我是说 怎么回事…你现在长牙了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And look at this. I mean, you, what-- You got teeth now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.81,0:05:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我已经有牙齿了 -你还会说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I already had teeth! -And you can talk!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.23,0:05:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 韦尔顿女士 抱歉有个坏消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Also, Ms. Welton, sorry to report,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.15,0:05:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这周的比赛门票不会售罄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but this weekend's match will not be completely sold out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.28,0:05:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不意外 我们已经连续输了四场比赛 现在面临降级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not a surprise. We've lost four matches in a row, and we're facing relegation.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.36,0:05:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你有什么好抱歉的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But why be sorry?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.91,0:05:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是进展地很顺利嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's all going rather smashingly.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.54,0:05:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（达斯乐啤酒）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.45,0:05:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很开心成为达斯乐新的品牌大使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm happy to be the new brand ambassador for Darsteiner.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.75,0:05:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特最爱的啤酒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The favorite beer of Jamie Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.92,0:05:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 把我的纹身拍进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait, wait, wait. Get my tats.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.88,0:05:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要拍进去 这对我很重要 是中文的“胳膊”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get that one. It's very important to me. Chinese for "arm."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.47,0:05:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰米 -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Jamie. -What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.97,0:05:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喝酒 -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Just drink the beer. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.52,0:05:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不做评价 你和那傻蛋和好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No judgment, but are you back with that twat?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.02,0:05:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好胃口\NBon appétit.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.73,0:06:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 我们结束了 天呐 我很高兴你这么关心我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. We're done. God, I love that you care though.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.52,0:06:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我够得着 我现在就在你的嘴上亲一口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll kiss you on the mouth if I can reach those lips.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.44,0:06:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这整件事是我操办的 我能拿到10%的分成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I put this whole thing together. I get 10%.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.07,0:06:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们喜欢神话故事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, do you like mythology?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.70,0:06:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都知道独角兽 但你们见过啤酒瓶子独角兽吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've seen a unicorn. You ever seen a brewnicorn?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.41,0:06:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好笑了 -哦 不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That's fucking funny. -Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.62,0:06:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么我的啤酒宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that? It's my beerby.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.71,0:06:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走吧 -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Come on. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.12,0:06:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这部分是免费的 我不会多收钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Y'all getting all this for free. Not even extra for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.09,0:06:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.17,0:06:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果其他球员需要代言品牌的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If any of the other players needed some branding work done,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.26,0:06:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有兴趣负责这部分工作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is that something you'd be interested in?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.38,0:06:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望你给我工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want you to offer me a job
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.59,0:06:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为之前那晚 我在卫生间对你的善意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just 'cause I was nice to you in the loo the other night.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.55,0:06:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不行男人经常在卫生间里 互相找“活”干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why not? Men give each other jobs in toilets all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.97,0:06:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.81,0:06:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我指的是工作 正经的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I meant employment. Like job-jobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.65,0:06:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以不用手 也不用嘴 或是脚 -脚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-So not hand, or blow, or foot? -Foot?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.40,0:06:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对 严格来说应该是…两只脚 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're right. Technically it would be... feet, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.65,0:06:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好考虑一下吧 除非你想继续…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just give it a thought. Unless you want to carry on doing--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.78,0:06:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是做什么的来着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it you do again?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.95,0:06:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我因为差一点出名而出名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sort of famous for being almost famous.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.54,0:06:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excellent.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.79,0:07:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你可以把这当成一个后备计划 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Maybe think of it as a plan B. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.63,0:07:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 给你们一点建议 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, now, little tip for y'all, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.46,0:07:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸薯条叫“薯片” 薯片叫“洋芋片”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fries are called "chips." Chips are called "crisps."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.01,0:07:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“香肠”不是让你跟着晃脑袋的好歌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And "bangers" aren't great songs,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.51,0:07:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但吃一口就让你想跳舞 因为实在是太美味了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but they do make you feel like dancing 'cause they're so darn tasty.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.72,0:07:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候能赢比赛 你这该死的傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When you gonna win a game, you fucking wanker?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.27,0:07:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 巴兹 伙计们 这是我妻子米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Baz. Fellas. This here-- This is my wife, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.48,0:07:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很荣幸认识你 拉索夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Absolute pleasure to meet you, Mrs. Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.69,0:07:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反应真快 无缝衔接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice recovery. Well executed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.82,0:07:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 她是教练的老婆 什么都听到了 -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah, coach's wife. She's heard it all. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.61,0:07:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 泰德 你好啊 小家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Ted. Hello, young man.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.49,0:07:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是飞镖 那是靶子 尽量不要伤到常客\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here are the darts. There's the board. Try not to hit any regulars.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.08,0:07:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去玩吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, go have fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.33,0:07:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的桌子在这边 -走吧 你先\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Your table's this way. -Go on. After you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.83,0:07:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-三份炸鱼薯条 -好的 谢谢 再来两品脱啤酒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Three fish-and-chips? -Yes, please. And two pints.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.38,0:07:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我喜欢你的风格 -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I like your style. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.92,0:07:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.47,0:07:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会用报纸装炸鱼薯条吗 我之前读到过他们会这么干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do they wrap the fish-and-chips in newspaper? I read they do that here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.80,0:07:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会 我倒希望是 天 我喜欢那样 一边吃东西一边学知识\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. I wish. Boy, I'd love that. Having my food teach me stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.52,0:08:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那是你梦想中的场景 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's your dream scenario, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.52,0:08:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个了解罗莎帕克斯事件的甜甜圈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A doughnut that knows about Rosa Parks or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.65,0:08:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 没错 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. Exactly, yeah. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.44,0:08:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜圈圈中间那个洞里能装进很多智慧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can fit a lot of wisdom just in the hole.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.28,0:08:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.78,0:08:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么快就玩完了 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You already done, bud?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.57,0:08:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 他或许应该玩完\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, he probably should be.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.36,0:08:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I'm sorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.58,0:08:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Happens all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.25,0:08:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在干什么 -我只是好奇而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What are you doing? -I'm just curious, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.16,0:08:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摄影师会把照片发给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The photographer's gonna send me over the pictures,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.17,0:08:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会删掉你看上去像个傻瓜的那些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'll just kill the ones where you look like shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.13,0:08:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我把剩下的发给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I'll send them over to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.38,0:08:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 宝贝 根本不会有 我看上去像傻瓜的 因为…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Firstly, babe, there won't be any where I look like shit because...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.59,0:08:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其次 不如你直接拿到我家里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And B, why don't you just bring them over to my place
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.72,0:08:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以一起看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we can look at them together?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.93,0:08:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许可以裸着看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe we're naked.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.14,0:08:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不行 再次表示感谢 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hard no. Thank you again, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.15,0:08:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明智的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Smart move.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.48,0:08:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.32,0:08:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟他相处是迫于无奈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to hang out with that prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.28,0:08:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却选择跟他在一起 老实说 这件事太让人迷惑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The fact that you would choose to be with him is frankly mind-blowing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没跟他在一起 我们分手了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not with him. We broke up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.45,0:09:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 我们是在一起工作 再说谁问你意见了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're working together, actually. And who asked you anyway, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.45,0:09:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.66,0:09:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前不知道 所以…我道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't know that, so... apologies.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.46,0:09:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系 你应该为我的人生做点贡献\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's fine. You should definitely weigh in on my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.21,0:09:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以后每次需要做决定的时候 都会给你发短信的 怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make sure that I text you anytime I have to make a decision, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.42,0:09:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为训练时 山姆无人防守\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just that in training, Sam was wide open,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.97,0:09:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可杰米却不肯传球给他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and Jamie wouldn't pass to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.68,0:09:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但山姆无人防守啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But Sam was wide open.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.72,0:09:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我需要面对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now that's what I'm dealing with.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.48,0:09:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（基莉 我快憋不住了 我可以去尿尿吗）
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.81,0:09:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.57,0:09:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.19,0:09:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Okay. Now, hold on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.53,0:09:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们好像少看了一页 天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think we might have missed a page. Oh, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.41,0:09:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不想去坐真正的双层巴士吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you wanna go ride a real double-decker bus?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.04,0:09:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的给我们拼完之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After we finish.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.33,0:09:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See? I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.75,0:09:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先我们要先建造好 然后再坐上去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}First we gotta build it, then we can ride it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.96,0:09:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟实现梦想的步骤是一样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's kind of a Field of Dreams paradigm.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.09,0:09:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.88,0:09:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人多力量大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, six hands are better than four.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.62,0:10:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（考夫卡 最狂野的伏特加）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.95,0:10:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.75,0:10:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, how you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.38,0:10:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 这围巾真漂亮 我喜欢 -喂傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, look at that scarf. I like it. -Oi! Wanker.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.38,0:10:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把比赛搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you fuck up the match.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.30,0:10:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢关心 我们到时见分晓 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I appreciate you. We'll see what happens, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.56,0:10:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.27,0:10:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从没…你从没见过这东西吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You never-- Never seen one of these before.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.31,0:10:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫司康 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That right there, that's a scone, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.02,0:10:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟马芬挺像的 只不过干得要死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's like a muffin, except it sucks all the spit out of your mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.36,0:10:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的早餐 嘿你应该说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's your breakfast. All right? Hey! What do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.65,0:10:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.03,0:10:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 我们家的小孩就是有礼貌 我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. There you go. Some people's kids, holy moly.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.66,0:11:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-风景很不错 是吧 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's pretty nice out there, isn't it? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.25,0:11:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -我可以给咱俩做点早餐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey. -I can make us some breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.96,0:11:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.21,0:11:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 我想我只是还没适应时差\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing. I think I'm just a little jet-lagged is all.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.46,0:11:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm fine, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.71,0:11:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 米歇尔 你必须跟我说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. No. Michelle, you gotta talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.63,0:11:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗嘿 俄克拉荷马\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay? Hey, hey. Oklahoma.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.39,0:11:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一天…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every day...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.10,0:11:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我醒来时都希望我能找回一开始的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wake up hoping that I'll feel the way I felt in the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.98,0:11:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许婚姻就是这样 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But maybe that's just what marriage is, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.69,0:11:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会继续努力 你知道我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll keep trying. You know I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.53,0:11:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ready to go!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.04,0:11:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你得穿上裤子 孩子 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I mean, you're gonna need pants, kiddo. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.12,0:11:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道… -我们去把裤子穿上 走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You know-- -Let's get some pants. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.22,0:12:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.85,0:12:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚姻 你知道的 太复杂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marriage. Just so, you know, so complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.39,0:12:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要面临太多不同的挑战和…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So many different challenges and...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.89,0:12:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想…我不知道 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think-- I don't know. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.65,0:12:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你结过婚吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You ever been married?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.57,0:12:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内特 教练对浪漫关系的看法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, Nate. Coach's views on romantic relationships
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.53,0:12:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和对煎牛排的看法没有太多不同\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}are not too dissimilar from his views on cooking steak.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.99,0:12:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你煎超过五分钟 味道就差了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, you spend any more than five minutes on one, loses its flavor.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.45,0:12:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说得对吗 教练 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That sound about right, Coach? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.78,0:12:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你介意我问你一个私人问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you mind if I ask you a personal question then?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.87,0:12:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fire away.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.87,0:12:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你这么担心你的婚姻问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you were worried about your relationship,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.29,0:12:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你干嘛要飞到7100公里之外的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then why did you fly 4,438 miles away?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.17,0:12:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么具体的数字你张口就来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is a very specific number to know off the top of your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸以前是制图员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, my dad used to be a cartographer.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.17,0:12:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他过去总说我是0.0016公里高\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Used to say I was .001 miles tall.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.39,0:12:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 这个问题问得好 为什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Well, it's a good question. Why do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.10,0:12:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想是到了某个节点 我意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think at some point I realized
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.77,0:12:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的存在会产生更坏的影响 而不是好的影响\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that me being around so much was doing more harm than good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.36,0:13:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说 每次我尝试解决问题 或是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like, anytime I tried to solve any of her problems, or...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.90,0:13:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为她做一些贴心的事 都会起反效果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}do something sweet for her, it just would backfire.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.12,0:13:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和我们咨询的心理医生一致认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then she and this therapist we were working with
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.33,0:13:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好能给她一些空间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}decided that maybe the best thing to do would be to give her a little space.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.87,0:13:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…我给了她7000公里的空间…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And so... well, I gave her 4,400 and...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.59,0:13:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7100公里的空间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thirty-eight. Thirty-eight miles worth of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.55,0:13:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰了 我听说你们当中 有人捡到了我手机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry to interrupt. I was told one of you had my phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.18,0:13:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank heavens.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.39,0:13:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我删除了一些应用来优化性能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I deleted some apps to optimize performance.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.81,0:13:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望没把“海战”游戏删掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not Battleships, I hope.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.44,0:13:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好 其实我没有经常玩啦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, well. I was playing that too much anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.65,0:13:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不妨碍你们商量比赛日计划了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll leave you lads to your match day planning.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.40,0:13:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,且慢 朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, well, hold your horse there, amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.36,0:13:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事我想问下你的意见 可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You mind if I get your take on something?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.24,0:13:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.36,0:13:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很开心能受邀加入核心集团\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Very exciting to be invited into the inner sanctum.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.79,0:13:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索队 也可以这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Team Lasso, as it were.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.29,0:13:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你老婆结婚很多年了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and the missus. Y'all been together a while, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.00,0:14:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 28年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, 28 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.25,0:14:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五个儿子 三条狗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Five boys, three dogs,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.55,0:14:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只20岁的猫 它要是哪天死了 我会伤心死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one 20-year-old cat whose impending death will wreck me emotionally,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.47,0:14:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个将我们全部容纳进去的小房子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and one small house that manages to fit us all in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.05,0:14:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去简直人生赢家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sounds like a full life right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.77,0:14:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我猜你们肯定也有困难的时候吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I assume y'all have had your fair share of hard times though, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.60,0:14:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没听到我说五个儿子、小房子 和快死的猫这部分吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you not hear the five boys, tiny house, dying cat part?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.73,0:14:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过人生就是这样 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the thing though, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.99,0:14:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你和对的人在一起 那即便是困难时期也会变得容易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're with the right person, even the hard times are easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.95,0:14:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快打911 有人丢了真相炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone call 911. I want to report a truth bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想他们这里应该是999 -是999\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I think they do 999 here. -It is 999.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.08,0:14:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对的 -用于紧急事件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes. It is, yeah. -For emergencies?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.42,0:14:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 我觉得这样很容易出麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, that seems troublesome to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.09,0:14:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说刚学步的小孩 一屁股坐在手机上…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, toddlers and, just, butt dials and--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.51,0:14:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-因为是重复的数字 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-'Cause it's one key. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.72,0:14:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能警察和救护车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'd probably have police cars and ambulances
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.72,0:14:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一下子全都来了 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-just zipping all over the place. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.68,0:14:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这种事常有 不是吗 -确实 是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Well, that happens a lot, doesn't it? -It does. Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.64,0:14:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-解开了我多年的疑惑 -明白了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That explains it, actually. -There you have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.77,0:14:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔洛怀特和克里斯鲍威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Arlo White here with Chris Powell.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.06,0:15:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在内尔森路体育馆 AFC里士满主场 为您现场直播\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Live from Nelson Road Stadium, the home of AFC Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.65,0:15:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 各位赶紧围过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, everyone! Get in a fucking circle.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.36,0:15:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们去打败他们 -来吧 小伙子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Let's throw this down! -Come on, boys!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.11,0:15:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 手伸出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, hands in.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.65,0:15:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数到三 一、二、三…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}On three. One, two, three...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.99,0:15:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-里士满 -走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Richmond! -Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.45,0:15:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.63,0:15:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 你有细菌恐惧症吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie, you a germophobe?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.46,0:15:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在想你为什么不愿意 和其他球员一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I'm trying to think of a reason you didn't put your hand in
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.55,0:15:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手伸到中间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with the rest of the team.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.55,0:15:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Didn't want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.63,0:15:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得说 伙计 有时候你会让我想起 我外婆和她的遥控器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta say, man, sometimes you remind me of my grandma with the channel hopper.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.72,0:15:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是按错按键\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You just push all the wrong buttons.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.72,0:15:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如咱俩谈个交易吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, then how's about you and me make a deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.23,0:15:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 我洗耳恭听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, I'm listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.69,0:15:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以继续鼓吹你那些打鸡血式的狗屁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You get to keep on preaching all of your yeehaw bullshit,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.65,0:15:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换 我会继续无视你 因为这个球队没救了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and in exchange, I'll keep ignoring you, because this team is tragic.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.24,0:15:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有球都是我进的 球迷也都是来看我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I score all the goals, and I'm the only one they come to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.99,0:15:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去公平吗伸手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does that sound fair? Hands in.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.70,0:15:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道 我很想跟你掰扯清楚一些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I'd love to hash out some of the nuances there,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.66,0:16:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我最近过得不太顺利…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I'm not having the best of days--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.12,0:16:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 你怎么说不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, it doesn't matter what you say.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.62,0:16:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在我脑海里 我只听到了今晚我进球后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause in my head, I'm just hearing the crowd cheer my name
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.42,0:16:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们呼喊着我的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}after I score a goal tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.30,0:16:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt... Jamie Tartt...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.34,0:16:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这旋律挺上头的 但现在不是胡闹的时候…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As undeniably catchy as that tune is, I need you to cut the crap right now--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.39,0:16:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.85,0:16:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 小家伙 你来了 嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, big guy. There he is. Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.10,0:16:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰米塔特 -你好 小朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Jamie Tartt? -Hello, little lad.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.81,0:16:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能在我衣服上签名吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Would you sign my shirt?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.23,0:16:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 转过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, turn around.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.90,0:16:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很酷吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's pretty cool, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.69,0:16:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一次我再进球 那不仅是为我进的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, next time I score a goal, it won't just be for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.07,0:16:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是为你进的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be for you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.91,0:16:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有为我 但是…只为我们俩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And for me. But... just for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.83,0:16:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-酷 -好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Cool. -Good lad.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.59,0:16:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.13,0:16:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 我们离开这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's get out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.80,0:16:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt... Jamie Tartt...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.35,0:16:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快点 守门员 -林克发现了机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Come on, goalie! -Link finds space.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.89,0:17:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他绕到后面射门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He rears back to shoot it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.31,0:17:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大中场球员漂亮的进球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A stunning goal by the Canadian midfielder!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.81,0:17:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-搞什么呢 -我讨厌那个没用的傻屌该死的拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fuck's sake! -I hate that poxy wanker! Fucking Lasso!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.85,0:17:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不过他家人不错 -该死的 保罗别帮他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Nice family though. -Damn it, Paul! Don't humanize him!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.11,0:17:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开局仅仅6分钟 里士满就以2-0落后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, after only six minutes, Richmond are 2-0 down.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.65,0:17:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker! Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.57,0:17:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满的支持者们正在发泄情绪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the Richmond supporters are making their feelings known.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.07,0:17:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker! Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.16,0:17:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯 不难推测 如果这种情况持续下去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chris, you have to think, if this continues,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.16,0:17:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索任教里士满的时间会很短 而且不会太好看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lasso's time with Richmond will be short and not very sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.12,0:17:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔特拿到了球 很聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tartt receives the ball. Clever there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.17,0:17:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-加油 杰米 -他找到了空挡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Go on, Jamie. -He finds space.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.88,0:17:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥比桑亚在他右侧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He has Obisanya on the right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.25,0:17:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有传球 他自己射门了 太漂亮了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, he's doing it himself. And what a finish!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.05,0:17:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特精彩的单人进球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt with an incredible solo goal!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.76,0:17:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特 你是该死的进球王\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt, you fucking king!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.97,0:17:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt... Jamie Tartt...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.31,0:17:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了这位新生代超级明星杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And thanks to budding superstar, Jamie Tartt,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.31,0:17:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满在29分钟时将比分变成2比1\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond are right back in it at 2-1 in the 29th minute!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.90,0:17:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我 -他在喊什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Me! -What's he yelling?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.19,0:17:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“我” 他在指着他后背的名字 不停地喊“我”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Me." He's pointing at the name on his back and repeatedly yelling "me."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.32,0:17:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.91,0:17:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为他在喊“肉”呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought he was saying "meat."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.16,0:18:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 是啊 “我”的确更说得通 好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But, yeah, yours makes a lot more sense. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.83,0:18:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-加油 -奥比桑亚阿加入了进攻阵容\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Come on! -Obisanya joins the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.25,0:18:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-尼日利亚人出局了 -狗屁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-The Nigerian is taken out! -Bullshit!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.54,0:18:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 裁判他们必须停止这种行为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, ref! They gotta knock that off!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.00,0:18:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本森会被罚黄牌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be a yellow card here for Benson.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.42,0:18:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个处罚太轻了 奥比桑亚还没站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you have to say he got off easy there. And Obisanya is still down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.26,0:18:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他可能受伤了 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He might be hurt. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.84,0:18:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.18,0:18:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂关心一下你的队友好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi! Check on your fucking teammate.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.52,0:18:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长在教育这个年轻的超级明星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The captain dispensing some wisdom to the young superstar.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.44,0:18:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing wrong with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.15,0:18:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-山姆 -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sam? -Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.98,0:18:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你移动一下 好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna have to move you there. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.32,0:18:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你他妈是不是有病 -这是什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What is your fucking problem? -What is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.91,0:18:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯特和塔特吵了起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kent and Tartt are at each other's throats!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.82,0:18:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 伙计们好了 别打了 -希望多数人都是清醒的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. Hey, guys! Come on! Knock it off! -Hopefully cooler heads will prevail.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.99,0:18:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈要杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fucking kill you!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.12,0:18:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是一队的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Same team!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.16,0:18:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这令人无法接受 阿尔洛 -克里斯 你有跟队友动过手吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Unacceptable, Arlo. -Chris, have you ever struck a teammate?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.25,0:18:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你疯了吗那又怎样 -没有 但我有过这个念头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Are you mad? So what? -No, but I've wanted to.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.33,0:18:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们是一队的 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He's my own player. -Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.54,0:18:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我其实有点羡慕 -你们得…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm actually a bit jealous. -You gotta be--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.59,0:18:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一次发生这种事还是2001年的纽卡斯尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We haven't seen this since 2001 in Newcastle.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.01,0:19:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满本赛季在输球的路上越走越远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And a season of lows for Richmond sinks even further still.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.39,0:19:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗 山姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You all right, Sam?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.68,0:19:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说 现在一点都不疼了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honestly, it doesn't even hurt anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.72,0:19:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但所有人都大动肝火 我觉得我应该继续趴着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But everyone was making such a fuss, I thought I should just stay down.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.56,0:19:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.10,0:19:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拉你起来 你要假装瘸得很厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna pull you up, you're gonna pretend to limp very badly,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.19,0:19:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后表现出一副你要勇敢撑下来的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you're gonna gesture like you think you can bravely go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.74,0:19:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们会喜欢的 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-They'll love it. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.62,0:19:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥比桑亚站起来了 但他能继续比赛吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obisanya is on his feet, but can he continue?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.79,0:19:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is he okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.58,0:19:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来他会带着伤痛比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks like he'll play through the pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.46,0:19:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么坚强的意志 这是大家喜欢看到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Such determination. You love to see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.54,0:19:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的 山姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Attaboy, Sam!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.13,0:19:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔特上前踢任意球 这是一个追平比分的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tartt steps up to take the free kick, with an opportunity to tie the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.42,0:19:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会传给队友还是直接射门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will he find a teammate or go for glory?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.01,0:19:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对塔特而言 这通常是一个反问句\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With Tartt, that's usually a rhetorical question.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.73,0:19:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他进了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he's done it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.56,0:19:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特第二个进球 里士满在38分钟时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's two for Jamie Tartt, and Richmond are level
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.82,0:19:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追平对手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the 38th minute!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.61,0:19:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是一个很特别的球员 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's a special player, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.40,0:20:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.24,0:20:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不禁要问 里士满要是没有他怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you have to wonder, where would Richmond be without him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.83,0:20:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.79,0:20:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me! Me!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.54,0:20:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还是第一次见 泰德拉索直接跑进了看台\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We certainly haven't seen this before. Ted Lasso is running into the stands.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.88,0:20:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, where the hell is he off to?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.01,0:20:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他丝毫没有慢下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's not slowing down on those steps.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.84,0:20:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德拉索的心肺功能真是令人刮目相看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's some real impressive cardio from Ted Lasso there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.68,0:20:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is he okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.56,0:20:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 瑞贝卡 -你好 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, Rebecca. -Hello, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.56,0:20:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你做得很好 爸爸 -是啊 你没问题的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You're doing great, Dad. -Yeah, you got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.60,0:20:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了 伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.69,0:20:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让杰米当替补\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna bench Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.94,0:20:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想先跟你说一声\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I didn't wanna do it without checking with you first.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.03,0:20:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 泰德 你是球队经理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But, Ted, you're the manager.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.94,0:20:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 不管你做什么决定 我都支持你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So whatever you decide, you have my full support.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.41,0:20:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 老板 好了 一会见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, boss. All right. Later, alligators.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.24,0:20:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见 爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bye, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.29,0:20:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德拉索似乎决定重新加入 已经在进行中的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And it appears Coach Lasso has decided to rejoin the match already in progress.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.46,0:20:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伯兹 热下身 一会你上场 快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roberts, warm up. You're going in. Let's go. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.13,0:20:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 荧光男 我们要换人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, highlighter. We got ourselves a sub.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.38,0:21:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-16号换下9号 好吗 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sixteen's going in for nine. Okay? -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.96,0:21:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 先生 谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Appreciate you, sir. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.43,0:21:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.89,0:21:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来拉索打算早早就换人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, it looks like Lasso is making an early substitution here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.81,0:21:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让罗伯兹下场 换下…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's bringing Roberts on, and he's taking off...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.94,0:21:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.03,0:21:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我们最好的球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's our best player!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.40,0:21:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.49,0:21:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't know what you're doing!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.03,0:21:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't know what you're doing! You don't know what you're doing!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.33,0:21:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What on earth?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.95,0:21:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要换下他最好的球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's taking off his best player.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.37,0:21:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而上半场只剩下不到一分钟了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And with less than a minute remaining in the half.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.92,0:21:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-傻屌 -16号 罗比罗伯兹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Wanker! Wanker! Wanker! -Number 16, Robbie Roberts,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.96,0:21:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替换9号 杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for number 9, Jamie Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.59,0:21:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你的表现很棒 为我们拉回了比分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, way to play out there. Way to get us back in.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.55,0:21:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴吧 该死的蠢蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut up. Fucking stupid twat.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.55,0:21:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裁判看了看表 上半场结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The referee looks at his watch, and that's halftime.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.76,0:21:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在更衣室里 等待拉索的会是怎样的反应呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of reception awaits Lasso in his locker room?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.68,0:21:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（塔特）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.86,0:22:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 坐下仔细听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi, sit down and listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.66,0:22:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们打平了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got ourselves a tied game.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.33,0:22:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice work.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.75,0:22:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我们处于被压制的状态 必须改变这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fellas, we're broken. We need to change.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.17,0:22:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我知道改变会很吓人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, look, I know change can be scary.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.84,0:22:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一秒 你还在课间休息时 跟朋友们一起玩“一二三木头人”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One minute, you're playing freeze tag out there at recess with all your buddies.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.85,0:22:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一秒 你就长了青春痘 声音变得沙哑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next thing you know, you're getting zits, your voice gets low.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.31,0:22:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次你的美术老师斯坎隆小姐弯下身子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And every time your art teacher, Ms. Scanlon, leans over your desk
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查看你的作业进度 你内心都小鹿乱撞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to check and see how your project's going, you feel all squiggly inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.28,0:22:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是一个迷人的女人 不是传统意义上的美女 但依然很迷人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was a striking woman. Not classically beautiful, but striking.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.32,0:22:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我第一次看到晒痕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}First time I ever saw tan lines.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.99,0:22:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分时候 改变是好事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Most of the time, change is a good thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.45,0:22:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为我们现在需要的就是改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I think that's what it's all about.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.83,0:23:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥抱改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Embracing change.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.75,0:23:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢一些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Being brave.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.34,0:23:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做你必须做的 这样你人生中的每一个人…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doing whatever you have to, so that everyone in your life...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.55,0:23:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能继续他们各自的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}can move forward with theirs.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.76,0:23:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为或许…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause maybe...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.18,0:23:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你唯一可以让她幸福的方法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's the only way you can truly help her be happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.32,0:23:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然 我说的“她”是指“足球女士”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously by "her," I'm referring to Lady Football.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.49,0:23:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都能圆回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good save.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.74,0:23:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆 下半场我们要把你换到中场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sam, we're gonna shift you to midfield for the second half.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.62,0:23:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的改变 彼尔德会告诉你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Beard's gonna walk y'all through the rest of the changes.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.25,0:23:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 还有一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, hey, hey. One last thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.04,0:23:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望我说话的时候所有人都能看着我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I want everyone's eyes on me when I say this. Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.59,0:23:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（相信）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.76,0:23:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我就没喜欢过塔特 -我们都知道 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Never really liked Tartt. -We know, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.05,0:23:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人 过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everybody, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.97,0:23:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有两分钟补时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two minutes of added time remaining.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.89,0:24:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双方依然是二比二平\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still level at two goals apiece.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.10,0:24:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满踢得很好 即使没有杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond have played well, even without Jamie Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.69,0:24:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.23,0:24:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没人防守 就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's open. He's open. He's open. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.86,0:24:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个直塞传球 从科伯恩身边划过 肯特接到球开始加速\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A through ball from Cockburn. And Kent is off to the races!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.82,0:24:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.78,0:24:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯特只需要击败一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kent has only one man to beat.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.45,0:24:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可以自己射门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He could take it himself,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.99,0:24:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他多传了一次 传给无人防守的奥比桑亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but he makes the extra pass to a wide open Obisanya!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.83,0:24:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他稳稳地踢进了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he buries it!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.63,0:24:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.22,0:24:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满领先 此时补时仅剩下不到一分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond take the lead with barely a minute of stoppage time left.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.77,0:24:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满第三个进球的球员 是24号山姆奥比桑亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Scorer for Richmond's third goal, number 24, Sam Obisanya.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.03,0:24:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.03,0:24:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起我太开心了 -没事 我喜欢我喜欢这股能量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm so sorry! I'm just so happy! -No, I love it! I love this energy!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.00,0:25:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-给 教练 帮我抱着这家伙 -太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Here, Coach. Take this guy from me. -Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.00,0:25:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the way you do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.09,0:25:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮 先生们干得好 就是这样好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nicely done, gentlemen! Nicely done! Way to do it! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.97,0:25:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做的那个决定 太有种了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Took balls, what you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.80,0:25:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就只有这个而已 罗伊 我们就只有这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's all we got is balls, Roy. It's all we got.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.55,0:25:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的耶就是这样 做得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right! Yeah! There you go. Way to play.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.52,0:25:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about that, Coach?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.69,0:25:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吗 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You hear that, Coach?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.44,0:25:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker! Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.52,0:25:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是同一个词 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, same word, ain't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.23,0:25:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 但是意义不同了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, but different.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.07,0:25:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉像回到了80年代 当时坏的意思就是好 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, kinda like back in the '80s when bad meant good, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.03,0:25:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时谁是总统来着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who was president back then?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.08,0:25:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-罗纳德里根 -罗纳德里根那个演员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ronald Reagan. -"Ronald Reagan? The actor?"
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.37,0:25:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计 我喜欢你模仿布朗博士 真是活灵活现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, man. I love it when you do Doc Brown. You walked me right into that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.47,0:25:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Daddy! Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.89,0:26:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿你来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey! There he is!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.52,0:26:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得怎么样我们赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about that, huh? We won one.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.39,0:26:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸 -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Daddy? -Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.48,0:26:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's a wanker?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.77,0:26:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛 孩子 意思是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, kiddo. That is a...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.40,0:26:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个喜欢自力更生的男人 明白了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a man that likes to be alone with his thoughts. Make sense?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.90,0:26:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你看得更清楚一点 准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's give you a better view of all this. Ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.36,0:26:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上来吧 孩子 看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get up there, kiddo. Look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.20,0:26:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向大家挥挥手 就是这样 让他们知道 让他们看到 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wave to the people. That's it. Let them know. Let them see, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.50,0:26:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.38,0:26:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.80,0:26:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.63,0:26:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想我们初次相遇的情景 当时我们还在念书\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just keep thinking about the first time we met, back at school.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.64,0:26:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个老旧的停车场里只有我们两个人 在同一时间出现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Us being the only two people in that big old parking lot at the exact same time.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.94,0:26:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太巧了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So random.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.73,0:26:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们无从知晓我们的故事将从那里开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No way for us to know that it was going to be the start of something.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.61,0:26:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -我吓到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey. -Did I scare you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.11,0:27:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大晚上的在停车场里悄悄靠近一个女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You snuck up on a woman in a parking lot at night.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.62,0:27:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 罗伊 干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, Roy, well done.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.74,0:27:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我是个白痴 昨天我也干了一件很白痴的事 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. I'm an idiot. I was also an idiot yesterday, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.92,0:27:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.42,0:27:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good night, Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.63,0:27:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good night, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.05,0:27:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回头去看我们经历的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I look back at everything we've been through,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.31,0:27:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不愿意有哪怕一丁点的改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I wouldn't change a single thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.27,0:27:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是现在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.31,0:27:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.61,0:27:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米歇尔 如果有什么我能做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, if there is something I could... do
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.86,0:27:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是我能说的 只要能让你开心…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or something I could say that would make you be happy...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.57,0:27:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我在一起 我都愿意去做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just being with me, I'd do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.66,0:27:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会毫不犹豫地去做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd do it in a nanosecond.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.45,0:27:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我什么都控制不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I ain't got no control over any of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.91,0:27:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必再努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't have to keep trying anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.17,0:27:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.80,0:27:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会有事的 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna be okay. Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.56,0:28:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 快踢 很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, quick feet. There we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.43,0:28:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.27,0:28:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟自己发过誓 我这辈子绝不对放弃任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I promised myself I would never quit anything in my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.06,0:28:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不是放弃 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you're not quitting, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.69,0:28:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是放我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're just letting me go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.91,0:28:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.49,0:28:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.04,0:28:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.12,0:28:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯 -嗯 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Yes. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.58,0:28:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不客气 -谢谢你 珊农 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's all right. -I appreciate you, Shannon. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.88,0:28:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 伙计 赛季一结束我就去看你 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, buddy. I'm gonna see you the second after the season's over, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.63,0:28:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们每天都要聊天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we're gonna talk every day?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.43,0:28:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 和从前一样 小伙子 你知道的 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Absolutely. Just like we do, big guy. You know it. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.01,0:28:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 给我一个拥抱 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, gimme a hug, please. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.56,0:28:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay now, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.27,0:28:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我爱你 去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I love you. Go ahead, get on.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.88,0:30:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 傻屌 今晚干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi, wanker. Good job tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.38,0:30:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.80,0:30:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看着我们 我们也许能翻盘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep an eye on us. We might be turning this thing around.
