[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.97,0:00:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, mon cher.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.02,0:00:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach! Over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.15,0:00:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.65,0:00:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Z哥 丹尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Z-man, Dani.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看上去像是一个美丽的天使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He looks like a beautiful angel-man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.04,0:00:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good morning, sunshine.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.33,0:00:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.75,0:00:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想错过出发时间 所以我就睡这了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't want to miss the bus, so I just slept in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.21,0:00:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我想吐 对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, I'm gonna vomit. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.33,0:00:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.64,0:00:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我在干什么这他妈是我的房间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait. What am I doing? This is my fucking room.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.76,0:01:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi! Out.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.39,0:01:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（我们找到内特了 他在“宿醉城”）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.77,0:01:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.77,0:01:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 早上好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. Good morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.77,0:01:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你煮了咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got you a coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.61,0:01:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.23,0:01:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很早就醒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You been up long?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.32,0:01:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一两个小时吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hour or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.82,0:01:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想 一共三个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know? I guess three hours total.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.24,0:01:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last night was fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.62,0:01:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 五星好评 “新鲜认证”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah. Five stars. Certified fresh.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.25,0:01:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是不是得走了 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Have you got to go? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.42,0:01:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你不必着急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But, you know, you don't need to rush out or anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.00,0:01:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你延长了退房时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got you a late checkout.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.84,0:01:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真体贴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's very thoughtful of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 你该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on then. You go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.63,0:01:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要再睡个回笼觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna go back to sleep,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.01,0:01:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再点上一顿丰盛的早餐 记在你账上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then I'm gonna order a huge breakfast on your tab.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.97,0:01:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常专业了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a pro move right there. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.06,0:01:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意随时为你买单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I'll be your Underhills anytime.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.81,0:01:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 那就再见了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Well... I'll see you around, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.65,0:02:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.36,0:02:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.48,0:02:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-教练 -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Coach. -Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.82,0:02:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你心里有事吗 教练 -没有 怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Something on your mind, Coach? -No, why?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.90,0:02:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚坐了五小时的大巴 但你一句话都没说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just had a five-hour bus ride where you didn't talk a lick,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.45,0:02:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你平时一直说个不停的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that's a record by about five hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.41,0:02:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我要告诉你一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, look. I'm gonna tell you something
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.25,0:02:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这件事我以后都不想再提起 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but then I don't wanna talk about it ever again, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.38,0:02:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -我是认真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. -I'm serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.04,0:02:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望你拿这件事开玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want to make jokes about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.55,0:02:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者给我那种“心照不宣”的眼神\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want you giving me any knowing glances.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.05,0:02:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-明白我的意思吗好 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You know what I mean? Okay. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.93,0:03:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上 我…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last night, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.93,0:03:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟瑞贝卡的朋友靓女睡了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I slept with Rebecca's friend Sassy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.27,0:03:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想聊聊吗 -对 我想聊 立刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Want to talk about it? -I'd love to. Yeah. Immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.90,0:03:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这儿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这房间不是闹鬼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought this room was haunted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.74,0:03:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了 我们已经解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. We sorted that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.20,0:03:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在方便吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is now a good time?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.87,0:03:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 你进来吧 她戴着耳机 听不见我们说话的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. You can come in. She can't hear anything with those in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.16,0:03:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.24,0:03:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盖尔 你认为皇室都是蜥蜴人 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gail, you think the royal family are lizards, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.08,0:03:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,23岁 好年轻啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Twenty-three. So young.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.33,0:03:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在听什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's she listening to?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.75,0:03:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还能听什么 谋杀案播客节目\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Always murder podcasts.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.22,0:03:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚真够疯狂的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last night was crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.88,0:03:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 太草率了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, yeah. It was pretty sloppy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.14,0:03:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在需要喝一杯咖啡缓解宿醉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could really use a bucket of coffee to nurse this hangover.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.81,0:03:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你完事了可以去帮我买吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you wanna go get one with me when you're done?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.02,0:03:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不行 我很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not today. I can't. I'm busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.77,0:03:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在撒谎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.57,0:04:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我要请你先出去一下了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. I'm gonna have to ask you to leave,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.61,0:04:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她就快按到我的大肌腱了 我会忍不住叫出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause she's about to go to town on my hamstrings and I make a lot of noises,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.66,0:04:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让别人听到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I don't like people hearing my noises.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.49,0:04:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那一会见了 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cool. All right. I'll see you around, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.37,0:04:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.58,0:04:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这不是我通常会做的事 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause, look, it's just not something I've ever done before, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.83,0:04:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是在批评玩一夜情的人 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And look, I got no judgment on people that have one-night stands, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.34,0:04:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你就好这口 那随意 这是我想说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, if you are, you know, nuts for butts, have at it. That's what I say.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.55,0:04:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你爽到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, did you have fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.76,0:04:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 教练 我不想聊这些细节的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Coach. I don't like all that kiss-and-tell stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.47,0:04:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你爽到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, did you have fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.19,0:04:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她爽到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And did she have fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.94,0:04:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你晃得我都恶心了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that movement's making me feel queasy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.24,0:04:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那还有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. So, then what's the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.03,0:04:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是因为我还不能接受这个事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, maybe I just haven't really come to peace with the fact
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.82,0:04:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一秒我还在利物浦的K歌房崩溃大哭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I went from having a mental breakdown at a karaoke joint in Liverpool
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.16,0:04:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一秒我就跟这个刚认识的女人睡了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to, you know, sleeping with a woman I just met.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.62,0:04:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我还顺便离了个婚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then somewhere in between there, getting a divorce.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.17,0:04:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得说得通 -我必须得说 这太美妙了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Well, it makes sense to me. -I must say that this is lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.63,0:04:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我很小的时候起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ever since I was little,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.71,0:05:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就梦想着能和一群哥们坐在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I always used to dream about sitting down with a bunch of mates
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.92,0:05:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈论男女之间复杂的感情故事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}talking about the complex dynamics between men and women.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.55,0:05:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 各位 我还有一个问题 我应该告诉瑞贝卡吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, here's another question for y'all. Should I tell Rebecca?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.10,0:05:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别 -拜托 为什么不说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. -Come on now. Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.27,0:05:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我发现她对我有所隐瞒 我一定会很伤心的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, it'd break my heart if I found out she was hiding something from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.65,0:05:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么回事你们在开会吗 -对 我遇到了和女人有关的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What's happening? You having a meeting? -Yep. I'm having lady problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.44,0:05:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想问问你的意见 -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'd love to get your perspective on it. -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.82,0:05:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 我能跟你说实话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, can I be honest with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.03,0:05:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let it rip.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.32,0:05:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你似乎对自己过于苛刻了 为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You seem intent on going 12 rounds with yourself. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.04,0:05:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做错什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you do wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.08,0:05:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.91,0:05:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候做这个了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Time to get you some of these.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.67,0:05:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 剪子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What, scissors?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.75,0:05:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 剪掉障碍 放松点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. To cut yourself some slack.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.50,0:05:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.55,0:05:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真是步调一致 这个梗都能接住 厉害了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Y'all stuck the landing on that. That was nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.09,0:05:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得给你们几个定制一批缎面外套\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell you what, I gotta get you all some satin jackets made,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.89,0:05:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背面绣上“泰德拉索的私人情感智囊团”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with "Ted Lasso's Personal Dilemma Squad" embroidered on the back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.56,0:05:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这名字太长了 肯定有更好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a clunky name. There's gotta be something better here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.64,0:05:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我想想 我知道了 “情商战士”怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me think. I know. How about the "EQ Warriors"?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.65,0:06:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“支持骑士”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The "Knights of Support"?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.86,0:06:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了吧 听上去像是护裆牌子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nah. Sounds like a brand of jockstrap.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.32,0:06:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“骄傲男孩”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The "Proud Boys"?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.37,0:06:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“钻石狗”怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about the "Diamond Dogs"?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.78,0:06:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的 内特 就叫钻石狗了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Attaboy, Nate. Diamond Dogs it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.75,0:06:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（如果你的“事情”提前弄完了 告诉我一声）
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.34,0:06:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.84,0:06:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（我们可以去喝一杯）
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.02,0:06:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这会应该在曼彻斯特啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you were supposed to be in Manchester.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.98,0:06:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们跟西汉姆打比赛 所以我在城里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We played West Ham, so I'm in town.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.44,0:06:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 进来吧 你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Come in. How you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.73,0:06:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.44,0:06:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我碰了十次球 带球两次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had ten touches, I had two completed dribbles,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.15,0:06:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在98分钟的时候 他们让我踢了一个任意球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and in the 89th minute they let me take a free kick.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进了 小弟弟勃起了一半\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I scored. Got half a chub.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.95,0:06:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你打算把勃起了一半的小弟弟 送到我这来 是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you thought you'd bring your half-chub over here then, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.20,0:06:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我只是…想跟你聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. No, I just... wanted to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.29,0:07:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索抛弃我的时候一切都发生得太快了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, everything happened so fast when Lasso dumped me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.88,0:07:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 说什么呢 拉索才没有抛弃你 是曼城把你要回去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi. Come on. Lasso didn't dump you. Man City wanted you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.75,0:07:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 拉索本可以阻止这件事 但他没有 所以是他抛弃了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. Lasso could have stopped it, but he didn't. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.55,0:07:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我把话说完 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just let me finish, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.43,0:07:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟很多女孩约会过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I dated a lot of girls, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.93,0:07:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你在已经很优秀的杰米身上 看到了更加优秀的可能性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you, you saw an even greater Jamie inside an already great Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.35,0:07:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我变得更有文化了 你带我去看演出之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You made me cultured. Took me to plays and shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.61,0:07:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你很讨厌那些啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You hated all of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.02,0:07:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 因为那让人很困惑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, 'cause it's confusing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.19,0:07:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总是演一些情绪化的东西 让你情感泛滥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They do all these emotional things, make you feel all these emotional ways.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.40,0:07:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是真当你宣泄出来 大声喊出来 或是在演出时说话时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then they get mad when you start trying to shout out
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.74,0:07:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们又不乐意了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and talk to them during a performance.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.32,0:07:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太奇怪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.00,0:07:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还教会我不要太我行我素\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You also taught me to try to not get in me own way so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.75,0:07:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…谢谢你做的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So... thank you for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.13,0:07:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're welcome, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.09,0:07:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你第一次来我家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, this is the first time you've been over to this house
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.43,0:07:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却没发奇怪的色情表情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you haven't sent me some, like, weird sex emoji.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.51,0:08:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-比如说茄子或是喷水 -或是小松鼠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Like the eggplant or the squirting water. -Or the little squirrel.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.14,0:08:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小松鼠 我一直都不懂那是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The little squirrel. I never understood that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.27,0:08:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它握着一个坚果 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, he's holding a little nut, isn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.31,0:08:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.61,0:08:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He is. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.24,0:08:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.32,0:08:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跟我喝一杯吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you wanna have a drink with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.91,0:08:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.20,0:08:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你说的“喝一杯”是指…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unless by "drink" you mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.83,0:08:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这就是你的套路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So that's how you get sex?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.46,0:08:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从不说自己想要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By not trying for sex?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.84,0:08:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候这样才有用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sometimes that is exactly how it works.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.38,0:08:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never knew that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.52,0:08:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Morning, boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.39,0:08:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你不仅有饼干吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, you don't just get biscuits today.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.81,0:08:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还给你买了一盒松露巧克力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I also got you a little box of chocolate truffles.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.65,0:08:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你这个混蛋 别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, you fucker. Don't do this to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.99,0:08:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该拿一块松露\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you should do is take one of them truffles
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.61,0:08:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夹在两块饼干之间 就像一个小号的早餐三明治…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and smoosh it in between the biscuits like it's a little breakfast sandwich--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.32,0:08:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 好了 就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, there you go. You got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.28,0:08:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.08,0:09:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我想再次谢谢你 在利物浦的时候对我的支持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. And hey, I wanna thank you again for being there for me up in Liverpool.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.79,0:09:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没什么 泰德 -不 那对我意义重大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It was nothing, Ted. -No, no. It was something.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.00,0:09:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在欠你一份人情 小姑娘 有什么事尽管找我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got a coupon for life, young lady. Yeah. I got your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.92,0:09:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把我当成是你私人的圣伯纳犬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think of me as your own personal metaphorical Saint Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.30,0:09:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要一个人面对雪崩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't need to be dealing with a metaphorical avalanche
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.97,0:09:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挂在我脖子上的波旁酒会解救你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to avail yourself to the metaphorical bourbon hanging around my neck.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.31,0:09:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是打个比方 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Metaphorically speaking. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.02,0:09:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.10,0:09:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.94,0:09:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想帮忙的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you do want to be there for me,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.85,0:09:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一会要跟俱乐部的两个小股东开会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have a meeting later with two minority owners of the club.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.19,0:09:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛奶姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Milk sisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.28,0:09:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集合了人类最可怕的特质\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The most horrible human cocktail
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.49,0:09:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅枯燥乏味 还喋喋不休\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of being terribly dull and yet, they never shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.07,0:09:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我一起去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please join me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.16,0:09:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Done and doner.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.12,0:09:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 我只需要给你们介绍一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Perfect. I can just introduce you all,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.12,0:09:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你留在那里说一些有的别的 然后悄悄开溜去做其他事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}leave you wittering on, and slip out and do anything else.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.91,0:09:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们拥有俱乐部多少股份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much of the club they own?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.12,0:09:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn微软雅黑}{\b0}{\fs12}{\3c&H000000&}{\shad1}2.9%\N2.9%.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.38,0:09:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就取个整数 叫她们“2%牛奶”好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna round that down to two. Then I can call those gals the "2% Milks."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.38,0:09:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 他们一定会喜欢你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God. They're gonna adore you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.05,0:09:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会很有趣的 好了 我不打扰你了 再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna be fun. All right. I'll leave you be. See ya now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.09,0:10:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以我的经验来看 我发现如果你真心相信一件产品\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In my experience, I've always found that endorsements work best
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.60,0:10:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那赞助的效果是最好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you really believe in the product.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.10,0:10:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 如果你们告诉我你们的喜好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I can find good opportunities for you guys
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.81,0:10:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以为你们找到很好的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you let me know what you're into.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.60,0:10:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢飞人乔丹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love Air Jordans.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.61,0:10:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我跟一双乔丹鞋做爱我都愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd fuck a pair of Jordans.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.73,0:10:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 所以算运动服饰 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. So, athletic wear then, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.53,0:10:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢问题导向的产品\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm into issue-oriented products.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.61,0:10:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,环保的、反污染的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, pro-environment or anti-pollution.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.49,0:10:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这类东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That kind of thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.61,0:10:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 还有乔丹鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, and also Air Jordans.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.49,0:10:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想跟鞋睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I don't want to sleep with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.28,0:10:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾萨克 你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Isaac, what about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.29,0:10:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗华利糖果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rolos.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.21,0:10:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以是糖果和巧克力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, sweets and chocolate then?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.63,0:10:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我只爱罗华利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Just Rolos, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.88,0:10:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那种又酸又甜的软糖 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And none of that Sour Patch bullshit either, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.46,0:10:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.59,0:10:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个很好的开始 谢谢各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, that's a great start from you guys. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.35,0:10:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.22,0:10:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.31,0:10:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡说我可以暂时在这里办公\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rebecca's letting me use this room as my office
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.23,0:10:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会给我再找一个合适的地方 所以我准备了一个盒子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until she sets me up with somewhere proper. That's why I have this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.02,0:10:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要用这个房间 我就把所有东西装进盒子里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So if they need to use the room, I can just shove everything into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.77,0:10:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常高效 你一会想看电影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Efficient. Do you want to see a movie later?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.44,0:10:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你这人是怎么回事 -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What the fuck is wrong with you? -What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.57,0:11:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨天问你要不要跟我喝咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I asked you if you wanted to go get coffee with me yesterday
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.78,0:11:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说你很忙 -我确实忙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-and you said you were busy. -I was busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.62,0:11:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你昨晚也没回我短信 -是啊 因为我很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You never texted me back last night. -Yeah. I was busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.12,0:11:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个吻呢你亲到一半停了 好像那个吻很烂一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about the kiss? You took off like it was a shit kiss,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.12,0:11:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不烂 我可有激情了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it was not a shit kiss. I was on fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.08,0:11:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我同意 -所以你到底有什么毛病 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I agree. -So what is your fucking problem, Roy?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.96,0:11:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我是一个职业足球运动员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, I'm a professional footballer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.38,0:11:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有过无数次一夜情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have had a million one-night stands.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.59,0:11:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我也是 -好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-So have I. -Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.67,0:11:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不知道为什么咱俩开始炫耀上了 -我也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I don't know why we're bragging about it. -Neither do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.59,0:11:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那些一夜情都让人觉得空虚 一开始不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And they always feel empty. Well, not the first part.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.68,0:11:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对 一开始很棒的 -超级棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No, at first they're wicked. -They're fucking great.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.72,0:11:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但等一切结束之后 我感觉… -糟透了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-But when it's all done, I feel like-- -Like shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.10,0:11:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 而且每次要么是我的手表被偷了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Exactly. And I always end up with my watch being stolen
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.23,0:11:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者媒体刊登了 我小弟弟是弯曲的这种花边新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or a story in the press about how my penis has a curve in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.69,0:11:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does it actually?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.06,0:11:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我只是利用臀部 让女方感觉上是弯的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I just make it feel like it does with my hips.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.98,0:11:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 重点是 我在尝试换一种方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anyway, the point is, I'm trying to do this differently.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.53,0:11:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该早点告诉你的 我道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should have told you that. I apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.53,0:11:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以后会努力更加坦诚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I am trying to be more honest.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.29,0:11:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.04,0:11:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.92,0:11:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我应该告诉你 我跟杰米睡了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think you should know that I slept with Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.96,0:11:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I am aware of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.13,0:11:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说昨晚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.26,0:12:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你不喜欢我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't think you were into me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.97,0:12:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你的想法 但我当时明确知道他的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't know what you wanted, and I knew exactly what he wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.47,0:12:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你因为我无意识犯的错 跟他睡觉来报复我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you fucked him to get back at me for something I didn't even know I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.64,0:12:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我…不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I-- No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.56,0:12:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.73,0:12:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.31,0:12:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说对了 就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yup. That's exactly what I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.57,0:12:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞砸了 罗伊 我真的很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I fucked up, Roy. I'm really sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.49,0:12:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不能发火\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I need you to be okay with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如等你想好了怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, why don't you just come and tell me how you feel about it
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.99,0:12:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来跟我谈谈你的想法吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}once you've figured out how to speak again?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（成功金字塔）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.34,0:12:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.10,0:12:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有心事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something on your mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.60,0:12:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就打算一直用哼哼回答我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that grunt all I get to go on?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.36,0:12:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 我尝试猜一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's okay. I'll give it a shot here. Let's see.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.03,0:13:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在考虑买第一套房子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are thinking about buying your first house.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.86,0:13:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not that. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.28,0:13:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚发现你爸可能有一点种族歧视\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You just realized your dad might be a little racist.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.58,0:13:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了 他60多岁了 而且来自伦敦南部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop. He's in his 60s and he's from South London.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.20,0:13:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸当然会有一点种族歧视了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course my dad's a little racist.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.62,0:13:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样 我和基莉互相有好感\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, me and Keeley might be starting up a thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.46,0:13:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但每次我想起她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but every time I think about her,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.96,0:13:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我满脑子都是该死的杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all I think about is Jamie fucking Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.72,0:13:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来某人陷入了人生中最复杂的几何形状\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sounds to me like someone's trapped inside life's most complicated shape.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.68,0:13:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三角恋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A love triangle.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.76,0:13:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 第二复杂的是 “我撞见了我岳母\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Second place of course is the "I just walked in on my mother-in-law
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.02,0:13:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换泳衣”的十二面体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}changing into her swimsuit" dodecahedron.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.18,0:13:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的表情像是有兴趣 跟你开几何形状玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does my face look like it's in the mood for shape-based jokes?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.98,0:13:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像 罗伊 一点都不像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Roy, it does not.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.98,0:13:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我替自己辩解一句 你这张脸一直都很严肃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But, in my defense, it rarely does.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.02,0:13:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我知道这时候该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know exactly what to do here, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.03,0:13:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.65,0:13:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 毛茸茸的小家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you fret, my fine furry fella.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.74,0:13:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过几分钟 你的感情烦恼就会成为过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In a matter of minutes, your relationship dilemma will be in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.79,0:13:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我召集了钻石狗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For I am rounding up the Diamond Dogs.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.66,0:13:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻石狗是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who the fuck are the Diamond Dogs?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.37,0:13:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一群关心他人的人 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just a group of people who care, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.75,0:14:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像那些在街舞音乐会上 连手都不愿举的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not unlike folks at a hip-hop concert whose hands are not in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.96,0:14:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 这是关于你跟基莉 对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, so this is about you and Keeley, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.67,0:14:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早料到了 -跟早年的恋爱不一样喽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Saw this coming. -Nothing like the early days of courtship.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.89,0:14:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这他妈是搞笑呢吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, this is my fucking nightmare.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.68,0:14:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你跟基莉就像是饼干和奶油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think the idea of you and Keeley is like cookies and cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.60,0:14:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都同意吧 两种美味结合 变得更好吃了 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I think we all agree, two great tastes that go great together, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.98,0:14:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对 -完美的类比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Perfect analogy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.27,0:14:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我喜欢她 但我们都知道 她前男友是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I am into her. But we all know who her ex-boyfriend is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.11,0:14:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋中的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The prince prick of all pricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.23,0:14:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我满脑子都是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I've got him stuck right in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.44,0:14:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't understand the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.90,0:14:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉人多好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, Keeley's just so kind.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.65,0:14:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被她那样的人喜欢一定…很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, to be liked by someone like her must be... 's wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.41,0:14:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如格什温兄弟的歌中所唱的那样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shout out to the Gershwin brothers right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.37,0:14:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得对 格什温兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck yeah, the Gershwins.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.79,0:14:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是该死的 伙计们 你们还没明白 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But dang it, fellas, you're still not getting it!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.50,0:14:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.54,0:14:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然罗伊过去也睡过很多人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure, Roy here has slept with a bunch of different people in his past.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.50,0:14:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但基莉的恋爱史和性史早于罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But Keeley's got her own romantic and sexual history that predates Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.63,0:14:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that's not okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.88,0:14:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说的是反话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He means the opposite.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.30,0:14:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢教练用反讽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love it when Coach does sarcasm.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.76,0:14:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我控制不了自己的情绪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't control my feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.31,0:14:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那既然如此 就让它们控制你好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, then by all means you should let them control you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.23,0:14:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's doing it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.89,0:15:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好眼力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good eye.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.15,0:15:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 罗伊 我不阴阳怪气了 帮我个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Roy, all this Chandler Bing-ing aside, do me a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.07,0:15:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让她的过去影响到你们的未来 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't let her past muck around with y'all's future, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.44,0:15:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她昨晚跟他上床了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She slept with him last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.24,0:15:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们在正式交往吗 -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I mean, are you two officially dating? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.12,0:15:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们已经睡过了 -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Have you already slept together? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.16,0:15:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你想做个总结吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, you wanna bring this home?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.16,0:15:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么幼稚 接受吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Grow up and get over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.50,0:15:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻石狗又得一分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Diamond Dogs have struck again.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.72,0:15:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都是混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're all pricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.01,0:15:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（富勒史密斯和特纳 奇西克艾尔啤酒和黑啤）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.39,0:15:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 看到牛奶姐妹了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All righty. See the Milk sisters anywhere?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.93,0:15:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要我去后面搜查一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want me to go skim the back room?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.23,0:15:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别让我后悔这个决定 泰德 -别担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Don't make me regret this, Ted. -Don't worry, don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.31,0:15:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会做个十足的绅士的 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna be an udder gentleman, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.06,0:15:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看过《BJ单身日记》吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I wonder if they've ever seen the movie Bridget Jones's Dairy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.53,0:15:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 这不算“牛奶”双关 我再想个好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, that's not my breast milk pun. I can do better.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.53,0:15:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 这个主意太糟了 我是认真的 你回家吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God, this was a horrible idea. Seriously, please go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.12,0:15:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拜托 一定会很有趣的 -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Come on. It's gonna be fun. -Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.41,0:15:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在这儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.42,0:16:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁伯特 你在这里做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rupert, what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.63,0:16:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是来庆祝的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We came to celebrate.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.96,0:16:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡 这是瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rebecca, Rebecca. Rebecca, Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.75,0:16:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴又见到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's nice to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.63,0:16:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是泰德 -你好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-And this is Ted. -Howdy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.93,0:16:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们一起喝点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Join us for a drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.84,0:16:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 鲁伯特 还要点别的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go, Rupert. Anything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.31,0:16:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我们的朋友也来一杯 谢谢 梅\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A couple more glasses for our friends here. Thank you, Mae.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.43,0:16:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和从前一样漂亮 从你的西区到大理石拱门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are as delicious as ever. From your West End to your Marble Arch.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.48,0:16:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你裤裆里的大本钟看紧了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep your Big Ben in your pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.15,0:16:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的邀请\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you for your invitation,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.32,0:16:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们是来见牛奶姐妹的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we're actually here to meet with the Milk sisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.20,0:16:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They won't be coming now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.66,0:16:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 真糟 他们是过期了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no. Did they expire?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.41,0:16:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.33,0:16:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, yeah, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.16,0:16:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我不能拥有俱乐部的股权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know I'm not allowed an ownership stake in the club,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.67,0:16:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们很乐意将自己的份额卖给贝克丝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but they were nice enough to sell their minority share to Bex here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.13,0:16:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以为我得先把助学贷款还完了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I always thought I'd finish paying off my student loans
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.80,0:16:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能考虑买下一个足球俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before I purchased a football club.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.14,0:16:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然 她需要我提供一点财政支持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously, she needed a little financial aid from yours truly.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.97,0:17:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是等我们结婚了 她的就是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But, well, when we're married, what's hers will be mine
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.43,0:17:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的…还是我的 这是我从你身上吸取的教训\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and what's mine... well, that'll stay mine 'cause I've learned from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.65,0:17:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们订婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're engaged?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.11,0:17:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 恭喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. Congratulations.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.91,0:17:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们还是喝一杯吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you better join us for a drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.28,0:17:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人 跟我们喝一杯 我买单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone! Drinks with us. It's on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.79,0:17:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三大杯 谢谢 梅 反正免费的 我们要最大的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Three lagers, please, Mae. They're free. We want the boots.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.50,0:17:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬里士满 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.54,0:17:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond! Richmond! Richmond! Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.42,0:17:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond! Richmond! Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.38,0:17:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 你最想合作的产品是“快乐”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. The product you'd most like to get into business with is joy?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.26,0:17:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 很多很多快乐\NSí. Mucho, mucho joy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.56,0:17:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定是否会有人愿意付钱给你 丹尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know if I can get you paid for that though, Dani.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.18,0:17:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意免费分享快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I like to give away joy for free.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.14,0:17:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 谢谢 丹尼 -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-All right, thanks, Dani. -You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.27,0:17:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 足球就是生命 队长\NHey. Football is life, Capitán.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.44,0:17:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yup.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.24,0:17:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再为杰米生气了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm done being mad about Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.41,0:18:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一个成年人 我不是小孩子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm a grown man. I'm not a baby child.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.33,0:18:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事翻篇了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.75,0:18:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 你介意跟房间里剩下的人 也说一遍吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Would you mind saying that to the rest of the room?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媒体有权利知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, the press deserves to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.84,0:18:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯特先生 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.97,0:18:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好 -嗨 我《独立报》的基莉琼斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Hi. Keeley Jones, The Independent Woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.56,0:18:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能重复一遍刚才说的话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Would you please repeat what you just said?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.18,0:18:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我翻篇了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.98,0:18:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚能约你出去吗拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I take you out tonight? Please?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.90,0:18:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. You.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.86,0:18:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉琼斯 《独立报》线上版\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley Jones, The Independent Woman Online Edition.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.41,0:18:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么要相信你的突然转变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, why should I trust this sudden change of heart?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.33,0:18:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我爱你胜过我恨他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I like you more than I hate him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.62,0:18:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就差一点 非常接近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, barely. It's very close.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.96,0:18:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有头发的那位女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Woman with the hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.50,0:18:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉琼斯 《独立报女性杂志》的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley Jones, The Independent Woman Magazine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.55,0:18:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我同意你会带我去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where would you take me if I did say yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.34,0:19:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知道 喝咖啡 -就不能再好点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I don't know. Coffee? -Can't do any better?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.60,0:19:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-吃晚餐 -好 听起来很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Dinner. -Yeah, that sounds great.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.06,0:19:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位长眼睛的女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, woman with the fucking eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.23,0:19:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉琼斯 《独立报》女性周日插页版\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley Jones, The Independent Woman insert on Sunday.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.11,0:19:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能解释一下你是怎样利用屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could you please elaborate on the hip movement
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.03,0:19:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来让小弟弟感觉是弯的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that makes your penis feel like it has a curve in it?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.49,0:19:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 提问环节到此为止 我们球场上见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, no more questions. We'll see you on the pitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.28,0:19:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬鲁伯特 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To Rupert!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.66,0:19:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们 里士满人 同胞们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Friends, Richmonds, countrymen.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.71,0:19:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俱乐部的噩梦结束了 我回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our club's nightmare is over now. I'm back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.92,0:19:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地 泰德拉索太烂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank God. 'Cause Ted Lasso sucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.96,0:19:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-无意冒犯 泰德 -没关系 巴兹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No offense, Ted. -All good, Baz.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.01,0:19:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你、杰里米和保罗在表达感受方面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You, Jeremy, and Paul have been refreshingly candid
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.05,0:19:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是充满激情的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about y'all's feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.39,0:19:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺酷的 英超联赛的教练 竟然知道我们的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pretty cool Premier League gaffer knows our names.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.43,0:19:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 -闭嘴 你们两个笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I know, right? -Shut up, you twats.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.18,0:19:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再试一次 别帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm trying again. No help.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.52,0:19:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 如果她射中了靶子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. So, if she hits the board,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.44,0:19:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望大家都表现出赢了足总杯的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want it to sound like we just won the FA Cup.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.90,0:19:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna leave?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.99,0:20:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让他得逞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna give him the satisfaction.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.28,0:20:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡 我们是时候再次成为朋友了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, Rebecca, it's time to be friends again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.91,0:20:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是我和贝克丝每周都会跟你一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Especially since Bex and I are gonna be sitting with you
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.25,0:20:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在老板坐席上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}every week in that owner's box.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.71,0:20:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会每周都去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not going every week.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.96,0:20:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.50,0:20:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且每周 当他们把摄像机对准我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And every week, when they shove a camera in my face
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.43,0:20:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问我你的现状如何时 我都会告诉他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and ask me how I think you're doing, I will tell them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.14,0:20:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会手下留情的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be relentless.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.10,0:20:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁伯特 你们挺把这些飞镖 当回事的 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, Rupert, y'all take your darts over here pretty seriously, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.06,0:20:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…还有那个你们都玩的撞球游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This and... what's the billiard game y'all do
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.98,0:20:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字像是饼干品牌的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that sounds like a brand of cookies?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.49,0:20:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-斯诺克 -对 就是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Snooker? -That's it. That's the one, yup.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.36,0:20:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 我喜欢披着厚重的毯子 蜷缩在沙发里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, I'd love to curl up on a couch under a weighted blanket,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.87,0:20:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边看《电子情书》 一边大快朵颐“斯诺克”饼干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}watch You've Got Mail and devour a box of Snookers.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.83,0:20:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来试试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See what we got here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.83,0:20:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 中了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey! There it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.63,0:20:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你喜欢飞镖吗 泰德 -还行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Do you like darts, Ted? -They're okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.92,0:21:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更喜欢玩丢沙包\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm more of a, you know, cornhole man myself. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.26,0:21:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来场比赛如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about a game?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.34,0:21:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以赌点什么 比如说一万英镑\NWe could, you know, maybe wager, say, £10,000?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.31,0:21:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如我的医生 在我迷上意大利宽面时告诫我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, as my doctor told me when I got addicted to fettuccine Alfredo,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.73,0:21:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我而言有点过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that's a little rich for my blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.23,0:21:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如这样吧 如果你赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about this? If you win,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.27,0:21:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以让你挑选本赛季 最后两场比赛的上场球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll let you pick the starting lineup of the last two games of the season.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.36,0:21:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我赢了 你不能靠近老板坐席\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if I win, you can't go anywhere near the owner's box,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.49,0:21:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少瑞贝卡还掌权的时候不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}at least not while Rebecca's still in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.12,0:21:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.28,0:21:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.49,0:21:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信有些人会称之为“骑士精神”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I believe some folks call it white knighting,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.25,0:21:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我只是跟着直觉走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I'm just following my gut here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.54,0:21:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事的 -不 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's okay. -No. Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.58,0:21:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你觉得怎么样 -我接受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What do you think? -You're on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.54,0:21:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -开始和结束时都要得分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. -Double in, double out.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.88,0:21:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都按你说的来 鲁鲁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever you say, Rupe-a-dupes. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.80,0:21:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得告诉我输了还是赢了 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just let me know if I'm winning or losing, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.63,0:21:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都忘了我把这个带在了身上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I forgot I had these on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.85,0:21:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Wait a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.39,0:21:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都忘了我是个左撇子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I forgot I'm left-handed.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.44,0:21:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下有意思了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is gonna be a hoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.36,0:22:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们去哪吃晚餐 -是个惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-So where are we going for dinner? -It's a surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.03,0:22:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好哎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有件事要问你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.61,0:22:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天你说你太忙了 没时间给我回短信…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, the other day when you said you were too busy to text me back...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.37,0:22:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 因为我很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, 'cause I was busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.91,0:22:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你从没告诉我你在忙什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you never told me what you were too busy with.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.96,0:22:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为是私事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, 'cause it was private.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.75,0:22:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在跟其他人约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you dating other people?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.34,0:22:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是的话也没关系 但我想知道 我不想当个傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay if you are. It's just that I wanna know so that I don't look stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.34,0:22:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是练瑜伽 好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was yoga, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.13,0:22:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和一群60岁的女人练瑜伽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do yoga with a group of women in their 60s.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.34,0:22:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们不知道我是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They have no idea who I am,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.72,0:22:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一周两节课 能提升我的核心力量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's twice a week and it's really good for my core.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.80,0:22:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常一堂课一小时 但莫琳最近在闹离婚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Normally only takes an hour, but Maureen's been going through a divorce
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.39,0:22:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她需要找人倾诉 发泄出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and she needed to talk about it and blow off some steam.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.39,0:22:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我们去了同志吧 一直待到凌晨两点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We all ended up at G-A-Y till 2:00 a.m.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.35,0:22:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我们和一群扮装皇后 去了巴勒姆区吃可丽饼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then we had crepes in Balham with some drag queens.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.40,0:22:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说了 这是私事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like I said, it's private.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.19,0:22:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在要亲你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna kiss you now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.61,0:22:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非这次又会把你吓跑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unless it's gonna make you run away again.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.03,0:22:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你想慢慢来 我尊重你的决定 但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know that you wanna take this slow and I really do respect that, but it--
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.58,0:22:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我可以摸摸你的屁股 或是你可以摸摸我的…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe I could just touch your arse a little bit or you could touch mine--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.67,0:23:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太没礼貌了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's your manners?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.68,0:23:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该先问过再拍照\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're supposed to ask before you take something.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.51,0:23:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说 我可以拿走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For example, may I take this?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.76,0:23:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不行 -我他妈非要拿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. -Well, I'm fucking taking it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.27,0:23:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着 这是我们第一次约会的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here. It's pictures of our first date.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.35,0:23:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 我做饭给你吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. I'm cooking for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.23,0:23:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,180分 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One hundred and eighty!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.49,0:23:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你 鲁伯特 太棒了 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well in, Rupert. Get in!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.95,0:23:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭上你的臭嘴 不然我给你缝上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut your stupid little twat mouth or I will shut it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.82,0:23:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以给你一份攻守名单呢 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shall I be giving you the lineup card now, Ted?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.41,0:23:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让奥比桑亚防守 那才是他该待的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I shall be putting Obisanya back on defense where he belongs.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.46,0:23:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是这么说的 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's exactly what I said, didn't I?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.50,0:23:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这不全是泰德的错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, now, it's not all Ted's fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.59,0:23:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的前妻把这个乡巴佬弄来这的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My ex-wife's the one who brought the hillbilly to our shores.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.55,0:23:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道她做事向来冲动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know she's always been a bit randy,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.26,0:23:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我没想到她会对整支球队下手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I never thought she would fuck over an entire team.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.22,0:23:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.64,0:23:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿飞镖的时候有点礼貌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Better manners when I'm holding a dart.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.77,0:23:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.85,0:24:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（鲁伯特-傻屌）
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.27,0:24:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅 我怎么才能赢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mae. What do I need to win?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.36,0:24:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个内环120分 再加一次靶心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two triple 20s and a bull's-eye.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.61,0:24:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.78,0:24:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗 鲁伯特我这一辈子都被人低估\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, Rupert, guys have underestimated me my entire life.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.00,0:24:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多年来 我不知道为什么会这样 曾经一度让我十分困扰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And for years, I never understood why. It used to really bother me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.83,0:24:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有一天 我载着儿子去学校\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But then one day, I was driving my little boy to school
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.58,0:24:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见印在墙上的沃特惠特曼的一句名言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I saw this quote by Walt Whitman and it was painted on the wall there.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.17,0:24:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写着“保持好奇心 但不要评判他人”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It said, "Be curious, not judgmental."
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.18,0:24:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这句话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.26,0:24:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我回到车上 开车去公司\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I get back in my car and I'm driving to work,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.68,0:24:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然之间我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and all of a sudden it hits me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.81,0:24:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些曾经看不起我的人 他们当中没有一个人有好奇心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All them fellas that used to belittle me, not a single one of them were curious.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.73,0:24:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们以为自己什么都懂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They thought they had everything all figured out.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.69,0:24:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他们评判一切 评判所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So they judged everything, and they judged everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.36,0:24:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意识到他们低估我这件事…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I realized that their underestimating me...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.87,0:24:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我是谁毫无关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who I was had nothing to do with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.58,0:25:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果他们好奇的话 他们会问问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause if they were curious, they would've asked questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.17,0:25:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.46,0:25:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如 “你经常玩飞镖吗 泰德”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Questions like, "Have you played a lot of darts, Ted?"
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.30,0:25:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我则会回答：“是的 先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To which I would've answered, "Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.22,0:25:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周日下午 我都和爸爸去体育酒吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every Sunday afternoon at a sports bar with my father,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.72,0:25:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我16岁开始 一直到他去世”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from age ten till I was 16, when he passed away."
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.48,0:25:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧烤酱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Barbecue sauce.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.78,0:25:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很精彩的比赛 鲁伯特 -走吧 我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good game, Rupert. -Come on, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.04,0:25:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个很漂亮的安慰奖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are a very lovely consolation prize.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.75,0:25:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡 泰德 好好享受你们的下午时光\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rebecca, Ted, enjoy your evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.67,0:25:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅 一如既往\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mae, as always.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.59,0:25:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊 太他妈爽了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Holy shit, that felt good.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.34,0:25:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有意思 是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was fun. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.22,0:25:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有一件事要做 -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Only one thing left to do now. -What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.01,0:26:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do I have to?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.23,0:26:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝酒我请 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drinks are on me!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.36,0:26:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（AFC里士满）
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.12,0:26:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我可以看你们 做这种欢快的韩国军事训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fellas, I could watch you do this jaunty North Korean military thing
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.91,0:26:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上一整天 但我需要你们帮个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you do all day, but I need a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.83,0:26:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为你两肋插刀 教练 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll die for you, Coach!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.21,0:26:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有点过了 山姆 但我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a little dramatic, Sam, but I see how you got there
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.54,0:26:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想接我那个军事的梗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with me invoking the military and all.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.00,0:26:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now here's what we're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.25,0:26:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们中有谁看过《芝麻街》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many of you fellas ever seen Sesame Street?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.51,0:26:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好 希金斯 -早上好 稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good morning, Higgins. -Good morning. One sec.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.39,0:26:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 挺直了 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's good. Straighten up. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.27,0:26:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 再等一下 就差我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hold on one sec. Let me get in my spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.64,0:26:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Here it comes, here it comes. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.60,0:26:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（嗨 老板 ）
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.03,0:26:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 泰德 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.61,0:26:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听不见 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't hear you!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.49,0:26:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.28,0:27:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah! Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.12,0:27:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们感觉到了 她感觉到了 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We felt it, she felt it!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.78,0:27:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了 耶 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I'm talking about. Yeah! Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.50,0:27:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才起来太快了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got up too fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.21,0:27:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德昨天让鲁伯特丢脸丢到家了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted embarrassed the hell out of Rupert yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.92,0:27:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.92,0:27:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个坏消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bit of bad news.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.01,0:27:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本赛季最后一场比赛 还有一万张票没卖出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have ten thousand unsold seats for the final match of the season.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.09,0:27:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放给游客\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Release them to the visitors.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.64,0:27:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是瑞贝卡 曼城会截走的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But Rebecca, Man City will snap those up.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.93,0:27:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的主场体育馆将会是一片蓝色\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our home stadium will be a sea of sky blue.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.94,0:27:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会气死鲁伯特的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That'll kill Rupert.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.44,0:27:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会损伤我们比赛的士气 我们就在降级的边缘了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll hurt our chances. We're on the brink of relegation.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.36,0:27:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么办吧 希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do it, Higgins.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.74,0:27:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道 去他妈的 \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, you know, fuck off!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.03,0:27:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.28,0:27:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sick of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.79,0:27:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你不断地惩罚鲁伯特 也无法带走你的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't take away your pain by constantly punishing Rupert.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.00,0:27:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当初你找借口跟我吃午饭 好让鲁伯特在我家里偷情的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where were these morals when you were having lunches with me
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.29,0:27:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么没见你这么有道德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so Rupert could have sex in our house?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.21,0:27:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我们是朋友的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought we were friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.63,0:28:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有无数的机会去做正确的事 但你没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You had every opportunity to do the right thing and you never did.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.55,0:28:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的孬种\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fucking pussy.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.72,0:28:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对 我活该内疚一辈子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're right. I deserve to carry that around. I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.02,0:28:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该再勇敢一点 对不起 真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should've been braver, and I'm sorry for that. I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.52,0:28:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想对你说 罢手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'm saying this to you now. Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.32,0:28:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or what?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.74,0:28:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不干了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I quit.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.11,0:28:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道接下来会怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know how this goes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.20,0:28:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会回来 摇尾乞怜 然后我会把工作还给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll come back, grovel for your job, and I'll take you back,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.16,0:28:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我会让你的生活更惨一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I will make your life just that little bit worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.17,0:28:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.09,0:28:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你安排记者偷拍的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You arranged for the photographer to take this.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.97,0:28:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和罗伊在狗仔队的相机存储卡里发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy and I found it on a paparazzi camera card.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.60,0:28:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说是你雇的他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said you hired him.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.52,0:28:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别否认 也别假装你不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't deny it or pretend that you don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.02,0:28:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么你跟泰德坦白 要么我替你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Either you come clean to Ted or I'll do it for you.
