[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.56,0:00:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（麦丝卷）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.40,0:00:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好 教练 -早上好 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Morning, Coach. -Morning, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.90,0:00:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一起吃早饭吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna grab some breakfast?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.15,0:00:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 我刚吃了一块麦片 现在饱着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nah, I just had one piece of cereal and I'm pretty stuffed.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.45,0:00:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过喝杯咖啡倒是可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could go for coffee though.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.28,0:00:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.41,0:00:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道今天感觉像什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what today feels like?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.16,0:00:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-第一天上学 -第一天上学 没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-First day of school. -First day of school. That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.75,0:00:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's close.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.33,0:00:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你呢 教练你有什么感觉 -有点紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What about you, Coach? How you feeling? -A little nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.92,0:00:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 没有谁最后一天紧张的 都是第一天紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, heck, yeah. No such thing as "last-day jitters."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.30,0:00:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得往右看 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gotta look right, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.38,0:00:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天我会适应的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I'm gonna get that someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.51,0:01:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忧郁蓝调\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So blues
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.64,0:01:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听我告诉你 -看看这位老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I can tell you -Check out my man here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.89,0:01:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忧郁蓝调 听我告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So blues, I can tell you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.82,0:01:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩不可能冲破我的防线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A girl's not gettin' by me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.37,0:01:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候反抗男权的最好方式 是踢他们的下体 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sometimes the best way to stick it to the man is go right between his legs, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.21,0:01:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得走了 教练 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-We gotta go, Coach. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（搜索 鲁伯特曼尼恩）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.72,0:01:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敲敲门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Knock-a-doodle-do.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好 拉索教练 -嘿 看看咱俩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good morning, Coach Lasso. -Hey, look at us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.18,0:01:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃虫子上瘾的早鸟 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Couple of worm-addicted early birds, am I right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.98,0:01:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴我堵着你了 我给你带了点礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I'm glad I caught ya. I brought you a little something.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.48,0:01:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 曲奇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Cookies.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.31,0:01:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你们这的人说的“饼干”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or as y'all call 'em here, biscuits, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.69,0:01:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我不建议你泡在肉汁里吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Though, I do not recommend you smother these in gravy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:01:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 我不…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, I don't really--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.90,0:01:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 看一眼嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on now. Take a lookie there.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.20,0:02:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哇 看上去很好吃的样子 -是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Those do look good. -Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.16,0:02:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 吃一块\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go ahead, take a nibble.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.33,0:02:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了 尝尝看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's it. Away you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.87,0:02:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.17,0:02:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从哪弄来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where did you get these?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.67,0:02:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢真是太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm glad you like 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.05,0:02:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧 我每天早上都给你带一些过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? I'll start bringing these to ya every morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.13,0:02:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当是“和老板的饼干时光”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call it "Biscuits with the Boss."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.42,0:02:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这个必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That really isn't necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.51,0:02:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我记下了 这算是我们的第一次分歧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, well, mark this down as the first time we disagree then.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.30,0:02:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 其实是第二次 茶太难喝了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, no, second time. Tea is horrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.89,0:02:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是刷锅水 我不知道你们干嘛跟自己过不去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Absolute garbage water. I don't know why y'all do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.93,0:02:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我们只有彼此了解了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anyhoo, you know, we can't really be good partners
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.06,0:02:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才能成为好搭档 对吗 -泰德…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-unless we get to know each other, right? -Ted--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.02,0:02:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先从简单的开始 非常简单的那种\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna start simple. Real easy, real easy one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.94,0:02:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要分享第一次看的演唱会 和最爱的演唱会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna do first concert, best concert.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.98,0:02:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先说 来吧 回答问题 快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You go ahead and go first. Go. Right off the bat. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.15,0:02:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辣妹组合…第二个问题还是辣妹组合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Spice Girls. And... the Spice Girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.20,0:02:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个问题是同一个答案 我喜欢 该我了 第一次看的演唱会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Same answer for both? I love that. My turn. First concert.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.58,0:02:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 是“赌徒”本人 肯尼罗杰斯老爷子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, come on. It was "The Gambler" himself, Mr. Kenny Rogers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.50,0:02:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 抱歉…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, I'm sorry--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.91,0:02:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.04,0:02:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.88,0:02:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下 泰德 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop. Ted, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.30,0:03:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今早没时间搞什么“和老板的饼干时光”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Biscuits with the Boss" is not something that I have time for this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.80,0:03:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后也没时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.18,0:03:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我明白了 老板 很清楚 -那就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I hear ya, boss. Loud and clear. -There we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.02,0:03:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.27,0:03:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明天还会带着饼干出现 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna show up tomorrow with biscuits, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.19,0:03:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 我不会打这个赌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on now. I would not bet on that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.90,0:03:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你想赢很多钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, unless you wanna win a buttload of money.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.78,0:03:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来击个掌 树\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}High five, tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.98,0:03:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我们第一天在威奇塔州立大学 训练时你对我说过什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Remember what you said to me our first day coaching at Wichita State?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.90,0:03:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别扎马尾辫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lose the ponytail?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.32,0:04:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松 他们只是孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Relax. They're just kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.49,0:04:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙绝对不是孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, these fellas sure as heck ain't kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.78,0:04:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看艾萨克 他就像是穿着钉鞋的罗丹雕塑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, look at Isaac. He looks like a Rodin sculpture in cleats.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.54,0:04:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是“球鞋”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boots.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.87,0:04:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不说钉鞋 说“球鞋”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They call cleats "boots."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.21,0:04:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 我记得你说过 那是汽车后备箱的意思啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you said that the trunk of a car was a boot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.38,0:04:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一词多义\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Also a boot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.71,0:04:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 如果我因为把钉鞋放进后备箱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on now. If I were to get fired from my job
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.01,0:04:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被开除了…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where I'm puttin' cleats in the trunk of my car--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.92,0:04:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你因为把球鞋放进后备箱而被开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got the boot from puttin' boots in the boot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.55,0:04:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.18,0:04:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生们 我们来做一组七对七训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, gentlemen. Let's go ahead and do a little seven on seven.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.14,0:04:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们称这种练习为“驱魔”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna call this drill "The Exorcist"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.39,0:04:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点是要控制“魔怔”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause it's all about controlling possession.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.73,0:04:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.61,0:04:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.41,0:04:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁去买点花 因为这里是山姆去世的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone get some flowers, 'cause this spot here is where Sam died.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.83,0:04:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太令人难过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's very sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.88,0:04:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 走开 你这混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi. Walk away, you little prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.63,0:05:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别激动 老爷爷 别忘了把假发戴上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, granddad. Keep your wig on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.51,0:05:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你 罗伊 -你没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thanks, Roy. -Yeah, you're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.18,0:05:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 山姆 过来一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Sam, come here a sec.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.76,0:05:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.85,0:05:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道地球上最开心的动物是什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what the happiest animal on earth is?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.93,0:05:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是金鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a goldfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.77,0:05:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道为什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.81,0:05:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知道 -因为金鱼只有十秒钟的记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. -Got a ten-second memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.82,0:05:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做条金鱼好吗 山姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be a goldfish, Sam. Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.57,0:05:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂了 去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, you got it. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.91,0:05:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 内特 -谁 叫我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, Nate. -Who, me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.29,0:05:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 在下一个内特到来之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Until we get another Nate here,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.08,0:05:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你把自己当作是“默认”内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need you to assume you're my default Nate, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.54,0:05:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个问题问你 山姆是怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, question for ya. What's the buzz on Sam here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.92,0:05:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看上去闷闷不乐的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Seems a little down in the dumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.26,0:05:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从尼日利亚过来之后 就一直表现不佳 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, he's been underachieving since he got here from Nigeria, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.72,0:05:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次离家从来都不容易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, well, first time away from home is never easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.55,0:05:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得做点什么让他开心起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna have to do something to Ni-cheer-ia him up, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.93,0:05:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得好笑也要尴尬地配合 是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still laughing at stuff you don't think is funny, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.10,0:06:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定什么是玩笑 什么不是玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not always sure what's a joke and what isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.19,0:06:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 这年头很难分辨了 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, it's tough to tell these days, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.11,0:06:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, Lasso! Go, Lasso, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.03,0:06:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, Lasso! Go, Lasso, go! Go, Lasso! Go, Lasso, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.70,0:06:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Higgins.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.99,0:06:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德拉索今早来了我办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted Lasso was in my office.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.20,0:06:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说了一堆 “你看的第一场演唱会是什么”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"What's the first concert you ever saw?"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.04,0:06:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-乔治男孩 -我不是问你 你这个笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Boy George. -Not you, you garden gnome.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.04,0:06:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想每天早上都过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wants us to get together every morning
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.63,0:06:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解我 听听我的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to get to know me and hear what I've got to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.46,0:06:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大的胆子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The nerve!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.59,0:06:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙不屈不挠 人又特别和善\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, the man's just relentless and nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.34,0:06:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管他去到哪 他的球员们都爱他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everywhere he's been, his players seem to love him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.63,0:06:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能会毁掉我们的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the one thing that could just muck this up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.18,0:06:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好啊 小伙子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.89,0:06:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来击个掌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Up top.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.52,0:06:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好 韦尔顿小姐 -你好 韦尔顿小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hello, Miss Welton. -Hello, Miss Welton.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.77,0:06:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯 你知道哪个球员在更衣室里 最有影响力吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Higgins, do you know which of the players has the most sway in the locker room?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.03,0:06:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.07,0:06:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要你有什么用 那帮我解决另一个谜题吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So helpful. Then solve me this different mystery.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.07,0:06:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我查查拉索在哪里买的饼干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find out where Lasso got those biscuits.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心了 饼干们希金斯警探来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Watch out, biscuits! Higgins is on the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.38,0:07:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们 打扰一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, fellas. Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.80,0:07:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都听好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen up!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.30,0:07:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 谢谢 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.92,0:07:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们周六要跟水晶宫队打比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, we got Crystal Palace coming here on Saturday.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.30,0:07:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么是我们需要知道的吗 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything we need to know, Coach?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.55,0:07:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-外侧球员速度很快 -还有什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Lot of speed on the outside. -Okay. Anything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.56,0:07:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速度很快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lot of speed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.14,0:07:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 你们都听到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, you heard the man.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.43,0:07:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们今年早些时候把他们打得很惨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Y'all whipped 'em up pretty good earlier this year,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.77,0:07:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我和教练不会干涉你们的比赛计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so me and Coach ain't gonna mess with the game plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.73,0:07:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.32,0:07:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想调整一下更衣室里的行为准则\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we would like to start fiddling with the way we do things in the locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.19,0:07:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果互联网教会了我们什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if the Internet has taught us anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.32,0:07:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是有时候匿名反而更容易倾吐心声\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's that sometimes it's easier to speak our minds anonymously.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.16,0:07:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗所以我让内特做了一个 老式的意见箱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right? So I asked Nate here to make us a good old-fashioned suggestion box.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.54,0:07:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.20,0:07:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我跟我侄女一起做的 她喜欢手工 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, did it with my niece. She loves crafts, so--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.25,0:07:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的 我也喜欢了解一下你的私人生活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I love glimpses into your personal life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.33,0:07:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.42,0:07:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 如果有人有任何不满或疑问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, if anything's got y'all hot and bothered,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.88,0:07:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就给我们写个纸条塞进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just go ahead and drop us a note.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.09,0:07:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是毛巾的颜色\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You could have issue with the color of the towels
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.97,0:07:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是自动贩卖机的食物 什么问题都能提\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or, heck, the food in the vending machine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.26,0:07:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去不错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sound good?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.35,0:08:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 好极了 明天见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, great. See y'all tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.64,0:08:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在成绩平平 四场比赛输了三场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi. We're middle of the table, we've lost three of four,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.73,0:08:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却关心更衣室里的零食够不够好吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you wanna know if the snacks in the locker room are tasty enough?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.07,0:08:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are they?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.99,0:08:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jesus Christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.28,0:08:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They are not.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.88,0:08:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a long time to wait, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.88,0:08:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尊重你不忙不慌的做事风格\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I respect you didn't hurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.89,0:08:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 第一天正式上班你感觉如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, how was your first official day?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.47,0:08:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not entirely sure
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.56,0:08:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这里的最小计量单位是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what y'all's smallest unit of measurement is over here,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.14,0:08:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的进展基本上就那么多吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but that's about how much headway I made.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.44,0:08:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你看上去丝毫没有气馁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And yet, you seem undeterred.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.78,0:08:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气的出场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Solid entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.20,0:08:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意做哪种动物 狮子还是熊猫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What would you rather be, a lion or a panda?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.82,0:08:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有事先走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have time for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.83,0:09:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.20,0:09:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-泰德 -肯定是熊猫啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ted? -Gotta go panda.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.29,0:09:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你疯了吗熊猫又肥又懒 而且身上的毛一股尿味\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you mad? Pandas are fat and lazy and have piss-stained fur.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.58,0:09:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狮子呢 强大又充满威严 是丛林的霸主\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lions are powerful and majestic and rule the jungle.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.38,0:09:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去跟大象说说看 我可以选大象吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Try telling that to an elephant. Can I be an elephant?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.63,0:09:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狮子或熊猫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lion or panda.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.76,0:09:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-熊猫 -狮子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Panda. -Lion!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.01,0:09:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么东西是黑白红相间的 -不知道 是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What's black and white and red all over? -I don't know. What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.26,0:09:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个靠近狮子全身挂彩的熊猫 必须选狮子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A panda that gets anywhere near a fucking lion. The answer is lion.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.64,0:09:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.89,0:09:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个瑞贝卡是一个非常强势的高个女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That Rebecca is an intimidating, very tall woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.35,0:09:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说 她眼神锁定我的一瞬间 我汗都下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, the minute she locked eyes with me, I started sweating.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.23,0:09:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啦 她这人就是有点情感障碍 你跨过去就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no. She got some fences, all right, but you just gotta hop over 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.73,0:09:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, babe.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.36,0:09:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here. Keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.95,0:09:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 杰米 你愿意做狮子还是熊猫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Jamie, what would you rather be? A lion or a panda?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.37,0:09:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 我就是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, I'm me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.12,0:09:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么想做其他动物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would I wanna be anything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.62,0:09:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你可能自己都没意识到 你的心理有多健康\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure you realize how psychologically healthy that actually is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.71,0:09:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cheers.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.67,0:09:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《午夜法庭》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Night Court.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.92,0:09:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.26,0:09:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是狮子 -绝对是狮子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He's a lion. -Definitely lion.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.97,0:09:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊猫能吃下与自己体重相当的竹子 你知道吗我儿子告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know pandas eat their weight in bamboo? My little boy told me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.72,0:10:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不会吧 -你在说什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No! -What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.35,0:10:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊猫就是有这种本事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pandas are capable of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.89,0:10:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道它们会不会经常这么干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know how often they actually do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.56,0:10:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从尼日利亚过来之后 山姆的成绩日益下滑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sam's down in every stat since Nigeria.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.77,0:10:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许英超联赛超出了他的能力范围\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe the Premiership's too much for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.65,0:10:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他只是需要在这里过得更舒适一点 仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, he just needs to get a little more comfy here, that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.07,0:10:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他周六就20岁了 -正好 生日\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He turns 20 on Saturday. -There we go. A birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.28,0:10:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为他准备点特殊活动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll do something special for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.70,0:10:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让偏离航线的船只回到正轨 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nudge that ship in the right direction, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.03,0:10:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.58,0:10:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看大家都写了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's see what we got here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.87,0:10:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“傻屌”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Wanker."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.66,0:10:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看还有没有别的 “滚开 傻屌”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's see what else we got. "Piss off, wanker."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.25,0:10:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“我希望你被巨无霸汉堡噎死”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"I hope you choke on a Big Mac."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.80,0:10:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-幸好是匿名的 -不 罗伊签了自己的名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good thing these are anonymous. -No, Roy signed that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.38,0:10:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-罗伊 -这个好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Roy. -Here's a good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.47,0:10:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“淋浴水压太低” 记下了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Shower pressure is rubbish." Make a note of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.85,0:10:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“傻屌” 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Wanker." Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.77,0:10:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要大声念出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna say that word out loud.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.85,0:10:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是一个“傻屌”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Another "wanker."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.02,0:10:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能让他们叫你傻屌 泰德 这个词不好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't wanna let them call you a wanker, Ted. It's bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.36,0:10:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's a wanker?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.36,0:10:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是视觉型学习者 谢谢你 我懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm a visual learner, so that's very helpful. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.28,0:11:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My pleasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.49,0:11:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我有个主意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, I got one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.53,0:11:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我跟一只虚张声势的猫一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if I joined forces with a swashbuckling cat
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.41,0:11:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为妓女演奏迷你吉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to play tiny guitars for women of the night
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.29,0:11:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边读亚历克斯哈利最煽情的小说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as we read Alex Haley's most seminal work?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.79,0:11:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要跟穿靴子的猫穿一条裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'd be in cahoots with Puss in Boots,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.55,0:11:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边为妓女演奏音乐一边读《根》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}playing lutes for prostitutes, reading Roots.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.92,0:11:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我想说的是《马尔科姆X自传》 被骗到了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, The Autobiography of Malcolm X. I gotcha.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.42,0:11:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.68,0:11:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了 帮我拿一下啤酒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go. Hey, hold my beer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.47,0:11:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看你的本事 小姑娘 来吧 让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, see what you got, young lady. Come on. What you got? What you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.14,0:11:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑呢吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.48,0:11:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You see that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.39,0:11:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他像大嘴怪一样把你耍得团团转\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She spun you around like the Tasmanian Devil.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.10,0:11:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 没错 只是没有那些讨厌的…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, she did. Except without all that annoying...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.03,0:11:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wrong again.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.62,0:11:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这么一件小事都做不好 希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why is this so hard for you, Higgins?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.79,0:11:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在什么时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What time is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.50,0:11:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“和老板的饼干时光”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's "Biscuits with the Boss" time!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.67,0:11:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有希金斯嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Higgins! Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个人有点多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Three's a crowd.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.13,0:11:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全不介意插在中间 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, that's a crowd I don't mind being smack-dab in the middle of, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.71,0:12:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 老板 看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, boss. Check this out. Pow.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.09,0:12:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们接着昨天的话头继续说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's tie up some loose ends from yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.80,0:12:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一场演唱会 肯尼罗杰斯 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}First concert, Kenny Rogers, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.60,0:12:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最爱的演唱会 1995年野兽男孩在HORDE音乐节上那场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Best concert, we got Beastie Boys at HORDE Fest, 1995.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.81,0:12:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会爱上这个故事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna love this story.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.18,0:12:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 你们这里播了OJ辛普森案了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, did y'all get the O.J. trial over here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.10,0:12:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 拜托 你不能这样随心所欲 跳着华尔兹就进来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, please. I can't just have you waltzing in here whenever you wish.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.52,0:12:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我换成踢踏舞怎么样 类似这种\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if I soft-shoe in, huh? Little something like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.07,0:12:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我可以走太空步进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or I can moonwalk in.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.61,0:12:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然最近的新闻闹得沸沸扬扬 但这个舞步还是很有趣的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Despite recent headlines, it's still a fun dance move to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.36,0:12:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-泰德 -你要从我的角度看待这件事 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ted, Ted. -You gotta see the way I see it, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.16,0:12:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个大楼里的所有人都是团队的一份子 AFC里士满的一份子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everybody in this building, part of the team. Part of AFC Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.78,0:12:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团队要加深感情 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Team's gotta bond. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.33,0:12:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如这样 我和希金斯今天一起吃午饭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, heck, Higgins and I are having lunch today.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.20,0:12:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我办公室正好有沙拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. We're having salads in my office.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.46,0:12:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 一会见了 老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, catch you later, boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.87,0:12:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯 午饭时见 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Higgins, see you at lunch, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.71,0:12:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯撒沙拉一会见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Caesar you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.05,0:12:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.80,0:12:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他令人无法抗拒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's intolerable.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.77,0:12:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 太不顺畅了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy. That is bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.10,0:12:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得找个人来检查下这家伙的前列腺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somebody ought to check this thing's prostate.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.06,0:12:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jeez.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.81,0:12:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.15,0:13:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 山姆 你赶紧去楼上一趟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Sam. You gotta pop upstairs real quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.15,0:13:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯想跟你谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Higgins wants to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.07,0:13:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go. Move it, move it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.95,0:13:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 他走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yep, yep. He's gone, he's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.95,0:13:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把门关上 嘿 伙计们 听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut the door, shut the door. Hey. Yo, hey, guys. Listen up, listen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.62,0:13:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这周六就是山姆的生日了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, Sam's birthday is on Saturday.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.50,0:13:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想着我们可以一起集资 给他个惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I was thinking we'd all chip in and get him something nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.00,0:13:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送他个礼物之类的 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice gift or something. Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.42,0:13:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 内特会带来另一个漂亮的盒子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, Nate's gonna be coming around with yet another impressive box.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.59,0:13:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看 它还有一张脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at this. It's got a face!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.51,0:13:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是他 -抱歉 他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He has a face. -Sorry, it-- He. He.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.05,0:13:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你把钱放进他的嘴里 像这样… -大家听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You put the money in his mouth. -Okay, you hear that, y'all?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.22,0:13:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把钱放进他的嘴里 明白了吗很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You put the money in his mouth. Got it? Okay, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.64,0:13:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go get 'em, Nate.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.56,0:13:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗帮帮他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay? Help him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.64,0:13:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢 科林\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Lovely. Thanks, Colin.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.48,0:13:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把钱放进他嘴里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You put the money in his mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.90,0:13:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你吃口香糖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yummy for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.28,0:13:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是薄荷味的 让钱的味道更清新\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's spearmint. Make the money smell nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.37,0:13:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 杰米 你真贴心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Jamie. That's incredibly thoughtful.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.25,0:13:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 杰米 耽误你一点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Jamie. Real quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.04,0:14:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是想跟你聊聊 你刚才把口香糖放进盒子里了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just wanna have a chat. Did you put gum in the box there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.46,0:14:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -你为什么要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. Yeah. -Now, why'd you go and do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.46,0:14:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抱歉 教练 -内特只是想帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sorry, Coach. -Nate's just trying to help us out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.63,0:14:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他也是团队的一份子 对吗 -是的 教练 你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He's part of the team, right? -Yeah, right, Coach. Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.22,0:14:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把这个球队看作是乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I see this team like a band.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.97,0:14:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很喜欢 -如果我们是滚石乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I love that. -And if we were the Rolling Stones,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.39,0:14:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就是米克杰格 因为我是头面人物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd be Mick Jagger, 'cause I'm the front man.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.93,0:14:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -我有很多招式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sure. -I got the moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.23,0:14:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的腰很细 是的 长相帅气 我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got a tiny waist, yeah. The whole bit. I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.31,0:14:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而罗伊则是基思理查兹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Roy would be Keith Richards,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.77,0:14:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他很老 所有人都很意外他竟然还没死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause he's old and everyone's surprised he ain't dead yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.15,0:14:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the fuck are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.65,0:14:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊 兄弟 如果你要冲澡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy, mate, if you're gonna go to the shower,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.40,0:14:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该先把毛衣脱掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you should take your sweater off first, pal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.87,0:14:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑呢 老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just taking the piss, mate. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.12,0:14:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会态度好点的 我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be better. Promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.96,0:14:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴听到你这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Glad to hear it. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.93,0:14:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马库斯 你有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marcus, what you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.22,0:14:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对本周末和水晶宫队打比赛 有什么感想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How are you feeling about taking on Crystal Palace this weekend?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.72,0:14:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要我说的话 用水晶做的宫殿似乎不堪一击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A palace made out of crystal seems mighty fragile if you ask me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.85,0:14:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-教练 -教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Coach. -Coach!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.31,0:15:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那位朋友 -特伦特克里姆 独立报的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah, right there. -Trent Crimm, The Independent.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.48,0:15:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得你 特伦特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I remember, Trent.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.11,0:15:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是好奇 你能解释一下越位犯规吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just curious. Could you explain the offside rule?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.57,0:15:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特伦特 参照1964年时美国最高发院\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Trent, I'm gonna put it the same way the US Supreme Court did
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.16,0:15:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对色情的判定标准\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}back in 1964 when they defined pornography.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.33,0:15:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要解释清楚不容易 但你见到了自然知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It ain't easy to explain, but you know it when you see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.25,0:15:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 这位先生 -《太阳报》的厄尼朗兹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah, this gentleman right here. -Ernie Lounds, The Sun.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.71,0:15:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.00,0:15:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个问题是给曼尼恩女士的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This question's for Ms. Mannion.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.00,0:15:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你叫我“韦尔顿”就好 -当然 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's "Welton." -Of course. My apologies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.30,0:15:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您对鲁伯特的新欢有什么看法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any thoughts on the newest Rupert girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.38,0:15:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和鲁伯特已经分开了 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Rupert and I are no longer together, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.26,0:15:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想跟演员还是模特交往 都是他的自由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He may consort with whatever model-actress, actress-model he pleases.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.60,0:15:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 鲁伯特目前的交往对象是另一个女孩 据说你们还没分手时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, the girl who came forward today is another one who was with Rupert
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.10,0:15:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就在一起了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}while you were married.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.23,0:15:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说他们是五年前开始的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, she says it started five years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.78,0:15:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的关系一直持续到…现在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And they kept it going until, well, still.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.95,0:15:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.74,0:16:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还一直以为男人不能一心多用呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And all this time I thought men couldn't multitask.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.29,0:16:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的提问环节到此为止了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid that's all we have time for.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.08,0:16:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢大家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.54,0:16:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.51,0:16:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（又一个）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.51,0:16:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（鲁伯特曼尼恩被拍到 与另一个嫩模出现在彻西区）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.76,0:16:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.85,0:16:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是想来看看你是否一切都好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just wanna make sure you're doing okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.97,0:16:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些记者真的很伤人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, that was pretty rough back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.64,0:16:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没指望他们好到哪去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I expect nothing less from the press.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.89,0:16:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.77,0:16:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你需要有人邮寄那个包裹吗 我是不会干这种事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, did you need somebody to post that? Because that person's not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.40,0:16:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 拜托 这是我儿子寄来的爱心包裹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, come on. This is a care package from my little boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.57,0:16:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这里面有什么东西 能让你开心起来 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe something in here can help cheer you up, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.41,0:16:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个营的迷你士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got a small battalion of army men.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.45,0:16:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这卡片上说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Says here on the card that
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.83,0:16:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该把他们部署在我的公寓 保证我的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm supposed to set 'em up in my apartment to help keep me safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.29,0:16:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-自制的卡祖笛 -好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Homemade kazoo. -Excellent.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.96,0:16:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个 所以不能给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only got one of those though, so you can't have that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.55,0:16:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.80,0:16:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at that right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.88,0:16:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是堪萨斯城最好吃的烧烤酱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, this right here is some of the best barbecue sauce in Kansas City,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.85,0:17:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可以说是全世界最好吃的烧烤酱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which makes it some of the best barbecue sauce in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.77,0:17:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.85,0:17:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有什么食物让你感觉回家了一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got some kind of food or something that can teleport you back home,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.69,0:17:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你觉得心里一暖 心情愉悦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}make you feel warm and fuzzy?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.19,0:17:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.74,0:17:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还有事吗 泰德 -有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Will that be all, Ted? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.41,0:17:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 我来找你是因为我遇到了一点麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, actually, the whole reason I'm here is 'cause I'm having a little trouble
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.12,0:17:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该怎么跟杰米塔特沟通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}figuring out Jamie Tartt's operating instructions,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.37,0:17:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你有没有什么建议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I was just seeing if you happened to have any advice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.04,0:17:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我恐怕…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, I'm afraid--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.38,0:17:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的眼睛亮了 你想到了什么对吗 说说看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your eyes just lit up. You got an idea. What is it? Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.80,0:17:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才想说你应该去找基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just gonna say you should go and talk to Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.01,0:17:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩显然关系不错 如果有谁了解杰米的话 那肯定是她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, you two have an obvious rapport. If anyone knows Jamie, it's her.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.43,0:17:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 老板就是不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See, that's why you're the boss, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.68,0:17:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好建议 我想好给你什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's good. Hey, tell you what I'm gonna do though.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.97,0:17:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你一个讨厌鬼 我看看 给你挑一个好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna give you one of these stinkers. Let's see. Let's get you a good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.14,0:17:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 这家伙是你的第一道防线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, this right here is gonna be your first line of defense,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.14,0:17:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防那个混蛋厄尼朗兹再来找事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in case that little turkey Ernie Lounds comes back around, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.94,0:17:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样冲着门口瞄准\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about that? We'll aim him right at the door there for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.11,0:17:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢了 老板 谢谢你的建议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, thanks, boss. I appreciate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.95,0:18:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的你看上去很美 摸一摸狮子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes! You look beautiful. Just pet the lion.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.74,0:18:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Exactly!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.50,0:18:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢 再给我一声咆哮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love it. Give me a growl, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.33,0:18:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很性感 很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sexy, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.88,0:18:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 很美 很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Beautiful. Yeah, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.42,0:18:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备下一组拍摄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's set up for the next shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.96,0:18:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨 -嘿 你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hi. -Hey, how you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.72,0:18:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好 你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm all right. How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.34,0:18:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的 不赖 所以你选了狮子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, not bad. So, you went with the lion, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.93,0:18:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对 -我有点受伤 但是挺酷的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -I'm a little hurt, but it looks cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.51,0:18:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这身太夸张了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I look insane.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.89,0:18:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我觉得比熊猫的装扮好看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I do think it's a better look than the panda.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.40,0:18:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.86,0:18:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死 我好饿 -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fuck, I'm famished. -Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.23,0:18:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分狮子都很饿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Most lions are.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.82,0:18:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这样吧 我们去吃点东西 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Look. Let's get some food. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.40,0:18:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你饿吗 -嗯 是免费的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You hungry? -Yeah, is it free?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.66,0:18:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份工作肯定很有趣吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gotta be pretty fun for you, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.16,0:18:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 他们付我很多钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I'm getting paid a shit ton
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.41,0:18:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扮成动物 卖有咖啡因的伏特加\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to get dressed up like an animal and sell caffeinated vodka.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.95,0:18:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这个狮爪子美甲我能带回家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I do get to go home with the paws.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.66,0:18:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算是福利了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, there's the perks right there. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.79,0:18:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能咬一口吗 -可以 来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Can I have a bite? -Yeah. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.04,0:18:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -小心 不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you. -Careful. You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.00,0:18:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你突然出现不是为了给我喂饭的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know that you didn't just pop down to feed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.59,0:18:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对 我想问问你关于杰米的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, you're right. I wanted to ask you about Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.59,0:19:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.05,0:19:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得什么能激励他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What would you say motivates him?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.77,0:19:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹箫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Blow jobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.27,0:19:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有别的选项吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there a second option?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.36,0:19:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我咬一口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on, give us another bite.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.82,0:19:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 一大口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.82,0:19:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我知道这孩子会是明日之星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, look, I know the kid's gonna be a star.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.78,0:19:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望他能对我正在为之努力的团队建设\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was kinda hoping he'd, you know, warm up
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.16,0:19:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热情一些 仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the team building I'm trying to do here. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.74,0:19:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 他这人吃软不吃硬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, he responds well to positive reinforcement.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.70,0:19:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这个我擅长啊 -那你稳了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That's my wheelhouse. -There you go, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.58,0:19:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 咬一口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Bite.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.46,0:19:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再让我咬一口 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Go on, give us one more bite. -Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.17,0:19:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.17,0:19:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-超大一口 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That was a big one. -Well, yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.38,0:19:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘴角沾了番茄酱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got some ketchup there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.76,0:19:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去就像刚吃了一只羚羊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks like you devoured an antelope.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.59,0:19:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-帮我弄一下 -小心 别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Help me. -Just be careful. Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.97,0:19:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见了 好多啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I feel that. There's a lot of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.56,0:19:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 确实很多 我正在…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, it's a lot and I'm just--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.47,0:19:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond! Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.56,0:19:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过一会 水晶宫队就要面对AFC里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are moments away from Crystal Palace facing AFC Richmond
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.40,0:19:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他们新的球队经理 泰德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and their new manager, Ted Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.65,0:19:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在球场上 所有的眼睛都会盯着 足球新秀杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}While on the pitch, all eyes will surely be on young phenom, Jamie Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.57,0:20:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们 该上场了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, fellas, here we go. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.86,0:20:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 有什么最后忠告吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, you got any last words?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.41,0:20:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-外侧球员速度要快 -外侧球员速度要快 你们听到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Speed on the outside. -Speed on the outside. You heard the man.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.49,0:20:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说的就这么多 还有最后一句\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's all we got for you, except for one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.54,0:20:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐 山姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that's Happy Birthday, Sam!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.42,0:20:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴巴通德永远是最棒的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Babatunde's the best.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.60,0:20:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -嘿 请享用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey. -Hey, enjoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.47,0:20:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们给我买了亲亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, man, you guys got me Chin Chin.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.47,0:20:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 这是陪伴我长大的牌子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow, this is all I used to eat growing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.94,0:20:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道你很久没回家了 所以我们想把家带到你面前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We know you haven't been home in a while, so we thought we'd bring some home to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.02,0:20:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You guys, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.83,0:20:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 生日快乐 山姆 -谢谢你 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey. Happy Birthday, Sam. -Thank you, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.37,0:20:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给你准备了一些礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got a few things in there for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.25,0:20:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, what's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.46,0:20:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子给了我很多士兵小人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, my little boy gave me a whole bunch of these.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.46,0:21:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我出门在外的时候保护我的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, help keep me safe while I'm away.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.72,0:21:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想念他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I miss him, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.68,0:21:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸总是捏我的耳垂 他认为这样会给我好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My dad used to-- always used to pinch my earlobes for good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.97,0:21:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是受不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me a fucking break.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.52,0:21:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.94,0:21:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 我不收下可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, is it okay if I don't keep this?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.27,0:21:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有你对美国军队的那种热爱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't really have the same fondness for the American military that you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.90,0:21:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-帝国主义 是的 -帝国主义\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Imperialism. Right. Yeah. -Imperialism.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.78,0:21:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 教练 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Coach. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.49,0:21:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.49,0:21:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去让水晶宫队看看 这到底是谁的地盘 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get out there and show Crystal Palace whose house this is, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.46,0:21:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西部和南部再次相遇了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}West meets South again.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.79,0:21:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是伦敦的德比赛现场 气氛极其紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Derby Day in London, and the atmosphere is electric.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.25,0:21:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会换了新主人 球员席换了新经理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With a new owner in the boardroom and a new manager in the dugout,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.42,0:21:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常年的弱队AFC里士满是否会赢来曙光\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}will it be a new dawn for the perennial underdog, AFC Richmond?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.89,0:21:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到本地人所说的“赛狗场”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Welcome to what the home fans call the "Dogtrack."
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.81,0:21:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是尼尔森路体育馆 本场比赛是AFC里士满队对阵水晶宫队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Nelson Road Stadium, for AFC Richmond against Crystal Palace.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.44,0:21:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是阿尔洛怀特 这位是克里斯鲍威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm Arlo White and this is Chris Powell.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.36,0:22:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴来到这里 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And it's great to be here, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.65,0:22:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你准备好了吗 -你前门开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You ready? -Your fly is down.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.99,0:22:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.70,0:22:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, shall we?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.66,0:22:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯 你有在美国球队经理 手下踢过球吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chris, did you ever play under an American manager?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.82,0:22:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有 阿尔洛 我不介意 我会说他们的语言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Never did, Arlo. Wouldn't have minded it. I do speak the language.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.83,0:22:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker! Wanker! Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.76,0:22:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于电视机前的球迷朋友们 我们为这粗俗的语言向大家道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To the fans at home, we do apologize for the fruity language.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.38,0:22:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker! Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.72,0:22:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新老板瑞贝卡韦尔顿 这一聘请决定风险很高\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a risky hire by new owner, Rebecca Welton.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.39,0:22:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是不是知道什么我们不知道的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does she know something we don't?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.73,0:22:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker! Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.14,0:22:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂给他一个机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi! Give him a chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.77,0:22:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.15,0:22:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有90分钟证明他们错了 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got 90 minutes to prove 'em wrong, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.78,0:22:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来试试吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's give it a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.86,0:22:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.41,0:22:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（全场比赛 AFC里士满 1-水晶宫FC 4）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.99,0:22:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不出所料\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And there you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.28,0:22:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对泰德拉索时代而言 这是一个不详的开端\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's an inauspicious start to the Ted Lasso era.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.66,0:23:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满队看上去一盘散沙 毫无斗志 而且一点不开心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond looked disjointed, uninspired, and, you have to say, joyless.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.84,0:23:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水晶宫4比1打败了里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Palace win and Richmond lose 4-1.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.51,0:23:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的亮点是山姆奥比桑亚精彩的防守\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only bright spot being the defensive play of Sam Obisanya.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.97,0:23:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的亮点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only bright spot?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.68,0:23:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我 就是4比0了 你们这些老混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Without me, it would've been 4-0, you miserable old pricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.89,0:23:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及杰米塔特在伤停补时的 一个于事无补的进球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And a meaningless consolation goal for Jamie Tartt in injury time.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.93,0:23:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.35,0:23:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 过来一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie. Real quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.06,0:23:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Regarding Jamie Tartt,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.61,0:23:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位从曼城借来的球员 踢进了毫无意义的一球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it was an insignificant goal by the Manchester City loanee,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.69,0:23:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他却高兴地仿佛赢了世界杯一般\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but he celebrated like he'd just won the World Cup.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.41,0:23:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识你不久 但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I haven't known you that long, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.41,0:23:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话 你是我训练过的最好的运动员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can honestly say you are the best athlete I have ever coached.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.37,0:23:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.54,0:23:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我很努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I mean, I work hard, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.88,0:23:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.50,0:23:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在球场上的表现非常好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are truly great at everything you do out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.97,0:23:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except for one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.26,0:23:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用左脚传球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My left foot cross?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.43,0:23:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 杰米 我想你也许过于确信 你是百里挑一的球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Jamie, I think that you might be so sure that you're one in a million,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.47,0:23:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时你忘记了在球场上 你只是11个人当中的一员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that sometimes you forget that out there, you're just one of eleven.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.85,0:24:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能想办法摒弃个人主义…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you just figure out some way to turn that "me" into "us"...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.73,0:24:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会前途无限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the sky's the limit for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.70,0:24:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说一句 那个进球很精彩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Was a heck of a goal out there, by the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.41,0:24:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.66,0:24:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满滑落到第13名的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond fall to 13th place.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.21,0:24:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信他们不会在这个名次上停留太久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure they won't be there very long.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.04,0:24:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看好吗 克里斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that optimism, Chris?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.54,0:24:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我今天喷了CK的激情香水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Actually, I'm wearing Obsession by Calvin Klein.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.05,0:24:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈丢人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was fucking embarrassing!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.18,0:24:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也同样气愤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am equally livid.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.97,0:24:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊 兄弟 -老天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Blimey, mate. -Jesus Christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.14,0:24:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.68,0:24:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没想到他还有这两下子 -干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Didn't know he had it in him. -Good lad.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.23,0:24:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.45,0:24:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, come on now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.07,0:24:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再纠结于这次失败了 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, let's shake this one off, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.74,0:24:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始变得更好 在那之前…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Start getting better on Monday. Until then--
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.16,0:25:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 DJ彼尔德 帮忙调解下气氛好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, DJ Beard-o, why don't you help pick up the mood in here, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.96,0:25:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五尺矮个和Q-Tip来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Little Phife Dawg and Q-Tip comin' at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.21,0:25:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 大家都来吃蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on now. Everybody get some cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.34,0:25:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是山姆的生日 来吧 给身体注入点糖分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, it's Sam's birthday. Go ahead, get some sugar in your system.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.26,0:25:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on now.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.97,0:25:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（当你第一次看见球）
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.68,0:25:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（傻吊）
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.76,0:25:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（#开除拉索）
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.52,0:25:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, y'all.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.10,0:25:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你们带了点甜食来缓解失败的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I come bearing sweet treats to numb the sting of defeat.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.07,0:25:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拿着 -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.69,0:25:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你们知道 我们可以比今天打得更好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And hey, just so you know, we can play a lot better than we showed today.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.24,0:25:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们下楼来加入大家 这对球队而言一定意义重大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know it would mean a lot to the guys if y'all just came down, joined in.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.58,0:25:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们知道你们还在背后支持着他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let 'em know you're still in their corner.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.87,0:25:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会强求的 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's all the arm twisting I'm gonna do though, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.00,0:25:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 你知道怎样能说服我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, you know what might convince me?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.42,0:25:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你告诉我这么美味的饼干是在哪买的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you told me where you got these delicious biscuits.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.76,0:25:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我说了 周一我就没机会给你带饼干了 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, if I did that, I wouldn't be able to bring you more on Monday, would I?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.77,0:26:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我在楼下等着你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Hope to see y'all downstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.73,0:26:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这蛋糕真好吃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's good cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.31,0:26:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米我是《独立报》的特伦特克里姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie! Trent Crimm, The Independent.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.48,0:26:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你们输得正常啊 你现在感受如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was quite a beating today. How you taking the loss?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.28,0:26:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 不是我一个人的事 我们是一个团队 我只是11个人当中的一员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, it's not just me though, is it? We're a team. I'm just one of eleven.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.33,0:26:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就像从小孩手里夺糖一样简单 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Candy from a baby. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.83,0:26:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们踢得太烂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were rubbish.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.50,0:26:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他的 没错 我非常不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck it. Yeah, I am taking it pretty hard, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.50,0:26:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的那些人 他们都在里面吃蛋糕呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The rest of them, they're all in there eating cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.96,0:26:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗 -真的 老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Seriously? -Yeah, seriously, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.22,0:26:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新教练放了音乐 就像一个派对 真是荒谬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The new gaffer's got music on in there. It's like a party. It's a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.87,0:27:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心 孩子 教练修好了水压\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Careful, son. The gaffer's fixed the water pressure.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.08,0:27:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌失败\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hate losing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.66,0:27:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来 要有信心 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bird by bird, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.21,0:27:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-晚安 教练 -晚安 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good night, Coach. -Night, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.88,0:27:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看谁来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here's trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.88,0:27:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看了比赛 -是吗你怎么看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I saw the match. -Yeah? What'd you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.09,0:27:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太烂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were rubbish.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.09,0:27:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 也许吧 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah, maybe so. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.05,0:27:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一件事需要你的建议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did wanna get your advice on one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.97,0:27:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么看…被你偷袭了接住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you think-- Look at that! Got ya!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.56,0:27:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗好吧 我低估你了 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah? All right, I underestimated you. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.64,0:27:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 没人能判断我的进攻 来吧 让我看看你的本事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See, no one sees me coming. Come on, what you got? What you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.27,0:27:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快 好吧 我要把背包放下了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was quick. Okay, I'm gonna take my backpack off now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.69,0:27:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要动真格的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna really do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.86,0:27:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我先抻抻腿 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Let me stretch here a little bit. -All right. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.11,0:27:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 好的 现在你有麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go. Okay. All right, now you're in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.45,0:27:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调整呼吸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get your breath back.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.96,0:27:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.22,0:27:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚给你发了照片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just sent you the pictures.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.05,0:28:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是我想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's exactly what I wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.85,0:28:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明星球员的女朋友和新任球队经理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The star player's girlfriend and the new manager.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.48,0:28:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定要这么干吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you sure you want to do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.15,0:28:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媒体会把他们生吞活剥的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The press will eat them alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.08,0:28:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韦尔顿小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miss Welton?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.58,0:28:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（突发绯闻 鲁伯特曼尼恩的新欢旧爱）
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.08,0:28:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do it.
