Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.50,0:00:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会听到主场球迷对AFC里士满 不间断的嘘声\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're hearing AFC Richmond being booed lustily by their home fans,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.26,0:00:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不说 这不是没有理由的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you have to say, not without good reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.97,0:00:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2比0 我们可以做得更好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}2-0. We're better than that!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.68,0:00:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 对不起 我没能给你那个 你想要的传球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie. Jamie. Sorry, I didn't put that cross where you wanted it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.10,0:00:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别放在心上 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Forget it, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.18,0:00:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 如果我给你一点 能帮你提升球技的建议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, would it be too forward if I gave you some advice
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.77,0:00:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会太直白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that might help improve your game a bit?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.81,0:00:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会 请说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Please, anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.90,0:00:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该去找个时间机器 回到你妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you need to do is get yourself a time machine, and go back to the moment
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.36,0:00:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即将跟一个毫无运动天赋的可悲小男人 上床的那一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when your mom was about to fuck a sad little man with no athletic talent.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.57,0:00:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她拉起来 让她坐飞机去阿根廷 丢到马拉多纳的老二上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pull her off him, fly her to Argentina, and drop her onto Maradona's cock.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.12,0:00:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望对你有用 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hope that helps, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.25,0:00:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, that's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.21,0:00:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受够了你侮辱所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm done with you being a prick to everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.42,0:00:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么我干倒你这老家伙 要么我被你这老家伙干倒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, either I beat up an old man, or I let an old man beat me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.55,0:00:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他的 动手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck it. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.01,0:00:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fucking--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.18,0:01:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, hey, hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.64,0:01:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静 都给我冷静\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Easy, easy, easy now!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.35,0:01:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 告诉他们搏击俱乐部的 首要准则是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, tell these boys what the first rule of my fight club is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.44,0:01:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-禁止搏击 -禁止搏击 好吗听懂了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No fight club! -No fight club. Okay? You understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.02,0:01:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看在手枪皮特的份上 各位 我们还要打下半场呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the love of Pistol Pete, y'all. We still got a second half to play.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.28,0:01:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坐 所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, please, sit down. Everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.57,0:01:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练救了你 老家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gaffer saved you, old man.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.20,0:01:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再敢说一次我老…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call me old...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.87,0:01:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你试试看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.05,0:01:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.67,0:01:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爷爷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}granddad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.97,0:01:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈弄死你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll fucking kill you!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.87,0:02:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4号桌排好了 从此刻开始就叫“无聊桌”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Table four is done and shall from now on be known as the boring table.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.96,0:02:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我坐那一桌啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But that's where I'm sitting.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.67,0:02:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没给伊莱恩肯纳安置好 讨厌的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I haven't placed Elaine Kenner. Awful woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.84,0:02:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她今晚不会出席 她的脸被自家的马踢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She won't be attending tonight. She was kicked in the face by her horse.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.34,0:02:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小可怜 马没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That poor thing. Is the horse okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.35,0:02:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去这支球队还是分裂的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks like we still got ourselves a team divided here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.52,0:02:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你知道我现在想什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, you know what I'm thinkin' about right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.35,0:02:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-《西区故事》 -你懂我 鲨鱼帮和火箭帮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-West Side Story? -You know it. Sharks and Jets.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.81,0:02:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这些家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think these fellas
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.90,0:02:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在体育馆跳跳舞就能化解矛盾了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}could solve their problems with a dance-off at a gymnasium?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.78,0:02:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 如果我没记错的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Course, if memory serves,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.49,0:02:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里弗和贝纳多当场被刺身亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Riff and Bernardo ended up getting knifed to death at that particular event.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.11,0:02:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 他们是在后面打架时死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, they didn't die until the rumble afterwards.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.41,0:02:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Right, right, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.58,0:02:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我15岁的时候 做过安妮塔的候补演员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I was 15, I was understudy for Anita.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.66,0:02:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我读的男校\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All-boys school.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.00,0:02:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又剥开了内森洋葱的一层外衣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have peeled yet another juicy layer of the Nathan onion.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.13,0:02:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼尔德教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach Beard!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.46,0:02:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的晚宴 是鸡肉和牛排二选一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For dinner tonight, it's either chicken or steak!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.88,0:03:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能选两种\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't tick both!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.84,0:03:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.05,0:03:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,败露了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Busted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.55,0:03:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Ted!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.01,0:03:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在 -我想知道你的携伴是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah! -I need to know who your plus-one is!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.39,0:03:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这位“两道主菜”先生\NWell, that'd be Mr. Two Entrées here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.27,0:03:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 他已经带了另一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, he's already bringing a date!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.07,0:03:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你今晚有空吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, you free tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.70,0:03:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有啊 我每天晚上都有空 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm free every night, yeah. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.99,0:03:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要带内森 -谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm gonna bring Nathan! -Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.49,0:03:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伟大的内森他就是我的伴儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nate the Great! He's gonna be my date!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.70,0:03:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且因为一些显而易见的原因 我们想坐8号桌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And for obvious reasons, we'd love to be at table eight!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.29,0:03:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.87,0:03:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼尔德 你吃鸡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Beard, you're having chicken!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.50,0:03:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.59,0:03:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周五睡衣日我要是早点知道就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pajama Friday? Wish I woulda known.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.72,0:03:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你讲个故事 你听完肯定很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna get a kick outta this story.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.72,0:03:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我17岁的时候… -泰德 我打断你一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-When I was 17-- -Ted, let me just stop you there
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.01,0:03:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你就要跟我讲你和睡衣的土味趣闻了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before you tell me a folksy anecdote about you and pajamas.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.47,0:03:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 你要是改变主意了 告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. When you change your mind, just let me know,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.39,0:03:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这是个好故事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause this one is a doozy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.77,0:03:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你找我有事吗我现在真的…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, was there anything you needed? 'Cause I'm really--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.94,0:03:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我、罗伊和杰米今晚能坐一张桌子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was wondering if me, Roy and Jamie could all sit at the same table tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.07,0:03:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可以吗 -可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Is that possible? -Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.15,0:04:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了因为我得让俩人冰释前嫌 我觉得应该可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great! 'Cause I got some fences I need to mend, and I think that might do the trick.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.03,0:04:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-泰德 我刚同意了 -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ted, I just said yes. -Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.78,0:04:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 这件真美 但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God, that one's absolutely beautiful, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.45,0:04:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得我已经驾驭不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think I can get away with that anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.45,0:04:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然可以 时尚的核心是自信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure you could. Fashion's all about confidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.46,0:04:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不自信 我是绝不会 穿睡衣参加毕业舞会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I didn't have any confidence, I never would've worn pajamas to my prom
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.50,0:04:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后一整晚都待在监狱里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and ended up in jail the rest of that night.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.96,0:04:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不想听那个故事 所以我不讲了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you don't wanna hear that story, so I ain't gonna tell it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.92,0:04:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗我不烦你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? I'll get outta your hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.25,0:04:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定为这次盛大的舞会 感到紧张吧 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're probably all revved up because of the big shindig, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.88,0:04:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我好得很\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no. I'm absolutely fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.38,0:04:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然过去是我和鲁伯特一起举办宴会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, even when Rupert and I were running the gala together,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.22,0:04:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但大部分工作都是我做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did most of the work myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.14,0:04:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我一点不紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I'm not revved up at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.68,0:04:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 我现在情绪很平稳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm actually, really, feeling quite mellow.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.64,0:04:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好 我们遇到了一个大问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good afternoon. We have a huge problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.94,0:04:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘉宾歌手罗比威廉姆斯不来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our musical guest, Robbie Williams, has canceled.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.90,0:04:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}God!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.98,0:04:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 他是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no. Who is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.19,0:04:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定 没关系 这都不是事 让我好好想想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no. That's absolutely fine. It's not a problem. Let me just think.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.03,0:04:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我们这么办 希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, here's what we're going to do, Higgins.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.28,0:04:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚 我会告诉大家罗比取消了演出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tonight, when I tell everyone that Robbie has canceled,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.45,0:04:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没关系 因为你会找到更好的替代\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by then it won't matter because you will have found someone better.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.46,0:04:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-靠你了 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-There ya are. -Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.25,0:05:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是世界级的解决问题达人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am a world-class problem solver.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.17,0:05:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 你能接得住 加油很好 看看呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There it is. You got it. Catch it! Yep! Look at that!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.55,0:05:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以的 希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got this, Higgins!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.22,0:05:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡感谢你的辛勤付出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Rebecca's grateful for all your hard work!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.26,0:05:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Ted!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.98,0:05:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我讨厌这条领带 宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I hate it, babe.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.56,0:05:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我的风格 没有兜帽 没有拉链\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just not me. There's no hood, no zips.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.86,0:05:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有涂鸦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no graffiti.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.40,0:05:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有涂鸦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No graffiti.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.07,0:05:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯了 我看上去像个银行家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mad. I look like a banker.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.12,0:05:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裤裆那么紧 才不像呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not with trousers that tight around the crotch, you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.66,0:05:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我看上去像一个屌很大的银行家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. I look like a banker with a great cock.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.37,0:05:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝 如果这种人存在的话 我们就不会在一起了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Babe, if those existed, we wouldn't be together.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.42,0:05:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便啦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.84,0:05:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.92,0:05:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你涉足时尚业 会得到更多的赞助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, you're gonna get more endorsements when you start embracing high fashion.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.80,0:05:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是帮你打造品牌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just trying to help build up your brand.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.68,0:05:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 别这样 你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie, no. What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.47,0:05:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在做…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm doing...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.85,0:05:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风格\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}style.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.77,0:05:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 人们并不知道 其实我对时尚很在行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, people don't know it, but I'm good at this fashion shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.23,0:05:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗 -对 时尚血统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Are you? -Yeah, I'm like a progeny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.98,0:06:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.82,0:06:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 蹲下 狗狗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi. Down, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.49,0:06:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖狗狗 去找好吃的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a good boy. Find the treat, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.82,0:06:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, hon.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.24,0:06:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死 是语音信箱 你发的消息我收到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shoot, I was hoping I'd catch ya. Got your message.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.45,0:06:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来咱俩玩上了电话鬼抓人游戏 现在你是“鬼”了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Playing a little phone tag, it appears. And you are now it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.33,0:06:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你猜怎么着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. Guess what.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.79,0:06:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我穿着你让我带的西装\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm wearing the suit you told me I should bring.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.04,0:06:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是对的 一如既往\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were right, as always.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.17,0:06:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 就这些 我爱…我想你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Okay, so, that's it. I love-- I miss ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.59,0:06:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你替我给小家伙一个拥抱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And just go ahead and give the little guy a squeeze for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.22,0:06:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之后再聊 再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.77,0:06:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 真好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. All right, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.48,0:06:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢吟游诗人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gotta love a troubadour.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.23,0:06:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.98,0:06:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妈呀 看看你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Holy moly, look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.02,0:06:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-希望我没来太早 -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hope I'm not too early. -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.57,0:06:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者太晚 我希望尽量卡在中间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or too late. I was trying to go for somewhere in between.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.44,0:06:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不晚 你时间把握得刚刚好 内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, no. You threaded that needle perfectly, Nate.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.36,0:06:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了 -是的 好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good. -Yeah, nailed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.11,0:06:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, let me ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.87,0:06:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是那种会希望朋友直接指出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you one of those guys that likes it if your friends tell you
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.29,0:06:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你牙缝里有食物的人吗 -当然了 是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-you got a piece of food in your teeth? -Absolutely, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.29,0:07:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 你的西装太不合身了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, good. 'Cause that suit does not fit at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.12,0:07:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗 -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Really? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.04,0:07:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来想买一套新的 但是太贵了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was gonna buy one, but, you know, they're so expensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.84,0:07:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想着就借我爸的穿穿好了 -有道理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I just thought I'd borrow my dad's. -I hear ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.26,0:07:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧 我们去趟商店 跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. We'll make a little pit stop. Come on, follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.51,0:07:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.76,0:07:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（里士满剧院）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.81,0:07:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you lookin' at?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.93,0:07:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好吗我的西装怎么样 还不错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You boys all right? How's my suit? All good? Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.52,0:07:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.81,0:07:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 谢谢大家给我拍照\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, thank you, guys, so much for taking my picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.57,0:07:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们叫什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are your names?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.90,0:07:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是杰瑞 你是戴夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you're Jerry, and you're Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.32,0:07:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们都是为我来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you all came for.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.28,0:07:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左眼眉 右眼眉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Left eyebrow. Right eyebrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.33,0:07:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困惑的表情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Confused look.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.12,0:07:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍吧 这才是你们真正会登出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, now for the one that you'll actually use.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.21,0:07:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 亲爱的 亲一下怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's it, darling. How about a kiss?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.04,0:07:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（第十届资助贫困儿童年度福利晚宴）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.84,0:07:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-浪漫永存 -伙计们 抱歉 我只是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Romance is not dead. -Guys, sorry, sorry. I just--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.13,0:07:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让他们拍张照 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Gonna let them take a picture. -Yeah. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.84,0:07:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上得进去了 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need to get inside. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.89,0:07:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡 看这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rebecca, over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.80,0:07:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很好 女士们 -瑞贝卡 看这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Nice, ladies. -Rebecca, over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.93,0:07:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看上去美极了 -现在 看向左边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You look perfect. -Now, look to your left.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.85,0:08:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这个环节\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hate this part.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.02,0:08:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-韦尔顿女士 -很美 好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Miss Welton. -Lovely. Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.31,0:08:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.77,0:08:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把一只脚放在另一脚前面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just put one foot in front of the other, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.82,0:08:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手放在屁股上 张开手指成爪型\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then put your hand on your hip and make, like, a claw shape.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.32,0:08:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最上相的姿势\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the most flattering.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.70,0:08:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-瑞贝卡 笑一笑 -瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Rebecca, give us a smile. -Rebecca!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.66,0:08:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看她 美炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at her. She's fucking fit!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.22,0:08:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别扭来扭去的 大方展示你的西装\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't strut. Let the suit do the work.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.81,0:08:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德拉索 我的天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted Lasso. My God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.10,0:08:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是 老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right back at ya, boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.31,0:08:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时就有预感你会选这件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had a hunch you were gonna pick this dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.40,0:08:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请允许我说一句 这裙子就像为你量身定做的一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And may I say, you are wearing the heck out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.82,0:08:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.90,0:08:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看内特 挺帅的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Check out Nate. Looking pretty dapper himself, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.36,0:08:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴再次见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.57,0:08:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很高兴认识你 -很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.57,0:08:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我失陪一下 -没问题 去忙你的事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-If you'll both excuse me. -Absolutely, yeah. Go do your thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 彼尔德在那边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, there's Beard over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.91,0:09:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他的新欢 简\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's his new gal, Jane.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.92,0:09:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 他们在周五晚上的象棋俱乐部认识的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, they met at his Friday night chess club.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.42,0:09:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然 他们喜欢彼此的套路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apparently, they liked each other's moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.97,0:09:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That wasn't a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.05,0:09:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Was it not?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.55,0:09:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是有一点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I guess it kinda was.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.43,0:09:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不拍 走开 去死 不拍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. No. Fuck off. Fuck you. No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.52,0:09:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.10,0:09:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就比较尴尬了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is gonna be so uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.52,0:09:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要换桌 -别走 嘿 回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm switching tables. -No, no, no. Hey. Come on back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.73,0:09:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我安排的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is my doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.86,0:09:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你们骗来了 坐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I parent trapped y'all. Take a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.66,0:09:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 你们两个傻小子让更衣室分成两派\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, listen. You two knuckleheads have split our locker room in half.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.91,0:09:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到更衣室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And when it comes to locker rooms,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.54,0:09:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望更衣室就像我妈的泳衣一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I like 'em just like my mother's bathing suits.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.62,0:09:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望看到的是一个整体 听懂了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I only wanna see 'em in one piece, you hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.50,0:09:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们必须解决这个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So we're fixing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.79,0:09:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我你们最看不惯对方的地方 说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me what's the biggest issue you got with each other. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.88,0:09:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's a piece of shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.13,0:09:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他脑袋着火了 我不会往他耳朵里撒尿的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If his brain was on fire, I wouldn't piss in his ear.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.88,0:09:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 不是非得变成好朋友才能做好队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, hey. You don't need to be best friends to be great teammates.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.30,0:10:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想大鲨鱼和科比 对吗 列侬和麦卡尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think about Shaq and Kobe, right? Lennon and McCartney.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.47,0:10:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连胡迪和巴斯光年 也看对方的塑料不顺眼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Heck, even Woody and Buzz got under each other's plastic.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.76,0:10:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡迪不是布做的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wasn't Woody made out of cloth?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.02,0:10:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的提醒 内特 但现在不是时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I appreciate you, Nate, but now's not the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.77,0:10:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这些强势二人组之间 有什么共同点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what all those dynamic duos had in common?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.06,0:10:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相尊重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mutual respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.77,0:10:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们得找到一些共同点 谁想开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Y'all gotta find some common ground. So who wants to get the ball rollin'?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.94,0:10:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.07,0:10:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内特 你的西服很好看 我觉得你很帅\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nate, that's a very nice suit. I think you look chic.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.28,0:10:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 其实这是我人生中的第二套西服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. It's actually only the second suit I've ever owned.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.54,0:10:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一套是我出生时自带的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The first one was my suit when I was a naked baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.21,0:10:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 泰德讲的时候很好笑 我…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, it's funny when Ted says it. I--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.21,0:10:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个名词叫“诞辰礼服”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, the term "birthday suit"
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.63,0:10:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这样说会更有笑点 -天啊 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-woulda helped you a ton there, yeah. -Oh, God, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.76,0:10:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 我们再试一次 好吗 嘿 杰米 从你开始好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's try this again, all right? Hey, Jamie. You wanna go?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.43,0:10:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.85,0:10:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-罗伊 -他是个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Roy. -He's a piece of shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.47,0:10:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来回就这一句话好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna stick with that, huh? Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.60,0:10:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个主意 可能会帮上点忙 也可能会伤到大家的感情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here's an idea that's gonna help a little or hurt a whole lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.06,0:10:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁想喝一杯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who needs a drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.65,0:10:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演出嘉宾那件事有什么进展吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any progress with the musical guest?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.24,0:10:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟很多经纪人谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've talked to a number of agents
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.86,0:11:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还列了一个非常详尽的 无法参加的候选人名单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and made a fairly extensive list of those who cannot make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.91,0:11:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是排除法 一切进展顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Process of elimination. We're on our way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.00,0:11:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你在这儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, there she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.58,0:11:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在练习演说词吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're working on your speech, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.75,0:11:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁伯特很擅长演讲这部分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rupert was always very good at the public speaking part.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.46,0:11:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你分享一个小技巧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, here's a little trick of the trade.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.96,0:11:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始拿自己开涮 开个小玩笑什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just make fun of yourself right off the bat, a little joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.51,0:11:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Folks will love that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.59,0:11:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我应该开自己什么玩笑呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, so, what should I make fun of myself about?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.06,0:11:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, right, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.73,0:11:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道…你可以…不行 好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know-- You know what would be-- No. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.23,0:11:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说不出口 是吧 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not gonna walk into that one, are you, Ted?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.32,0:11:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 老板 不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, ma'am. Nope, nope, nope. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.95,0:11:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck though.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.03,0:11:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想到了 不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? I thought of something. No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.45,0:11:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后走车四\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Queen to rook four.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.08,0:11:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们下象棋都不用棋盘的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait, are y'all playing a game without a board?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.54,0:11:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰了 对不起 请继续\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry to interrupt. My fault. Sorry. Carry on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.63,0:11:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑士走王五\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Knight to king five.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.60,0:12:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good evening,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.85,0:12:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎参加第十届资助贫困儿童 年度福利晚宴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and welcome to the Tenth Annual Benefit for Underprivileged Children.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.06,0:12:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我可以拥抱你们每个人 感谢你们的善意捐助…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I could hug each of you as a thank you for your kind donations, well...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.52,0:12:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能不会那么做 因为大家都知道 我不喜欢拥抱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I probably wouldn't because, as we all know, I'm not much of a hugger.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.65,0:12:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍候是我们的竞拍环节 我希望大家都把支票本带在了身上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I do hope you've all brought your checkbooks with you for our auction later.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.91,0:12:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们可以竞拍我们的里士满球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you can all bid on our very own Richmond players.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.29,0:12:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老规矩 除非球员签了免责协议 不然不准调戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Same rule as always, no hanky-panky unless the player signs a waiver.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.47,0:12:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rupert?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.84,0:12:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.97,0:12:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个…意外的惊喜啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What a... lovely surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.72,0:12:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道我会来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Weren't you expecting me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.39,0:12:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为你拒绝了我的请帖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only 'cause you RSVP'd no.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.23,0:12:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做一个有钱的废物就是有这样的好处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, one of the perks of being a wealthy good-for-nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.56,0:12:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候晚上的时间很神奇地就空出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sometimes my nights just magically free up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.24,0:13:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}May I? Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.57,0:13:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们、先生们 通过你们的帮助 我们去年筹集了80万英镑\NGals and gents, with your help, we raised £800,000 last year.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.54,0:13:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年 希望会更多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this year, hopefully even more.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.37,0:13:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我是不请自来 但我实在太想帮忙了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I know I'm crashing your party, but I so badly wanna help.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.59,0:13:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手指脚趾都在祈祷 你会让我留下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My fingers and toes are crossed that you will have me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.38,0:13:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.13,0:13:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他在“无聊桌”放把椅子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get him a seat at the boring table.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.55,0:13:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only joking.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.34,0:13:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4号桌 鲁伯特曼尼恩 各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Table four. Rupert Mannion, everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.06,0:13:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 美女\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, doll.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.19,0:13:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妈呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.53,0:13:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -那…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you. -That--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.53,0:13:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内森 拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nathe, Nathe, Nathe. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.49,0:13:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 伙计们 这是我新买的西服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, guys, this is a brand-new suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.54,0:13:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就别捉弄我了 明天补上行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rather than messing with me tonight, can you just get me two times tomorrow?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.29,0:13:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊不准我们再欺负你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy said we're not allowed anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.92,0:14:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他居然撞了我的头 我有一半时间都是晕着的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He fucking headbutted me. I'm still dizzy half the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.84,0:14:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生让我别喝酒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The doctors told me not to drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.01,0:14:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.76,0:14:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要穿衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yet another reason shirts exist.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.55,0:14:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴 一点都不好笑 烫到了我的乳头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut up, it's not funny. Burned my nipple.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.14,0:14:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望我是那个冰块\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wish I was that ice cube.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.81,0:14:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会竞拍跟你共度一夜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will be bidding for a night with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.36,0:14:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, love.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.44,0:14:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是一次约会 不是一整晚 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, it's just a date though. It's not a whole night. So...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.07,0:14:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候就知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.57,0:14:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计 这事我经历过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mate, I've done these before.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.82,0:14:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她竞拍价超过三千块 你就得跟她上床\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If she bids over 3,000, you will have to fuck her.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.24,0:14:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是真的吗 -你不用做全套的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Is that true? -You don't have to go all the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.33,0:14:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做一部分就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just, like, some of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.63,0:14:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用手指\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fingering.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.05,0:14:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你们的 这桌都不是正常人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck you. Fuck this table.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.34,0:14:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie, it was a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.43,0:14:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a joke. Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.47,0:14:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened now?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.77,0:14:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一如往常 杰米那个戏精又作天作地了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just the usual. Jamie being a little bitch prima donna.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.90,0:15:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊 我问你一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy, let me ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.52,0:15:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你23岁的时候什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What were you like when you were 23?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.69,0:15:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在联盟里踢球 赚很多钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Playing in this league, making all that money.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.03,0:15:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一个作天作地的戏精 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Little bitch prima donna. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.91,0:15:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道人们都说 “年轻人浪费了青春”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know how they say that "youth is wasted on the young"?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.58,0:15:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我说 别浪费了岁月给你的智慧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I say don't let the wisdom of age be wasted on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.08,0:15:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.46,0:15:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚想到的 我太厉害了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just came up with that. I feel pretty good about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.59,0:15:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟科林和艾萨克谈过了 我想感谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted to say thanks for talking to Colin and Isaac.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.14,0:15:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的脸为什么贴这么近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why is your face so close to mine?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.85,0:15:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始的计划是拥抱你 但我临阵退缩了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, my initial plan was to hug you, but I just chickened out just now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.77,0:15:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.28,0:15:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了 够了 -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay, we're done. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.36,0:15:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 我想介绍你认识鲁伯特曼尼恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, I'd like to introduce you to Rupert Mannion.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.99,0:15:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼恩先生 你好吗 -叫我鲁伯特就好 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Mr. Mannion, how are you? -It's Rupert, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.62,0:15:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是管理我俱乐部的人 更不应该见外了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Especially for the man who's managing my club.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.29,0:16:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经是你的俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Used to be your club.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.58,0:16:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 但是…在我心里 依然是我的俱乐部 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, of course, but... it's still my club in here, love.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.88,0:16:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上一支球队就会爱一辈子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Love of a sports team is a lifetime obsession.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.88,0:16:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.80,0:16:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点像你最好朋友的姐姐 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kinda like your best friend's older sister, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.92,0:16:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, but do me a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.01,0:16:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你去了堪萨斯城 遇到一个叫汤姆迪宁的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're ever in Kansas City and come across a fella named Tom Dineen,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.80,0:16:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉他我说过这话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}don't tell him I said that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.01,0:16:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.64,0:16:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们接连输了两场这事 我就不太喜欢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't love our last two losses though.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.14,0:16:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-成绩太差了 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Horrible showing. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.48,0:16:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须得说 真希望我没说出口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Had to say it, wish I didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.86,0:16:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 谁知道呢 也许我们能翻盘呢 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay. Who knows? Maybe we'll turn it around, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.40,0:16:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天 我相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. I believe you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.20,0:16:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you believe him?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.66,0:16:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你说不 那今晚可就没法收场了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Night's gonna take a turn for the worse if you say no.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.99,0:16:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然相信泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course I believe in Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.21,0:16:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正是我们需要的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's exactly what we've needed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.67,0:16:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别喝太多香槟 亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not too much champagne now, dear.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.46,0:16:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竞拍的时候要保持清醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gotta stay sharp for the auction.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.63,0:16:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如你来负责竞拍吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you do the auction?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.51,0:16:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我不能抢了你的风头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I couldn't. This is your night.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.38,0:16:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道大家更想看到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We both know they'd rather see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.35,0:16:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 这是…为了孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And besides, it's... for the children.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.85,0:17:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the children.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.10,0:17:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 失陪一下 我得招呼下其他客人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. If you'll excuse me, I need to speak to the other guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.02,0:17:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不说 我喜欢你这条裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I must say, I love that dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.19,0:17:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显得你很年轻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's very youthful.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.15,0:17:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你这样光鲜亮丽的站在舞台上 我为你高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good for you for getting back out there looking like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.74,0:17:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.12,0:17:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.87,0:17:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.33,0:17:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她今年过得不容易 她还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's been a hard year for her. Is she okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.62,0:17:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 她很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, she's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.25,0:17:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是很多事情需要操心 比如今晚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, a lot of moving pieces putting together a thing like this though.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.34,0:17:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后有个叫罗比威廉姆斯的家伙 临时爽约了 而且…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then she had this fella... Robbie Williams cancel on her and--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.09,0:17:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-罗比 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Robbie? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.18,0:17:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的老朋友了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, he's an old pal of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.01,0:17:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很乐意给他发个信息 我肯定能请得动他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm happy to text him. I bet you I can get his ass over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.22,0:17:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一定会很开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I bet she'd love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.43,0:17:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找她 先把旗子升起来 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll go track her down and run it up the flagpole, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.98,0:17:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 这是我家乡的俗语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. That's an expression from back home.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.90,0:17:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-意思是我要先问过她 -好极了 好戏开演了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Just means I'm gonna ask her. -Fabulous. Showtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.94,0:17:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 看好你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, go get 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.78,0:17:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有更烈一点的 比如说威士忌加冰之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I get something stronger, like a Jack on the rocks or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.61,0:17:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一份和两份混在一起 三份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A double and a single in one. A triple.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.87,0:18:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们、先生们 今晚计划稍微调整一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ladies and gentlemen, slight change in plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.08,0:18:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我禁不住哄骗 成了今晚的拍卖人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have been cajoled into being your auctioneer for this evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.46,0:18:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的第一个受害者是杰米塔特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And our first victim is Jamie Tartt.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.05,0:18:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝 你一定要赢到我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Babe, you have to win me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.47,0:18:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会竞拍自己男朋友的 看上去多可悲啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't bid on my own boyfriend. I'll look pathetic.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.60,0:18:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝 现在是2020年了 女人可以做任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Babe, it's 2020. Women can do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.60,0:18:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 拜托 你这么性感 上去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's not happening. Come on, you look hot. Go up there!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.18,0:18:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看他 各位 年轻帅气、魅力四射 真是个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at him, folks. Young, gorgeous, charming. The bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.77,0:18:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们起拍价是五千英镑\NSo, we'll start with £5,000.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.73,0:18:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要他 鲁伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want him, Rupert.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.11,0:18:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢丽尔巴纳比出价五千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Five thousand from Cheryl Barnaby.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.70,0:18:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满设得兰矮种马的养殖大户\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond's premier breeder of Shetland ponies.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.41,0:18:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人出价六千吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we hear six?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.08,0:18:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Six thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.29,0:18:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六千 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Six. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.83,0:18:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-七千 -七千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Seven thousand. -Seven thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.92,0:18:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ten thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.13,0:18:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stunning.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.63,0:18:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是竞价还是竞价人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that applies to the bid and the bidder.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.76,0:19:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.09,0:19:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一万两千英镑 -一万四千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Twelve thousand pounds. -Fourteen thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.10,0:19:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万四千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fourteen thousand!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.68,0:19:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万六千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sixteen thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.89,0:19:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万八千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eighteen.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.48,0:19:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万八千 还有人出价吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eighteen thousand. Do I hear any advance?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.40,0:19:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有 两万五千\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Twenty-five thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.36,0:19:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两万五千一次 两万五千两次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Twenty-five thousand! Going once. Twice.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.44,0:19:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成交 基莉琼斯拍得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sold to Keeley Jones.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.28,0:19:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花两万五千英镑就能领回家的男朋友 为什么还要免费享用呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why spend the time with your boyfriend for free when you can have him for 25 grand?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.70,0:19:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你欠我一次人情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You owe me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.71,0:19:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你在这儿呢 出来透透气 是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. There you are. Getting a little fresh air, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.25,0:19:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 那些人力车真蠢 但看上去还挺有趣的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Those rickshaw bike things are so silly, but they do look like fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.59,0:19:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.51,0:19:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你坐过吗 -没有 女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You ever been on one? -No, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.30,0:19:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久之前 我和我妻子度假的时候 租过那种自行车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My wife and I once rented one of those tandem bikes on vacation a while back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.89,0:19:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么美好的回忆 她摔断了胳膊 而我…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not the best experience. She broke her arm and I actually...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.27,0:19:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嗑到了牙 还伤到了会阴处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I chipped a tooth, and I bruised my perineum.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.19,0:19:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 你还好吗 -只是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, you okay? -It's just...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.90,0:19:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人 他了解我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That man, he knows me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.36,0:20:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前觉得即使他做了那些事 但他的坦诚算是高尚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I used to think his blunt honesty was noble rather than what it really is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.28,0:20:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which is just...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.58,0:20:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐藏自己不安全感的最残忍的方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the cruelest way of hiding his own insecurities.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.46,0:20:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会说穿这个、吃那个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'd say wear this, eat that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.75,0:20:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很听话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I listened.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.51,0:20:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我却独自一人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But now I'm alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.55,0:20:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我独自一人 泰德 正如他当初所说 这就是我选择离开的下场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm alone, Ted. Just like he said I would be if I left.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.27,0:20:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want to be alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.52,0:20:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 好了 没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. It's okay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.83,0:20:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想坐上去离开这里吗来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna hop on this thing and get the heck outta Dodge? Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.79,0:20:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望我可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wish.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.21,0:21:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不行 不过谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not right now. Thank you though.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.97,0:21:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经开始拍卖了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Has he started the auction?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.64,0:21:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.72,0:21:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 我很开心他这么做了 这样我们会募集到更多的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. I'm glad he's done that. We'll get much more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.94,0:21:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管他做了什么 人们都一样喜欢他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No matter what he does, they just love him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.27,0:21:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要回去吗 -不 你进去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You wanna head back in? -No, you go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.69,0:21:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得缓一缓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to freshen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.78,0:21:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这样子估计就像是 午睡刚醒的罗伯特史密斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I probably look like Robert Smith after he's woken up from a nap.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.41,0:21:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常情绪化的男人 没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Very emotional man. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.20,0:21:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我去里面等你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, I'll see you inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.30,0:21:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是新人的那会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I was coming up,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.38,0:21:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俱乐部有个老家伙叫道格拉斯斯塔谢维克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there was this old geezer at the club, Doug Stashwick.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.89,0:21:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他总是针对我 我们互相看不顺眼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was always on me. Hated each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.60,0:21:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想知道我们怎么赢了联赛吗 -不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You wanna know how we won the league? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.39,0:21:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是美国佬教练那一套\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was the same shit Yankee Doodle was peddling.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.81,0:21:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他坐下来对我说：“大家都把话说开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He sat me down and he said, "Let's get it all out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.19,0:22:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出对彼此的不满”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You tell me why I'm a prick, and I'll tell you why you are."
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.40,0:22:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是个可恶的混蛋… -不 我先来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You're a nasty bastard-- -No, I'm going first.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.74,0:22:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我知道我应该传给你…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even though I know I should pass to you...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.03,0:22:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你太自私太傲慢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you're so selfish and arrogant.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.95,0:22:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次我传给你 都让我他妈想吐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every time I do, it makes me want to fucking puke.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.58,0:22:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候 墙上挂了一张你的海报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I had a poster of you on my wall when I was a kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.75,0:22:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时喜欢看你比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Used to love watching you play.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.72,0:22:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你已经不是曾经的你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you're not the player that you used to be,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.43,0:22:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了几个奖杯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and just because you won a few trophies,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.76,0:22:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想要所有人都臣服于你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you walk around here expecting everyone to kiss your ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.81,0:22:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对 我确实会这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I can be like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.69,0:22:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在轮到你承认我说的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now's the bit where you admit to what I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.36,0:22:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想承认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.99,0:22:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你说的…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even if it is just...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.66,0:22:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么一点对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a little bit true.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.21,0:23:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和那个叫道格的 你们最后成了朋友吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and that Doug bloke, you ever become friends?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.38,0:23:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然没有 我希望他死了才好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck no. I hope he's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.63,0:23:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬你也一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To you dying.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.22,0:23:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Such a prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.64,0:23:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊 搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Howdy, partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.60,0:23:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我联系罗比的事 你问过瑞贝卡了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you ask Rebecca what she thought about texting Robbie?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.36,0:23:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到她 别担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? I couldn't find her. I say don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.86,0:23:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你改变了主意就告诉我 短信立马就发出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you change your mind, say the word and-- sent.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.53,0:23:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他随叫随到 我再去倒点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll be right over. Top up.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.57,0:23:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 鲁伯特 我突然想到了一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Rupert, something just occurred to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.78,0:23:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能发短信给罗伯威廉姆斯 让他今晚过来…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you could've texted Robbie Williams asking him to come tonight...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.79,0:23:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你叫他别来也很容易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you could've probably just as easily asked him not to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.50,0:23:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我这人就太烂了 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, now, that would've made me a real piece of shit, wouldn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.76,0:23:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 泰德 你觉得瑞贝卡知道 真正的阿黛尔长什么样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Ted. Do you think Rebecca knows what the real Adele looks like?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.89,0:24:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要进行一次小小的冒险 我需要一位副驾驶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to go on a little adventure, and I need a copilot.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.23,0:24:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想要我 -对 不要最贵 只要最好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-And you want me? -Yeah. Forget the rest, I need the best.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.94,0:24:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.82,0:24:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你 顺便一提 -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you, by the way. -Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.53,0:24:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红毯照片已经在网上登出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The red carpet photos are already online,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.70,0:24:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于也好看一次了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I actually look all right for once.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.42,0:24:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴很帮上你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Glad to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.59,0:24:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.71,0:24:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think you should know
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.80,0:24:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竞拍杰米的那个年轻女人 是他今晚带的另一个伴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the young woman that was bidding on Jamie was actually his other plus-one.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.85,0:24:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个不要脸的小王八蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cheeky little prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.89,0:24:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能喝一口你的酒吗 -可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Can I have a sip of your drink? -Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.48,0:24:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.69,0:24:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最讨厌橄榄了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In anything else, I hate olives.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.61,0:24:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这个橘黄色的阴蒂一样的东西 真的很诡异\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think the little, like, orange clitoris thing is really freaky.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.91,0:24:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟足球运动员约会过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you ever dated a footballer?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.37,0:24:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了 -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What? -Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.95,0:25:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不该笑的 听上去…有评判的嫌疑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I shouldn't laugh. It sounds... judgy.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.33,0:25:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系 你本来就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's okay. You are a bit judgy.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.54,0:25:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我18岁的时候 谈了一个23岁的足球运动员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So when I was 18, I dated a footballer that was 23.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.30,0:25:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我快30了 我还在约会23岁的足球运动员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now I'm close to 30, and I am still dating a 23-year-old footballer.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.30,0:25:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是女版的莱昂纳多迪卡普里奥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm Leonardo DiCaprio.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.85,0:25:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他们都挺有趣的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They are pretty fun though.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.10,0:25:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单、有钱、强壮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Simple, rich, fit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.60,0:25:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那责任感呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about accountable?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.02,0:25:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.61,0:25:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说 所有人都会犯错误 但是…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I mean, everyone makes mistakes, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.65,0:25:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嫁给了一个男人12年\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was married to a man for 12 years
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.99,0:25:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从来没有为自己犯过的错承担责任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who never once took responsibility for any single one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.00,0:25:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.25,0:25:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨 -我叫基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hi. -I'm Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.34,0:25:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我叫贝克丝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, I'm Bex.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.42,0:25:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很高兴认识你 贝克丝 -很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Really nice to meet you, Bex. -Nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.30,0:25:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介意我和这位单独聊聊吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you mind if I just have a minute on my own with this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.47,0:25:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, sure. Lovely to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.76,0:26:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是你的新女友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She your new girlfriend?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.14,0:26:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别激动 宝贝 这都是品牌计划的一部分 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Relax, babe. It's all part of the branding plan, innit?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.85,0:26:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有两个女人为我竞拍 会提升我的价值\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I've got two women bidding on me, it makes me look more valuable.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.86,0:26:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白我的意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you know what I mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.77,0:26:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很聪明吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's fucking smart, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.69,0:26:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是名单上唯一 赢过冠军联赛的罗伊肯特 大家欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And now, the only former Champions League winner on the menu, say hello to Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.53,0:26:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Granddad.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.08,0:26:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出价最高者将有机会在豪华酒店度过一天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the highest bidder gets to spend a day at a swanky hotel by the pool
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.42,0:26:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在泳池边喝冰冻黛可丽 晒着日光浴…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}drinking frozen daiquiris and soaking up the rays--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.04,0:26:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我们说好的 没有黛可丽 没有日光浴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, we said there's no daiquiris and no rays.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.09,0:26:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有该死的泳池 我们不会离开邮编是SW14的区域\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's not gonna be a fucking pool either. We're not leaving SW14.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.38,0:26:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去很嫉妒 太有意思了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You looked so jealous. It was so cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.14,0:26:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得嫉妒有意思 是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think jealousy is cool, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.10,0:26:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道 宝贝 我从不嫉妒别人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't know, babe. I don't get jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.68,0:26:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人出价一百英镑竞拍这个 突然间变得很无趣的约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, can we have 100 quid for what's turning out to be a very boring date?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.52,0:26:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 一千英镑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. A thousand pounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.31,0:26:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有人加价吗 -两千英镑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Any advances on that? -Two thousand pounds!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.86,0:26:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢丽尔很厉害啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cheryl's got fire inside her.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.15,0:27:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-三千英镑 -宝贝 你这样只会让自己难堪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Three thousand pounds. -Babe, you're just embarrassing yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.70,0:27:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四千英镑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Four thousand pounds!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.70,0:27:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五千英镑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Five thousand!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.54,0:27:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六千英镑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Six thousand pounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.91,0:27:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-六千还有人加价吗 -对不起 我错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Any advance on six? -I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.08,0:27:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢丽尔拍得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, sold to Cheryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.72,0:27:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的拍卖到此结束 但还有一个小惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That concludes the auction, apart from one small surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.60,0:27:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本人会捐赠一百万英镑\NI am personally donating £1 million to the cause.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.15,0:27:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.65,0:27:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢大家 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you very much. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.53,0:27:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就超出了 瑞贝卡筹集80万的目标 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that, I believe, gets Rebecca over her goal of 800,000. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.45,0:27:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了孩子们 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the children, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.55,0:28:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.72,0:28:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是卡姆科尔 是一名还未被发掘的新秀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This here is Cam Cole. He's an undiscovered mega-talent.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.72,0:28:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 卡姆 给他们展示一下你的才艺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on, Cam. Show 'em what you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.44,0:28:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你疯了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you insane?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.52,0:28:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 瑞贝卡 你不能以貌取人 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Rebecca. You do not wanna judge this book by its cover right here, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.86,0:28:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The hell with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.61,0:28:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.91,0:28:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 女士们、先生们 我很遗憾通知各位…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello again. Ladies and gentlemen, I regret to inform you that...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.20,0:28:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗比威廉姆斯因为突发事件今晚无法到场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Robbie Williams is unable to be here tonight due to an emergency.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.38,0:28:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们请到了优秀的替代歌手 你们一定会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we have a brilliant replacement for you who you are just going to love.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.30,0:28:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者 至少在回去的路上有得吐槽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or, at least, have lots to talk about on the way home.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.97,0:28:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请欢迎这位来自…请欢迎卡姆什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All the way from outside... please welcome Cam something.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.81,0:28:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特么的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bollocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.69,0:28:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.96,0:29:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 亲爱的自然母亲 请原谅我们的所作所为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mama, sweet mama nature Please forgive us and what we've done
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.55,0:29:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们别下棋了 去跳舞怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can we just forget about the game and go and have a dance?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.59,0:29:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后走国王五 将军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Queen to king five. Checkmate.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.81,0:29:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们伤害了妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've gone and hurt our mama
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.86,0:29:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她大发雷霆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And her wrath has begun
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.97,0:30:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我是妈妈的好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I'm a good boy to my mama
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.10,0:30:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.89,0:30:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有糟糕的兄弟姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got bad siblings
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.90,0:30:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（卡姆科尔）
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.53,0:30:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-非常感谢 -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you so much. -You're so welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.20,0:30:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们玩得很开心 -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-We really had a great time. -Thank you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.29,0:30:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.95,0:30:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次感谢你这么大方的捐助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you again for such an unbelievable donation.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.75,0:30:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-明年再见了 -我已经等不及了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-See you again next year. -Can't wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.47,0:30:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个万人迷啊 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What a charmer, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.34,0:30:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Indeed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.26,0:30:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也许觉得你是唯一看透他本性的人…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You may think that you're the only one that can see who he really is...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.69,0:30:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.82,0:31:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐 你没事吧 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, boy. You all right, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.41,0:31:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快走吧 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Quick. -All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.32,0:31:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚很愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fun night.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.91,0:31:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 等等 慢点走 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, wait, hold on. Slow down, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.17,0:31:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能别生我的气了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will you stop being mad at me now?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.00,0:31:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, babe.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.63,0:31:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你哪里对不起我了吗 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you even know what you're sorry for, Jamie?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.47,0:31:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总问这个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You always ask me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.39,0:31:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 帮我个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, do me a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.60,0:31:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两口子吵架别拿我当道具\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't use me as a prop in your little fights.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.56,0:31:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我觉得自己像个傻子一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Made me feel like an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.06,0:31:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. I--
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.44,0:31:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不该那么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I shouldn't have done that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.90,0:31:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.53,0:31:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正也没人会竞拍你 伙计 走开啦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one was bidding on you anyway, mate. Just fuck off.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.41,0:31:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.66,0:31:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟他道什么歉啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you saying sorry to him for?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.71,0:32:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做人要承担责任 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Being accountable matters, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.67,0:32:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们分手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're done.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.09,0:32:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see you around.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.93,0:32:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.43,0:32:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我能拿走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me, can I take these?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.64,0:32:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两瓶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.45,0:32:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想不想大醉一场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you wanna go get, like, really drunk?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.53,0:32:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好啊 -然后我们可以去抢个银行什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes, I do. -Then we can go rob a bank or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.00,0:32:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米歇尔和亨利下周过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle and Henry are coming out next weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.13,0:32:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了 教练 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, that's great, Coach. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.21,0:32:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 跟我说说你和简 到底怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So come on, tell me about you and Jane. What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.09,0:32:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又犯了同样的错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.30,0:32:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-更在乎输赢而不是对方 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Put the game before the dame, huh? -Yup.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.09,0:32:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候能吸取教训呢 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When are you gonna learn, Coach?
