[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.91,0:00:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（国家日报 模特泳池派对混乱）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.67,0:00:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.42,0:00:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Siri 呼叫“猪头”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Siri, call Shithead.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.89,0:01:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.98,0:01:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《太阳报》没有任何 关于泰德和基莉的报道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is nothing in The Sun about Ted and Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.94,0:01:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有 你在办公室吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing. Are you in your office?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.94,0:01:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.23,0:01:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那赶紧给我上来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then get up here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.44,0:01:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见 孩子们 告诉妈妈我爱她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bye, boys. Tell Mum I love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.28,0:01:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敲门 嘿 老板 我不知道你周末过得如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Knock, knock. Hey, boss, I don't know about you,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我度过了一个无比惬意的周日\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I had an absolute peach of a Sunday.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.83,0:01:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.70,0:01:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 终于见到了大本钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, finally saw Big Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.33,0:01:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪 我还以为我已经见过 全世界最大的钟了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, I thought I'd seen the biggest clock there was.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.67,0:01:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小的时候 父母带着我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I was a kid, my folks took me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.50,0:01:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去密尔沃基市看了艾伦布拉德利钟塔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the Allen-Bradley Clock Tower up there in Milwaukee.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.09,0:01:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果他们把我一个人扔在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They ended up leaving me there all by myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.84,0:01:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三小时42分钟 你知道我为什么记得这么清楚吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, three hours and 42 minutes. You know how I know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.84,0:01:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直盯着钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were staring at a clock?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.22,0:01:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我盯着表看呢 答对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was staring at a clock. That's exactly right. Yeah, bingo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.60,0:01:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这问题很有迷惑性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a little bit of a mystery puzzle.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.89,0:01:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你立刻就猜到了 你很聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You figured it out right away. You're a sharp cookie.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.47,0:01:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-泰德 -在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ted. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.56,0:01:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到我们刚才谈论的时间问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Speaking as we were mere moments ago, about time,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.98,0:01:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不幸的是 我没时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I unfortunately don't have any.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.77,0:01:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要开一个品牌推广会议 所以…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have a branding meeting, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.11,0:01:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很同情奶牛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I always feel so bad for the cows,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.61,0:01:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你总得钉上牌子才能避免它们跑丢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you gotta do it otherwise they get lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.11,0:02:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个双关语的笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was a branding joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.20,0:02:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们是在堪萨斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we were in Kansas right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.58,0:02:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在正耐心等你笑完呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd just be sitting here waiting for you to finish laughing. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.29,0:02:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天见 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see ya tomorrow, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.58,0:02:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 我盯着钟表指针呢 -很好 你开窍了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. Counting the minutes. -Yeah, there you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.90,0:02:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我们来看看 守门员在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Let's see what we got here. I've got this fella up here, the goalie.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.48,0:02:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这些球员在这里 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then all these guys over here, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.74,0:02:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个往左 这个往右 再过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And going over here, going over that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.32,0:02:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙直接穿过中场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This son of a gun's gonna go all the way down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.20,0:02:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水晶宫队上周把我们打得落花流水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Crystal Palace kicked our booties last week.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.25,0:02:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们目前的进攻阵型\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this here, is our current offense that we are running,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为这个策略太烂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I think it stinks!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.04,0:02:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部擦掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get rid of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.59,0:03:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在可能会好奇 我干嘛要画在板子上再擦掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, you might be wondering why'd I draw all that up there just to erase it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.72,0:03:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我相信象征性姿态的作用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that is because I believe in symbolic gestures.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.56,0:03:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.52,0:03:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你昨晚几点回家的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What time did you get home last night?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.77,0:03:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没回家 -真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Didn't. -Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.73,0:03:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我们现在的进攻就只是传切战术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, look, our whole offense right now is all give-and-go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.15,0:03:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把球传给杰米 其他人就算完成任务了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give the ball to Jamie and everyone else can go to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.73,0:03:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要正式开始寻找新策略 听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I am officially on the prowl for any new ideas, you hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.28,0:03:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你有什么想法吗 内特 -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You got something, Nate? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.74,0:03:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.08,0:03:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 天啊 还是算了吧 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. No. God, no. Never mind, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.41,0:03:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快说吧 你也是我们的一员 来吧 别吞吞吐吐的了 你有什么想法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on now. You're one of us. Let's go. Fire away. What do you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.00,0:03:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 就是…不对 在另一个兜里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, right. Well, it's just... No, other pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.79,0:03:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我自己的一个想法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just something that I thought of.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.42,0:03:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.80,0:03:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.13,0:03:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 也不是特别好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what, it's not even very good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.34,0:03:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是馊主意 甚至挺丢脸的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's probably really bad. It's embarrassing even.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.47,0:03:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是… -抱歉 内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I just-- -Sorry, Nate.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.56,0:03:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太听得清那些不自信的人说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have a real tricky time hearing folks that don't believe in themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.47,0:03:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我直接问你好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna ask you real quick again.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.81,0:03:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你认为这个主意可行吗 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Do you think this idea will work? -Yeah, I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.94,0:03:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你干嘛那么大声 内特 -天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Why you screaming at us, Nate? -God!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.11,0:03:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就站在这儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.15,0:03:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 过来 跟我们详细解释下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, come on now. Walk us through it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.78,0:04:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我觉得如果我们从侧翼发起进攻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. So, I thought if we started the attack on the wing,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.28,0:04:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米就能进入左侧球场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie could run through nearside,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.70,0:04:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后防守球员会跟上来 山姆可以顶替他的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then when the defense follows, Sam could fill his spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.49,0:04:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 把杰米当作诱饵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, use Jamie as a decoy?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.33,0:04:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.12,0:04:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 算是吧 这种情况下是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Well, yeah, in-- Yeah, in this case, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.04,0:04:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来试试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's give it a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.17,0:04:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要用我的战术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What, you're gonna use my play?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.42,0:04:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我是说 我们会试一下 看看行不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I mean, we're gonna try it on, see if it fits.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.72,0:04:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, it might not.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.13,0:04:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是那样 这也是一个令人遐想的轮廓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then again, it might be a very flattering silhouette,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.01,0:04:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或许会穿上身走出店门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I might wear it right outta the store.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.89,0:04:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我感觉非常好 我走路的姿势都变得不一样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Makes me feel good and I start to strut.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.35,0:04:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心想：“我喜欢 我喜欢这种感觉”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm like, "I like this. I like the way this makes me feel."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.98,0:04:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他看看你的步伐 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Show him your strut, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.35,0:04:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就是这样 很好 就是这么走的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, there you go. Oh, yeah. Yep, that's how to strut.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.27,0:04:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看你的步伐 内特 来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me see you strut, Nate. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.19,0:04:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 内特 这样也行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you go, Nate. Yeah, that's one way to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.15,0:04:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.07,0:04:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去有点生气 但是不打紧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You look a little angry, but that's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.70,0:04:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错 我忘了球场在这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's my fault. I forgot the pitch is right this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.45,0:04:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 我们往这边走 跟上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's go. Strut this way. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.95,0:04:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still strutting.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.20,0:04:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一会见 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'll see you later. Yeah. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.12,0:04:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德嘿 能耽误你一点时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted! Hey, have you got a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.58,0:04:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯 一切还好吗 -还好 挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Everything okay? -Yeah, yeah. No, it's fine, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.26,0:05:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一点都不好 糟透了 -不会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's not fine. Everything's shit. -Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.93,0:05:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张照片将会登上 《太阳报》今天的头版\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This was gonna be the front page of The Sun today.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.39,0:05:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“球队经理挖明星球员墙角”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Manager Shags Star Player's Girlfriend."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.06,0:05:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得正确的版本应该是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think a more accurate headline would be,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.85,0:05:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“球队经理好心给年轻女孩喂饭 她并不是谁的附庸”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Manager Innocently Feeds Young Woman Whose Relationship Does Not Define Her."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.64,0:05:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 这件事很糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, this is really bad!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.23,0:05:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了一点 他们把我拍得太好看了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except I look insanely fit in this picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.40,0:05:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 光线映在你脸上很美\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, no, it's beautiful light.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.15,0:05:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友在这家报社工作 他说他最多能再拖一天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My friend who works at the paper said he can hold this story for one day
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.82,0:05:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.28,0:05:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等报道一出来 杰米会发飙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When this shit hits, Jamie is going to go mental.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.62,0:05:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有无数的狗仔队跟着我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's going to be photographers all over us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.16,0:05:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.08,0:05:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的下一张照片就不会这么完美了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The next picture of me will not be this perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.04,0:05:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会在张大嘴要打喷嚏时被拍下 就像…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am gonna be mid-sneeze face, like--
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.88,0:05:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你猜标题会怎么写 -祝你健康\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Guess what the headline will be. -Gesundheit?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.80,0:05:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“杰米的淫乱女友伤了塔特的心”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Jamie's Tart Breaks Tartt's Heart."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.76,0:05:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是刚才想到的吗 -是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Did you just come up with that? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.51,0:05:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所有人都会想读的 -当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Everyone would read that. -Of course they would.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.72,0:05:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道在这个该死的国家 押韵这个事有多大的威力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have no idea the power of rhyming in this goddamn country.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.10,0:05:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.22,0:05:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“拉索第三者插足导致球队惨败”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Lasso Makes Passo and Creates Team Fiasco."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.77,0:05:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基莉你全押上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley's got bars.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.02,0:06:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我又可爱又会押韵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm cute as a button and I can rhyme my ass off.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.98,0:06:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 怪不得他们想毁掉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}God, it's no wonder they want to destroy me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.78,0:06:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.58,0:06:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我爬楼梯爬了太久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, it took me so long to get up the stairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.54,0:06:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被…大约一百个人拦住闲聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was... stopped to talk by about a hundred people.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.62,0:06:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是什么都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.04,0:06:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找人把泰德和基莉的新闻发出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get someone to run the story about Ted and Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.25,0:06:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 老板 -泰德还有基莉 你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, boss. -Ted! And Keeley. Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.76,0:06:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在走廊捡到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I found that in the hall. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.09,0:06:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出了一点状况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, we got ourselves a situation here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.18,0:06:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给她看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go ahead, show her the picture, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.39,0:06:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗该死的《太阳报》 明天就要登出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See? And the fucking Sun is running it tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.48,0:06:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的 那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honestly, these people,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.77,0:06:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们完全不考虑别人的隐私和尊严\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they just have no regard for people's privacy and dignity.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.73,0:06:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我要查出来是哪个王八蛋拍的 还有是谁雇的他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm gonna find the piece of shit that took this and who hired them.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没这个必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. Not necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.98,0:06:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识报社的老板 我打个电话就能阻止这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know the owner of the paper. I can get this stopped with a phone call.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.49,0:06:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗天啊 谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really? Oh, my God. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.99,0:06:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 我怎么说的来着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See, what I tell ya, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.33,0:06:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这女人厉害着呢 坚强、自信、有能力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This woman right here is strong, confident and powerful.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.29,0:07:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板 我跟你讲 我不想看到 你和米歇尔奥巴马掰手腕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boss, I tell ya, I'd hate to see you and Michelle Obama arm wrestle,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.29,0:07:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但若真有这么一天 我肯定目不转睛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I wouldn't be able to take my eyes off it either.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.33,0:07:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是头一次被人这么夸奖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not a compliment I've had before.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.75,0:07:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-您的胳膊确实强壮得可以拍动作片了 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You do have perfect action figure-y arms. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.47,0:07:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种夸法也挺新鲜 总之 我很高兴能帮上忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's another one. Anyway, glad to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.22,0:07:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-All right. Yeah. -Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.18,0:07:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不客气 -再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. -See y'all later.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.10,0:07:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不可能找到我头上来 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no way she can trace that photo back to me, can she?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.56,0:07:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-应该是吧 -“应该”是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes. -What do you mean "yes"?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.19,0:07:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没用假名或是一次性手机吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you not use an alias or a burner phone?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.27,0:07:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是间谍 瑞贝卡 我只是球队运营总监\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not a spy, Rebecca. I'm just the director of football operations.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.65,0:07:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你两样都做得很棒呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And equally proficient at both.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.82,0:07:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 等等…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, thank you. Wait...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.99,0:07:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 来吧 山姆传给迪克森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, here we go. Sam lays it for Dickson.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.79,0:07:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 动作娴熟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, nice touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.08,0:07:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传给邦伯凯奇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Switch to Bumbercatch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.33,0:07:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米诱敌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie decoys through.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.63,0:07:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-山姆无人防守 -进了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sam wide open. -There it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.43,0:07:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮 内特 你感觉怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice play, Nate. How you feel?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.27,0:08:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 很多前所未有的感受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just don't know. So many new feelings. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.60,0:08:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点像长第一根阴毛的感觉 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kinda like getting your first pube, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.10,0:08:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 什么 -来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. What? -Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.56,0:08:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家做得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Hey. Nice work.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.02,0:08:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 先生们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, now, gentlemen,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.11,0:08:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一件事我们需要关注\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}here's the other thing we're gonna start focusing on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.69,0:08:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从进攻到防守的转换必须更加迅速\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Making quicker transitions from offense to defense.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.99,0:08:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要习惯“你好 再见”的模式 明天了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Y'all gotta start making your hellos goodbyes. You understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.20,0:08:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好一件事最简单的方法就是好好做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Easiest way to get that done well is to do it well.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.33,0:08:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但除此之外 你们要保持最佳状态 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But aside from that, you gotta be in great shape, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.16,0:08:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们所有人要围着场地跑两圈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, we are all gonna run two laps around this field.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.21,0:08:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡是输给我的人再加四圈 现在开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anyone who loses to me has to run four more. Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.13,0:08:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 让我看看你们的本事 -怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay, come on. What you got? -What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.13,0:08:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们追上来了 不准抄近道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're catching up. Don't cut that corner!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.14,0:08:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 你们追不上我 我是姜饼人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. You can't catch me, I'm the gingerbread man.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.18,0:08:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再快点 孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Faster, boys!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.73,0:08:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看看他这张脸 -科林 艾萨克 求你们了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Look at his face. -Colin, Isaac, please stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.98,0:08:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很疼 好疼啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, it really hurts now. It really hurts.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.73,0:08:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点 科林 这是我们的新教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be careful, Colin, now. That's our new coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.02,0:08:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对哦 小子 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Oh, right, boyo. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.78,0:08:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, gaffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.07,0:08:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.91,0:08:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 大家表现得非常好 伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, way to run out there today, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.33,0:09:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们跑得比我快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You guys are much faster than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.87,0:09:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了彼尔德教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except Coach Beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.96,0:09:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事我记得你高中时跑田径的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on? I thought you ran track in high school or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.25,0:09:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是象棋队的 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chess team, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.33,0:09:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利诺伊州冠军 宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Illinois State Champs, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.58,0:09:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 伊利诺伊是一个州 伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, yeah. Illinois is a state, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.46,0:09:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一件事 你们的衣柜里有礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One last thing, there are some gifts up in y'all's lockers.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.38,0:09:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提前放在里面的 希望大家喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In your little cubbies up there. So, hope you enjoy 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.02,0:09:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（奥森斯科特卡特 《安德的游戏》）
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.81,0:09:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（F斯科特菲茨杰拉德 《漂亮冤家》）
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.56,0:09:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一本破书\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a fucking book.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.07,0:09:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（马德琳英格 《时间的皱折》）
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.41,0:09:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（#我们是里士满）
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.58,0:09:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好计策 臭小子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice one, bitch boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.33,0:09:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -我只是觉得应该告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey. -Yeah, I just thought you should know
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.34,0:09:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的跟班内森每天都被杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that your boy Nathan's being harassed every single day
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.01,0:09:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他那帮混蛋死党们欺负\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by Jamie and his little... side-pricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.72,0:09:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯 -所以你早知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Right. -So you know already?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.43,0:09:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.55,0:10:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 你会解决这件事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you'll take care of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.22,0:10:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.68,0:10:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the fuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.85,0:10:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊 我在布鲁克里奇小学\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy, I learned two pretty big lessons
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.90,0:10:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崎岖不平的操场上吸取了两个教训\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on the rough-and-tumble playgrounds of Brookridge Elementary School.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.48,0:10:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一 如果小罗尼福奇给你棒棒糖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One, if little Ronnie Fowch offers you a candy bar,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.57,0:10:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要立刻拒绝 然后跑得越远越好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you immediately say no, and you get the hell outta there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.65,0:10:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为很有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause there's a good chance
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.99,0:10:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小兔崽子 刚在巧克力糖的包装袋里拉了屎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that little son of a gun has just pooped inside of a Butterfinger wrapper.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.83,0:10:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人见过他这么干 但有人吃到过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one ever saw him do it, but a couple people ate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.29,0:10:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二 如果老师告诉霸凌者别欺负人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Number two, if the teacher tells the bully not to pick on someone,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.50,0:10:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只会让情况更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's just gonna make it worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.92,0:10:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 你什么都不打算做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you're not gonna do anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.21,0:10:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.22,0:10:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛刺激他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why you winding him up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.14,0:10:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是关键 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's the one, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.26,0:10:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们要在这里干成事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we're gonna make an impact here,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.39,0:10:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一张倒下的多米诺骨牌 就在他的心里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the first domino that needs to fall is right inside that man's heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:10:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.03,0:11:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 我能问你件事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Jamie, can I ask you something? 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.24,0:11:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是40公斤哑铃 我要做三组 每组十个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's 40 kilos. I do three sets of ten.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.33,0:11:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在肱二头肌和三角肌之间切换\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then I alternate between bis and tris.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.87,0:11:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不关心你举什么 小白脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't give a shit what you lift, you little pretty boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.54,0:11:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你关心 因为你问了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, you do, 'cause you asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.21,0:11:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能举起40公斤哑铃吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you curl 40 kilos?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.63,0:11:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能 但我能把你的蛋蛋当吊球用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, but I can use your balls as a speed bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.59,0:11:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想试试吗 -不是特别想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Do you wanna try that? -Not especially.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.43,0:11:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你在球队里扮演什么角色吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you even understand the influence you have on this team?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.64,0:11:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是最好的 我知道 -不 你是个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm the shit, yeah. -No, you're a bellend.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.56,0:11:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但因为你有踢球的天赋 大家都很尊重你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But because your right foot was kissed by God the boys look up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.14,0:11:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让我质疑我的信念\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's made me question my own faith.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.19,0:11:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 当他们欺负内特时…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, when they pick on Nate...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.15,0:11:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在笑…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you laugh...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.82,0:11:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.90,0:11:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…他们认为这没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...they think it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.53,0:11:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 因为内特是个弱鸡 他什么都做不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, 'cause Nate's a weak baby and he can't do anything about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.24,0:11:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我会解决的 内特是个好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, all right. I'll take care of it. Nate's a good lad.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.16,0:11:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.67,0:11:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 罗伊 你今晚来俱乐部吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Roy. You comin' to the club tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.00,0:11:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 你会去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on, will you be there?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.29,0:11:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然了 兄弟 -那我去个屁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Of course, bruv. -Then fuck no.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.92,0:11:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科林 艾萨克 过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Colin, Isaac, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.05,0:12:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩平时总戏弄内特 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know how you two are always messing with Nate?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.93,0:12:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.76,0:12:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续 我觉得很好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep it up. Makes me laugh.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.27,0:12:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好 希金斯 -早上好 我只是在…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good morning, Higgins. -Good morning. I was just--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.44,0:12:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等在门口 好让我知道你准时上班了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Waiting at the entrance so I'd see you were here on time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.99,0:12:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 你似乎心情不错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Exactly. You seem in good spirits.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.32,0:12:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我刚刚意识到一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I am. I've just realized something.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.99,0:12:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张照片就算不能登出来又怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who cares if we can't run that picture?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.99,0:12:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更大的问题是本地社区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bigger issue is that the local community
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.95,0:12:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力挺球队 不管他们踢得有多烂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is getting behind the team no matter how badly they play.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.54,0:12:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉丝基础非常牢固\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is an outstanding fan base.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.46,0:12:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我相信我有能力将其毁掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, one I believe I can put an end to.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.09,0:12:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hooray.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.88,0:12:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.17,0:12:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我回来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. I'll go back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.22,0:12:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-今日份 -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Here you go. -Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.35,0:12:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟《太阳报》的老板谈过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I spoke to the owner of The Sun.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.64,0:12:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟上帝谈了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You spoke to God?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.47,0:12:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是太阳 是《太阳报》 -哦 对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No, the newspaper. -Oh, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.93,0:12:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他同意不刊登你和基莉那张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he has agreed to not run the photo of you and Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.15,0:13:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最有价值球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}MVP! MVP! MVP!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.23,0:13:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-左腿右腿 加把劲 -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Left leg! Right leg, not as good! -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.49,0:13:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了 -好啦 谢谢 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah! -Yes. Okay, thank you, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.15,0:13:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你说到哪了请继续\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. Yeah, no. You were saying. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.91,0:13:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In exchange,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.99,0:13:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同意让他的另一家 更有名气的报社《独立报》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've agreed for his more reputable newspaper, The Independent,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.45,0:13:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你做个专访\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to do a profile on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.04,0:13:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《和拉索教练面对面》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"One-on-One with Coach Lasso."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.41,0:13:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.58,0:13:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记者是特伦特克里姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The writer will be Trent Crimm.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.21,0:13:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他非常优秀 支持者们都对他马首是瞻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he's very good, and the supporters really listen to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.30,0:13:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我知道特伦特 他是一块难啃的饼干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no. I know Trent, yeah. He's a tough cookie.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.76,0:13:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗 -是的 但是没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Really? -Yeah, but that's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.05,0:13:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道要怎么对付 这种硬邦邦的饼干 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what you do with tough cookies, don't ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.64,0:13:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知道 -泡在牛奶里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. -Dip 'em in milk.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.39,0:13:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们试一下新战术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's run that new one.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.48,0:13:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, there he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.90,0:13:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 来自美国的泰德拉索教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, Coach Ted Lasso from America.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.94,0:13:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 《独立报》的特伦特克里姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, Trent Crimm from The Independent.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.36,0:13:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 很高兴和你共度一天 一定会很有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, excited to spend the day with ya. Gonna be fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.40,0:13:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我泰德就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And please, call me Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.78,0:13:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.87,0:13:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人防守\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wide open.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.04,0:13:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了 -进球了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah! -Snuck it by him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.46,0:14:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 山姆 感觉如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thataway, Sammy. How'd that feel?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.05,0:14:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好极了 教练 我从头到脚都震颤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, wonderful, Coach. I felt that one in my penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.76,0:14:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 这听上去很对 很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. No, that sounds about right. That's good. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.72,0:14:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 杰米 你的动作要更有迷惑性 宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Jamie, you gotta sell that run-through hard, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.31,0:14:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗过对方的防守队员 看好了 像这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make the defense believe you. Watch, like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.06,0:14:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球球传给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ball! Ball! Give me the ball!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.68,0:14:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我球传给我我想要球 求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want the ball! Give me the ball! I would like the ball, please!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.60,0:14:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make it a performance.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.69,0:14:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你在明年的ESPY 颁奖礼上拿奥斯卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you winning an Oscar at the ESPYs next year.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.02,0:14:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我当诱饵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want me to run decoy?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.44,0:14:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.48,0:14:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.94,0:14:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜的是 没人觉得这笑话好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unfortunately for you, though, no one thinks it's funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.53,0:14:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That true?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.91,0:14:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求同存异吧 我认为很好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agree to disagree. I find it hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.24,0:14:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得比《非亲兄弟》还好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought it was funnier than Step Brothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.62,0:14:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个评价很高哦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}High praise.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.00,0:14:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双层床塌掉的那个镜头…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That scene where the bunk bed collapses...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.21,0:14:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以为那是我看过的最好笑的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I used to think that was the funniest thing I'd ever seen,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.54,0:14:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今天我看到了这一幕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but then I just saw that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.63,0:14:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我得将我的搞笑排行榜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And now I'm gonna have to rethink my order of what I think is
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.71,0:14:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新排序了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the funniest thing I've ever seen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.92,0:14:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 据我所知 这叫体育和艺术结合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's when sports and art combine, as far as I'm concerned.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.30,0:14:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们 再来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, fellas, let's run it again. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.18,0:14:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cheers.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.47,0:14:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们懂了 他们明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, they're getting it. They're getting it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.26,0:14:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣的策略 泰德 是你想出来的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Interesting play, Ted. Did you come up with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.47,0:14:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.56,0:14:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们伟大的内特炮制出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is all cooked up by our very own Nate the Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.35,0:15:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“伟大的内特”是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who's "Nate the Great"?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.44,0:15:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在那儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah. There he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.15,0:15:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在这里遛狗 又发现一坨狗屎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone's been walking their dog here. Found another poo.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.32,0:15:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.11,0:15:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“伟大的内特”是做什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What exactly does "Nate the Great" do?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.49,0:15:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太确定他的头衔是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not exactly sure what his title is.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.99,0:15:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 教练 内特负责什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Coach. What is Nate's job around here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.66,0:15:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-打杂的 -好的 打杂的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Kit man. -There you go. Kit man.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.54,0:15:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说你们把一个英超联赛球队 的进攻战术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you mean to tell me you're entrusting a Premier League team's attack
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.54,0:15:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交到一个打杂的手里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the kit man?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.58,0:15:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个年轻人对足球的理解远在我之上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That young fellow's forgotten more about this sport than I'll ever know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.21,0:15:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天 他也许是个天才\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Heck, might be a genius.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.42,0:15:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么要补充的吗 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything to add, Coach?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.76,0:15:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.34,0:15:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, oh boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.43,0:15:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你了解彼尔德教练 你就知道这句评价的分量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you knew Coach Beard, you'd know what a big deal that was.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.30,0:15:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是认真的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You mean that, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.06,0:15:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的报道有了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, hell. There's your story right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.64,0:15:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,标题什么的全部搞定 “他点头了”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got a headline and everything. "Man Nods Head."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.73,0:15:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心了 盖伊泰勒斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Watch your back, Gay Talese.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.94,0:15:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫特伦特克里姆的记者 将要敲出一篇标志性新专访\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a new iconic profile about to be typed up by one Trent Crimm.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.07,0:15:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打起精神来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tighten up those lines!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.28,0:15:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们知道 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let 'em know, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.78,0:15:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.99,0:15:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿条毛巾来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get a towel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.07,0:15:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊 不要 -拿条毛巾来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Oh, God. No, no, no. -Get a towel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.08,0:15:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放开我 求你了 天啊 不要 -喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Let go. Please, God. Stop it. No. -Oi, oi!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.12,0:16:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the fuck are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.42,0:16:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米没跟你们讲别招惹他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie not talk to you about leaving him alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.17,0:16:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck's sake.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.97,0:16:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看上去像是忘了什么东西 -嗨 基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You look like you've forgotten something. -Hi, Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.18,0:16:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在找你那个混蛋男友 你的眼光可真是够差的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm looking for your prick boyfriend. You know how to pick 'em, don't ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.02,0:16:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的前女友不是偷了你的劳力士 拿去卖钱买毒品了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Didn't your last girlfriend steal your Rolex and sell it for drug money?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.90,0:16:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢我不需要手机也不需要手表\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So? I don't need a phone and a watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.28,0:16:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我没想给你男友当保姆 好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I didn't sign up to be your boyfriend's minder, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.95,0:16:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是新教练让我觉得自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the new gaffer's trying to make me feel responsible
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.87,0:16:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对该死的内特负有责任 我甚至连他姓什么都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for fucking Nate, whose last name I don't even know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.45,0:16:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他姓巴恩斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Barnes.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.70,0:16:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是谢利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. It's Shelley.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.83,0:16:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.92,0:16:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢被当猴耍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't like being tricked.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.29,0:16:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是你 还是那个“牛仔们好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not by you and not by, "Howdy y'all, cowboys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.21,0:16:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泰德拉索 来自堪萨斯”的家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My name is Ted Lasso and I'm from Kansas."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.51,0:16:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 你实在是太不擅长模仿了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow, you're, like, really, really bad at impressions, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.26,0:17:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他在激我 但我不会被牵着鼻子走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know he's trying to push my buttons, but I cannot be manipulated.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.31,0:17:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧 如果我愿意 我现在就能刺激你 全身上下所有的敏感点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. I could push all of your buttons right now if I wanted to.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.39,0:17:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不 不行 基莉… -事实上 我可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No, you couldn't, Keeley-- -I think, actually, I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.35,0:17:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不能 基莉…不 基莉 -你说什么我听不到你说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You couldn't, Keeley-- No, Keeley. -What was that? I can't seem to hear you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.61,0:17:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-基莉 你能不能听我说… -我听着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Keeley, if you would listen to me-- -I'm trying to listen to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.82,0:17:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我可以告诉你为什么… -告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I could tell you why-- -So tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.03,0:17:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会让你生气吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that making you mad?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.61,0:17:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.57,0:17:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.70,0:17:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“我是罗伊肯特 别人付钱找我打比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"I'm Roy Kent and I get paid to play a game,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.17,0:17:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我总是很生气”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I'm mad all the time."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.17,0:17:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实挺像的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's actually pretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.81,0:17:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 特伦特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Trent.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.14,0:17:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道你让我想起谁了吗 -不知道 谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You know who you remind me of right now? -No. Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.48,0:17:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种机器人吸尘器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One of them robot vacuums.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.98,0:17:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处晃悠寻找脏东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just kinda wandering around looking for dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.90,0:17:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-伦巴扫地机器人 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Roomba. -That's the one.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.28,0:17:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 我有个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, I have a question.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.90,0:17:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你们惨败给水晶宫队之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After your resounding loss to Crystal Palace,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.95,0:18:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的一个球员说 你们在更衣室举行了派对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one of your players said there was a party in the locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.78,0:18:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得在失败后开派对 是传达了一个正确的信息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you feel it sends the right message having a party after a loss?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.96,0:18:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特伦特 我自己从来不会 过多地纠结输赢这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Trent, I've never really concerned myself too much with wins and losses.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.46,0:18:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这句我要引用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now that's a quote I'll probably use.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.59,0:18:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You should get going.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.21,0:18:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告诉罗伊我们很快就走了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, will you let Roy know we're heading out soon?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.96,0:18:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-收到 -谢谢 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Copy. -Thanks, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.30,0:18:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要跟我们一起吗 我们要去找一些学生谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna tag along? We're gonna go speak to some schoolkids.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.55,0:18:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是巧啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, what a coincidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.14,0:18:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们采访当天 你刚好刚去参观一家本地学校\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The day of our interview you just happen to be visiting a local school.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.35,0:18:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就叫无巧不成书 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, that's the funny thing about coincidences, ain't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.52,0:18:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候就是这么巧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sometimes they just happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.73,0:18:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.73,0:18:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.65,0:18:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想来再次感谢你 阻止那张照片的刊登\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted to come and thank you again for stopping that picture from running.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.57,0:18:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你带了礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I bought you a present.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.28,0:18:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它让我想到了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Made me think of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.37,0:18:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很强大 但有一点不好接近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's strong and a bit prickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.25,0:18:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定不再害怕你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I've decided to not be scared of you anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.71,0:18:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你怕过我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't know you were.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.92,0:18:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我都要吓死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I was, like, fucking terrified of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.96,0:18:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 要是记者搅和我们感情的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My God, Jamie would have been so pissed off
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.76,0:19:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米会气疯的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with reporters poking around in our love life.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.09,0:19:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道为什么要跟你说这些 你肯定深有感触 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know why I'm telling you. You know all about that, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.56,0:19:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得你离婚的时候吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Remember when you got divorced?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.56,0:19:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It rings a bell.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.77,0:19:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会觉得很气愤吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I mean, didn't it, like, make you really mad
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.77,0:19:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都针对你 而不是鲁伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that they went after you and not Rupert?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.52,0:19:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明出轨的人是他 他却成了大家眼中的“白马王子”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause he was the one that cheated and he came across like Prince Charming.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.23,0:19:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让我非常生气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It really pissed me off.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.44,0:19:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媒体总是对男人网开一面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, the press are never awful to men.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.45,0:19:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人会为一张在马略卡岛 游艇上的裸体男人照片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one ever pays a fortune for a photo of a naked man on a yacht in Mallorca
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.70,0:19:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而支付一大笔封口费\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a week after his divorce.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.99,0:19:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个场景太具体了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's like a very specific scenario.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.33,0:19:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪 有人拍到了你在游艇上的裸照\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. That means there's a picture of you naked on a yacht.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.04,0:19:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看看吗在这儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I see it? Is it here?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.08,0:19:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 你要是不想给别人看 根本就不会提\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. You wouldn't have said something if you weren't dying to show someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.88,0:19:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.01,0:19:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从直升机上拍的 我当时在享受日光浴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was taken from a helicopter while I was sunbathing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.05,0:19:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的老天 瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Holy shit, Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.68,0:19:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的胸部长这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are those your real tits?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.14,0:19:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉像是十几岁的男孩子 我忍不住要盯着看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I feel like a teenage boy. I can't stop staring at them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.60,0:19:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从哪弄的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where did you get those?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.44,0:19:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My mum.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.60,0:19:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你拦下了这张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't believe you stopped this from running.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.44,0:19:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话 我一定会拿给所有人看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would have shown everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.82,0:19:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我得继续工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. I really need to get on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.49,0:19:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 给\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, sorry. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.24,0:20:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.91,0:20:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.70,0:20:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鞋忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.54,0:20:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鞋 对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shoes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.71,0:20:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 你那美丽的胸部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow, you really blew my brains out
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.29,0:20:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的让我大开眼界 瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with those beautiful breasts of yours, Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.52,0:20:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次见到我们学校的足球队时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I first saw our school football squad,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.60,0:20:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认为里士满小学会赢下一场比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't think that Richmond Primary would win a single game,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.40,0:20:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是会赢得联赛冠军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}much less the league championship.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.66,0:20:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了表示庆祝 有请AFC里士满的新任经理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To celebrate, please welcome the new manager of AFC Richmond,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.29,0:20:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ed Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.29,0:20:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 非常感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. I appreciate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.88,0:21:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 嘿 大家伙 你们好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Hey, gang. How y'all doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.17,0:21:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-傻屌 -雅各布\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Wanker. -Jacob.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.76,0:21:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.47,0:21:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我只是想过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I just wanted to come down
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.89,0:21:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你们走过了一个精彩的赛季\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and congratulate y'all on a heck of a season.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.10,0:21:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我知道还有一个人特别想跟大家见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But hey, I know someone else who's really excited to meet all of ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.35,0:21:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请跟我一起欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So if you please help me welcome
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.02,0:21:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,AFC里士满足球队的队长 罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the captain of your AFC Richmond squad, Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.40,0:21:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy! Roy! Roy! Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.78,0:21:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.49,0:21:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向来对公开演讲和学校都不是很感冒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Never been much for public speaking or school, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.79,0:21:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我看来就是浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Always seemed like a waste of time to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.00,0:21:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们离开这个闷热的体育馆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't we get out of this stuffy auditorium,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.34,0:21:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去足球场上好好地活动一下怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}go out on the pitch and have a proper fuck-about?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.06,0:21:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你这么做很酷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's really cool you do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.90,0:21:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么做只是因为 我该死的侄女在这儿念书\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only doing it 'cause my fucking niece goes here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.02,0:22:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗哪个是她 -那个笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Oh, yeah? Which one is she? -That idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.28,0:22:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 她来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh boy, here she comes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.28,0:22:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能玩头球吗 罗伊叔叔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can we do headers, Uncle Roy?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.70,0:22:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 过来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, all right. Come on then.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.12,0:22:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 跟我来 排好队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Come on, you lot. Line up.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.87,0:22:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头球 漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Heads. Lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.83,0:22:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 接着 完美\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next. Go. Perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.62,0:22:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 头球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next. Heads.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.84,0:22:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.38,0:22:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好 下一个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well done. Next.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.22,0:22:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next. Sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.97,0:22:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了 我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lovely. I liked it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.93,0:22:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很好 -罗伊 这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good. -Roy, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.27,0:22:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去那边 给他们示范下 这里交给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You hop in there, show 'em how it's done. I'll do a couple.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.14,0:22:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗准备好了吗来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How you doing? Ready? Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.52,0:22:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒 过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the spot. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.11,0:22:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到你了 菲比 让我们看看你的本事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go, Phoebe. Let's see what you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.32,0:22:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接得好 我们可能找到了一个守门员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, nice catch. We might have ourselves a goalie.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.24,0:22:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 你踢得真准\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, oh boy. That was right in the button.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.78,0:22:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好 菲比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good job, Phoebe.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.79,0:22:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.50,0:22:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉弄上血迹了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry about the blood there.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.42,0:23:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别拿去克隆我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't use it to clone me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.84,0:23:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴认识你 保重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice meeting you. Take care now.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.26,0:23:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种活动还没有人待过这么久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the longest anyone's ever stayed for something like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.84,0:23:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你邀请我们 -再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, thanks for having us. -Cheers.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.68,0:23:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次表示感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks again.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.01,0:23:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊 大获成功\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy, that was a blast.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.26,0:23:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你讲 你的侄女真可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I tell you what, that niece of yours is a real cutie patootie.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.81,0:23:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了 我受够了你的心理游戏 和你那些破礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Enough. I've had it with your mind games and your stupid gifts.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.98,0:23:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要送我《时间的皱折》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, what even is A Wrinkle in Time?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.48,0:23:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是一本很好的小说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a lovely novel.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.19,0:23:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲的是一个年轻女孩穿越时空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the story of a young girl's struggle with the burden of leadership
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.32,0:23:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为领袖的重担困扰不已的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as she journeys through space.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.61,0:23:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. That's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.20,0:23:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我是那个小女孩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I supposed to be the little girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd like you to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.37,0:23:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这些都不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. None of this matters.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.25,0:23:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我要和这镇子上所有人一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I'm just doing what everyone in this town is doing,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.46,0:23:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数着日子直到你离开为止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'm counting down the days until you're gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.46,0:23:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特伦特 你是个混蛋 一直都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trent, you're a colossal prick. You always have been.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.26,0:23:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲比 走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Phoebe, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.60,0:23:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你饿了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you hungry?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.01,0:23:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是传统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Little tradition.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.48,0:24:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战斗开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let battle commence.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.52,0:24:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted Lasso?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.81,0:24:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨 奥利 -真没想到 你在这干吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey there, Ollie. -Leave it out. What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.27,0:24:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你邀请我的 还记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I mean, you invited me, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.82,0:24:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我邀请所有坐过我车的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I invite every person who's been in my car.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.90,0:24:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 奥利 这是我朋友特伦特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Ollie. This is my friend Trent.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.45,0:24:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-特伦特 这是我兄弟奥利 -很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Trent, this is my buddy Ollie. -Pleased to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.57,0:24:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜 你们都认识了一个很酷的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Congrats. You both just met a cool person.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.33,0:24:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 两位 你们想吃点什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, gentlemen. You know what you're having?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.62,0:24:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主厨推荐什么我们就吃什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Well, you know, whatever the chef recommends.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.58,0:24:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我岳父 你们能吃一点辣吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That would be my father-in-law. Are you okay with a little bit of spice?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.13,0:24:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当我们是自家人的做法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have him make it for us like we're a couple members of the family.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.05,0:24:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇气可嘉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a brave man.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.13,0:24:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天 太佩服了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, man. Mad respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.09,0:24:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个决定可能不太明智\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That might not be the wisest of choices.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.72,0:24:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go, boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.89,0:24:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-尝尝吧 -等不及了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Dig in. -Can't wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.23,0:24:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这味道已经印在我脑子里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The smell's already deep inside my brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.39,0:24:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你会喜欢的 -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Gonna love it. -I appreciate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.02,0:24:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法想象堪萨斯有地道的印度料理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't imagine they have good Indian food in Kansas.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.82,0:24:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 我从没吃过印度料理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have no idea. I've never had Indian food.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.12,0:25:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 真挺辣的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow, that-- I mean, that's hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.79,0:25:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天 我感觉自己要喷火了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy. Feel like I'm about to breathe fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.84,0:25:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我吃不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think I can eat that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.80,0:25:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么别啊 我们得多吃点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? No, no, no. Come on now. We gotta put a decent dent in this,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.09,0:25:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然奥利要在他家人面前丢脸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}otherwise we're gonna embarrass Ollie in front of his family.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.93,0:25:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不行 我真的吃不下 -这样吧 都倒进我盘子里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No, really, I can't. -Come on, just dump it on my plate.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.02,0:25:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah. You're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.73,0:25:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你这么爱堪萨斯 为什么要…\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, if you love Kansas so much, why did you--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.10,0:25:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要离开家乡训练一种你几乎 一无所知的运动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why did you leave to coach a sport you can barely-- you know anything about?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.28,0:25:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了钱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Was it just the money?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.86,0:25:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 这工作还有工资\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait, I'm supposed to be getting paid?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.65,0:25:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物好吃吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you enjoying the food?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.28,0:25:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你岳父好吃极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell your father-in-law it's perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.66,0:25:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸他说好吃极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad! He says it's perfect!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.04,0:25:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 你在做的事非常不负责任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted. What you're doing is irresponsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.25,0:25:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个俱乐部对这里的人而言意义重大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This club actually means something to this town.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.83,0:25:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.96,0:25:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.59,0:25:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特伦特 你热爱什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trent, what do you love?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.22,0:25:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it writing?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.38,0:25:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.30,0:25:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 因为你很擅长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, good, 'cause you're darn good at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.22,0:25:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you. -You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.51,0:26:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呢我喜欢训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me? I love coaching.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.02,0:26:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要再说一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I'm gonna say this again
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.23,0:26:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免得你认为我第一次是口误\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just so you didn't think it was a mistake the first time I said it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.85,0:26:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 成功不在于输赢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For me, success is not about the wins and losses.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.61,0:26:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是在于帮助这些年轻人 成为最好的自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's about helping these young fellas be the best versions of themselves
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.36,0:26:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是在球场内还是球场之外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on and off the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.86,0:26:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事不总是容易的 特伦特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And it ain't always easy, Trent,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.36,0:26:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是伴随着质疑长大同样不容易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but neither is growing up without someone believing in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.70,0:26:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me ask you this.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.87,0:26:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的舌头还在嘴里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is my tongue still in my mouth?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.62,0:26:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我被辣得快出现幻觉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I am about to hallucinate from all the heat here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.04,0:26:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I really should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.17,0:26:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要截稿了 -好的 工作还是要做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Deadlines and all. -Hey, gotta do the work.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.63,0:26:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还是要说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I'll say this though.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.97,0:26:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很开心能跟你相处一段时间 特伦特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I really enjoyed getting to spend this time with you, Trent.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.26,0:26:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是认真的 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You actually mean that, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.89,0:26:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.89,0:26:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.18,0:26:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Thank you. -You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.10,0:26:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.02,0:26:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常盘子里都会剩很多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Normally, one dish is plenty,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.11,0:26:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们知道你们美国人很能吃 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we know how you Americans like to eat, innit?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.40,0:26:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大吃一顿 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's do it, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.44,0:26:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Try that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.37,0:27:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很美味 对吧 -岂止是美味 超辣的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Beautiful, right? -It's beyond beautiful. It's hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.83,0:27:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“威奇夫人的声音变得沉重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Mrs. Which's voice was grave.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.67,0:27:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,‘你明白什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'What do you understand?'
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.05,0:27:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'That it has to be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.30,0:27:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能是其他任何人’”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't be anyone else.'"
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.26,0:27:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.14,0:27:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个词不好 罗伊叔叔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a bad word, Uncle Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.23,0:27:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管好你自己吧 菲比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mind your own business, Phoebe.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.27,0:27:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be good.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.32,0:27:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（猪头）
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.78,0:27:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么事 -我拿到了报道的样稿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes? -I have an advance copy of the article.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.58,0:27:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-读给我听 -题目是《倔强的泰德》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Read it to me. -Title: "Wayward Ted."
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.33,0:27:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“不论你们如何看待 作为足球教练的泰德拉索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Whatever you think of Ted Lasso as a football coach,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.50,0:27:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你们保证 真相更加令人难以接受”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I assure you, the truth is harder to swallow."
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.30,0:27:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 你好吗 -很好 你的鼻子怎么了 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, how you doing? -Good. How's your nose, Coach?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.09,0:28:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事 谢谢关心 -“但你必须接受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's fine. Thank you for asking. -"And swallow you must,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.34,0:28:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为泰德已经在这里安营扎寨了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because Ted is out there in the community
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.14,0:28:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是勇敢地接纳还是愚蠢地抗拒”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}either bravely or stupidly facing the music."
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.93,0:28:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 你们好吗 -“由你们自己决定”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, fellas. How you doing? -"That's for you to decide."
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.10,0:28:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开 傻屌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Piss off, wanker!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.81,0:28:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨 -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hi. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.48,0:28:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你干嘛 -每次都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Stop it. -Every time.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.11,0:28:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“没错 他的确没有准备好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"And yes, he's in over his head.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.49,0:28:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他强调了两次他不在乎里士满是输是赢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He insisted twice that he didn't care if Richmond won or lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.78,0:28:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果拉索的方法是错的 那很难想象什么是对的”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if the Lasso way is wrong, it's hard to imagine being right."
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.79,0:28:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不读了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why have you stopped reading?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.29,0:28:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你一定要记住这些不是我说的 是特伦特克里姆的原话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please do me the favor of remembering that these aren't my words, it's Trent Crimm.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.05,0:28:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续读\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep going.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.26,0:28:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-“在这里推崇自我的行业 -…推崇自我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"In a business that celebrates ego, -...celebrates ego,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.59,0:28:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-泰德却很谦逊” -泰德却很谦逊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ted reins his in." -Ted reins his in.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.05,0:28:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的训练风格很温柔 从不会对你大声斥责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His coaching style is subtle. It never hits you over the head.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.56,0:28:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 罗伊 我不知道这是个退休派对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, Roy. I didn't know it was a retirement party.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.81,0:28:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.31,0:28:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再招惹内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop messing with Nate!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.32,0:28:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我刚才撞了谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I don't know which one of you I nutted,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.86,0:29:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为光线太暗了 我看不清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause I don't see so well at night anymore,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.32,0:29:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这句话是说给你们所有人听的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but that goes for all of you!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.15,0:29:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢发展壮大 直到你再也无法忽视他的存在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Slowly growing until you can no longer ignore its presence.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.91,0:29:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香草伏特加\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Vanilla vodka.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.29,0:29:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真够幼稚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Such a child.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.66,0:29:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.87,0:29:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.50,0:29:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管那意味着允许追随者成为领袖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whether that means allowing followers to become leaders,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.09,0:29:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是出于礼貌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or in a show of respect, eating food so spicy
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.38,0:29:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃掉肯定会让他 胃里翻江倒海的极辣的食物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's sure to wreak massive havoc on his intestinal system.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.64,0:29:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keys, keys, keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.01,0:29:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 找到了 憋不住了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, here we go. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.10,0:29:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我相信泰德拉索终会失败\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And though I believe that Ted Lasso will fail here
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.85,0:29:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满会承受降级的尴尬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and Richmond will suffer the embarrassment of relegation,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.02,0:29:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但当那一天到来 我不会拍手称快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't gloat when it happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.03,0:29:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我忍不住要为他加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I can't help but root for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.70,0:29:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck!
