[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.80,0:00:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.47,0:00:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(脏-干净)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.36,0:00:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who the hell are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.53,0:00:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨你好 我叫威尔 我是新来的俱乐部服务员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, hi! Hello. I'm Will. I'm the new clubhouse attendant.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.65,0:00:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你不是 我才是俱乐部服务员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, you're not. I'm the clubhouse attendant.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.91,0:00:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 希金斯 你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Higgins, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.41,0:00:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 这是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, what the fuck's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.57,0:00:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 我在努力搞清楚状况呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. I'm trying to figure it out myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.28,0:00:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-搞清楚什么状况我被开除了吗 -他被开除了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Figure what out? Have I been sacked? -Has he been fired?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.41,0:00:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都不知道 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything about this, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在这啊 -你在这啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-There you are. -There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.08,0:00:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是因为我叫艾萨克弱鸡了吗 -我不知道...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Is this because I called Isaac a pussy? -I don't know--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good morning, everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.04,0:00:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个坏女人 是你干的 对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You shrew. You did this, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.63,0:00:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内森 干嘛这么凶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why so hostile, Nathan?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.13,0:00:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我来告诉你为什么...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, I'll tell you why--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.92,0:00:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know my name?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.01,0:00:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟你签合同 当然不能写错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I had to spell it correctly for your contract.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.64,0:00:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内特道格 你没有被炒鱿鱼 更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nate-dawg, you haven't been fired. It's worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.89,0:01:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你升职了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've been promoted.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.40,0:01:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nate! Nate! Nate!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.96,0:01:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内森谢利 我把这个哨子授予你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nathan Shelley, I present to you this whistle.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.75,0:01:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它很悲伤 你知道为什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it is sad. Do you know why?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.34,0:01:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知道 -因为它从来没有被人吹响过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. -Because it has never been blown.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.92,0:01:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科林悲伤也是因为没被“吹”过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that the same reason why Colin's sad?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.60,0:01:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭借里士满足球俱乐部注入我的能量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By the power vested in me by the Associative Football Club of Richmond,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.97,0:01:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在宣布你正式成为内特教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I now pronounce you Coach Nate.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.64,0:01:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks a lot. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.56,0:01:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不别在室内吹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no! Not inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.19,0:01:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.34,0:02:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点搞晕了 这里的人不说“股藓”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It got confusing, 'cause they don't call it jock itch here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.67,0:02:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你不知道该买哪种喷剂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you didn't know what spray to buy?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.22,0:02:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 -那你买了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Yeah. What'd you go with?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.72,0:02:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肌肉先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr Muscle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.18,0:02:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.39,0:02:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不确定你是否知道 但按规定你得选一个新队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not sure if you know this, but the rules say you gotta pick a new captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.60,0:02:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道 按规定你就是我的队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir. You're my captain. That's the rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.31,0:02:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 按规定队长必须得上场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. The captain has to be on the pitch. That's the rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.28,0:02:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是现队长需要挑选一名新队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I say that the current captain has to pick the new captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.32,0:02:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的新规定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's my new rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.91,0:02:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.28,0:02:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, you have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.74,0:02:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我拒绝 -我坚持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I decline. -I insist.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.58,0:02:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能逼我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't make me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.21,0:02:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特 在你选好继任者之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent, until you choose your successor,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.84,0:02:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你作为队长的职责仍未履行完毕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your duties as captain of this squad remain unfulfilled.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.59,0:03:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要爱你很难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is why it's hard to love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.93,0:03:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You heard it, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.60,0:03:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He loves you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.89,0:03:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 各位 我有一个消息要宣布\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, gang. Here's the unskinny bop.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.14,0:03:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城要来我们的主场踢决赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Manchester City is coming into our house for the final match,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.48,0:03:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们要把这当作一场普通比赛来做准备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but preparation-wise, we gonna treat it like it's any other game.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.32,0:03:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是普通的比赛 我们可能会降级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it's not just any other game. We could get relegated.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.03,0:03:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在卡迪夫俱乐部的时候我们就被降级了 我们一家人都是粉丝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got relegated when I was at Cardiff. It's my family's team.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.07,0:03:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后我奶奶再也没理过我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My nana never spoke to me after that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.87,0:03:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是在遗嘱里给我留了一盒屎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She just left me a box of her shit in her will.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.62,0:03:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 如果俱乐部完了 那球队也散了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, and when clubs go down, teams get broken up.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.87,0:03:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你们美国没有降级一说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, do they not have relegation in America?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.33,0:03:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.75,0:03:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那赛季结束的时候那些烂队会怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what happens to all the shit teams at the end of the season?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.96,0:03:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们继续踢完余下的赛程\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They play out the rest of the schedule,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.67,0:03:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在半死不活的、只有一半观众的体育馆里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}going through the motions in meaningless games
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.84,0:03:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无波澜地进行无意义的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}contested in lifeless, half-empty stadiums,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.97,0:03:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人对此也欣然接受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and everyone's pretty much fine with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.72,0:03:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说得对吗 教练 -对 很蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-That sound about right, Coach? -Yeah, it's dumb.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.97,0:03:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 内特教练...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Now, Coach Nate--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.85,0:03:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.10,0:03:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别 别在这里吹 -室内不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Not-- No, not here. -Not inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.60,0:03:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内特教练想给大家看一段视频\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was saying, now Coach Nate has a video he wants to show.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.23,0:03:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.52,0:03:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我想你们看完 都会觉得充满斗志\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. So, I thought you'd all find this motivational.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.11,0:04:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.03,0:04:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Amigo Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.11,0:04:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然曼城没有好的理发师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clearly no barbers in Manchester.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.33,0:04:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不会说我的老东家一句坏话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I'd never say a bad word about me old club...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管每次比赛都是我带动全场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even though I did carry them through every match.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.00,0:04:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们都是好人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But they're good lads.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.63,0:04:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了罗伊肯特 他是个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apart from Roy Kent. He is a knob.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.25,0:04:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很开心有了一个像佩普这样靠谱的教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, and it's nice to have a real manager like Pep,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.09,0:04:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是那个美国牛仔小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}instead of that American rodeo clown.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.63,0:04:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当初是拉索把我弄走的 现在他们面临降级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, Lasso sent me away, now they're facing the drop.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.93,0:04:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周日 我会让这一切成为定局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sunday, I get to put the final nail in the ashes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.35,0:04:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是现世报 等着吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Instant karma, it's gonna get ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.44,0:04:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oops, innit?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.52,0:04:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说得好 -好了 我们去迎接挑战吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well said. All right, let's go climb that mountain!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.32,0:04:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 如果英超联赛是最好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, so if the Premier League is the best,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.36,0:04:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那下面一级的联赛叫什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then what's the league called right below it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.61,0:04:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冠军联赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Championship.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.20,0:04:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 也就是说 如果你是英超联赛的最后一名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, hold on one second. So if you come in last place in the Premier League,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.49,0:04:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就要去踢冠军联赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you get to play in the Championship?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.16,0:04:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很讽刺吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They also invented irony.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.45,0:04:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天 这地方的人说话太奇怪了 你不觉得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Man, this town has got a weird way with words, don't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.92,0:04:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说 拜托 现在都2020年了 我们就直接说“香烟”好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, come on, y'all. It's 2020. Let's just call 'em cigarettes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.84,0:04:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊 太对了 -你明白我的意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Oh, God, yeah. -You know what I mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.55,0:05:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们好吗 伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. How you doing, fellas?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.42,0:05:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想来道谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just wanted to say thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.72,0:05:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道你已经尽力了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, we know you did your best.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.22,0:05:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你的“尽力”还是很烂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even though your best is still shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.14,0:05:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-巴兹 -噢 拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Baz. -Oh, come on, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.14,0:05:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这个样子好像我们已经输了一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're acting like we lost the game already, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.56,0:05:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不能心存一点希望吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you have a little hope?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.89,0:05:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 你在这里待这么久了 还没明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aw, Ted. Haven't you lived here long enough to realize?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.98,0:05:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望越大失望越大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the hope that kills you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.20,0:05:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给内特发个信息吧 我们今晚有工作要做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you text Nate? We got a little work to do tonight, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.24,0:05:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们能行 我们赢了就能留在联赛里 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, come on. We got this. Look, we win, we're in, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.83,0:05:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水晶宫队曾经以6-0打败了诺里奇队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is a scenario where Crystal Palace beat Norwich by six goals,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.92,0:05:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只要一个平局就能避免降级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we avoid relegation with just a tie.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.75,0:05:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不行 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no. Nope. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.92,0:05:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌平局 内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I hate ties, Nate.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.30,0:05:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟你说多少遍平局很奇怪 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many times I gotta tell you that? They ain't natural, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.67,0:05:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果上帝想要比赛最终以平局结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If God wanted games to end in a tie,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.01,0:05:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一开始就不会发明数字 对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she wouldn't have invented numbers, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.84,0:05:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 伙计们 燃起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, guys. Let's fire up. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.97,0:05:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看在梅根马克尔的份上 不要再吹了 内特 我发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the love of Meghan Markle, do not blow that whistle again, Nate. I swear.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.85,0:05:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抱歉 -我楼上的邻居一听见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sorry. -I got neighbors upstairs,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.23,0:05:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要开始跺地板了 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they will just start stomping away. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.85,0:06:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 告诉我怎么才能打败曼城\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Tell me how we beat Manchester City.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.31,0:06:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们赢不了曼城的 -该死的 内特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-We cannot beat Manchester City. -Dang it, Nate!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.48,0:06:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我想从第一天上任的 助理教练嘴里听到的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is not what I want to hear from my assistant coach on his first day.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.19,0:06:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没戏的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is hopeless.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.20,0:06:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 没戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, I'm sorry. It's hopeless?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.57,0:06:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对 -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.50,0:06:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个小问题 你只有这身衣服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Quick question. Are those the only clothes you own?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.26,0:06:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗不是 我有三件同款的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This? No, I got three of these.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.93,0:06:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(相信)
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.93,0:06:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有印象吗 内特 有没有觉得很眼熟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That ring a bell, Nate? That ring a very large bell in your head?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.02,0:06:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把这个挂在自己家里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You had that hanging in your home?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.64,0:06:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挂了很多 这个是从浴室镜子拿下来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a ton of these hanging up in here. This one's from the bathroom mirror.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.31,0:06:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天早上看见的第一样东西 也是我每天晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the first thing I see every morning, and it's the last thing I see at night
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.19,0:06:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累得不想用牙线时见到的最后一样东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when I rationalize being too tired to floss.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.65,0:06:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信念不能进球 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Belief can't score goals, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.45,0:06:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 丧气鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, hello, Nelson.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.11,0:06:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请容我给你介绍另一位丧气鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me introduce you to another Nelson right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.37,0:06:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩肯定能处得来 因为你们俩都丧得不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think you two will hit it off just fine, 'cause you're both so damn pessimistic!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.16,0:07:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 希普利夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, Ms. Shipley!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.67,0:07:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信这位先生是在暗示 我们俩是一对悲观主义者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I believe the gentleman is suggesting that we are a pair of Negative Nellies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.17,0:07:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.26,0:07:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jackpot.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.84,0:07:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 老板 给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Morning, boss. Here you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.55,0:07:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 我感觉到你今天除了饼干 还带了别的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh. Ted. I sense you're carrying around something today besides biscuits.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.43,0:07:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好眼力 看得准\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good eye, small fry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.40,0:07:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想说这话 瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hate to say it, Rebecca,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.65,0:07:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的俱乐部要是没有足球教练 也许会更好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I think your football club might have been better off with a soccer coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.15,0:07:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话从何说起啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's this coming from?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.36,0:07:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 如果我们周日输了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, if we do end up losing on Sunday,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.57,0:07:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以做任何你认为 对俱乐部的未来最有益的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you just go ahead and do whatever you think is best for the future of this club,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.53,0:07:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.62,0:07:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便那意味着这家伙得...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even if that means this guy's gotta go...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.00,0:07:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,套个绳子一拉 你懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, you put that thing, and just... You know, whatever you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.33,0:07:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你怎样都行 我是说 别真的弄死我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever you wanna do. I mean, don't really murder me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.13,0:07:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你知道 就是... 你明白我的意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but, you know, just... All that. You get what I'm getting at?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.92,0:07:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开除我 你懂我的意思 -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fire me. You get the gist. Yeah. -Okay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.67,0:07:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为你不是一个“称职”的足球教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you think you're not a "proper" football manager.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.01,0:07:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来没打过比赛 不懂得规则\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone who's never played the game before, or knows the rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.05,0:07:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我对足球一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I don't know jack diddly about any of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.10,0:07:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但谁在乎呢荷兰足球界有一句名言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But who cares? There's a great saying in Dutch football.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.22,0:07:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会说荷兰语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, I don't speak Dutch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.85,0:08:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要说英文版的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I was going to tell you in English.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.48,0:08:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了 说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Perfect. Lay it on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.85,0:08:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“每个劣势都有其优势”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Every disadvantage has its advantage."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.11,0:08:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ooh, I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.19,0:08:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 你不知道自己在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure, you don't know what you're doing,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.90,0:08:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那也意味着你会有别于其他足球教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but doesn't that mean that you see the game in a different way
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.24,0:08:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一个不同的角度 看待这项运动 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}than any other football manager?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.20,0:08:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你凭借这一点 能造成极大的困扰 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And shouldn't that empower you to cause complete and utter confusion?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.54,0:08:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成困扰或是混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cause confusion or create chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.33,0:08:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是这个 谢了 老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yep. Yes, it is. Thanks, boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.92,0:08:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.01,0:08:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.17,0:08:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混乱已经开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chaos has already begun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.34,0:08:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 先生们 上课了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, gentlemen. School is in session.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.97,0:08:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要学习的是“假动作”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And today's lesson is "trick plays."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.18,0:08:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我们那里是这么叫的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At least, that's what we call 'em back home.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.89,0:08:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们这里叫什么来着 -攻防套路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What do they call 'em here again? -Elaborate set pieces.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.02,0:08:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我们还是叫“假动作”好了 这叫法有意思多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, we gonna stick with "trick plays." That's a lot more fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.40,0:08:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一个假动作背后的思想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, the idea behind every trick play
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.27,0:08:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要制造混乱 把对手搞晕 让他们的反应变慢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is to have chaos rain down upon your opponents and stun them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.61,0:08:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像庞贝古城那些可怜人遭遇岩浆时那样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Much like the lava did to those poor folks in Pompeii.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.28,0:09:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 我要你们想一想 你们整个足球职业生涯中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I want y'all to think about every single trick play you have ever run
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.95,0:09:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用过的每一个假动作 有谁想到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your entire time playing this sport. Anybody got one?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.33,0:09:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 丹尼 你想到了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, Dani, what you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.41,0:09:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为老虎队效力的时候 我们发明了一个伟大的战术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I played for Tigres, we had a great set piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.96,0:09:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有名字吗 -“沙人”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Did it have a name? -"The Sandman."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.54,0:09:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了 开了一个好头 “沙人”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Now we're cooking. "The Sandman."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.71,0:09:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今天就学这个 还有谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna learn that play today. Who else got one?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.47,0:09:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-“胡椒瓶” -“胡椒瓶”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"Pepper Shakers." -"Pepper Shakers"?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.01,0:09:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 复数 那应该是有两个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, plural. Gotta be two.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.43,0:09:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“贝克汉姆的老二”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Beckham's Todger."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.64,0:09:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝克汉姆我知道 老二我不是很懂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Beckham, I know. Todger, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.47,0:09:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是脏话 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-It's dirty. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.14,0:09:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“午夜普丁”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Midnight Poutine."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.31,0:09:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-普丁 -不是脏话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Poutine? -That's not dirty.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.06,0:09:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是加拿大特有的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just super Canadian.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.85,0:09:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-“飞天万能车” -迪克凡戴克主演的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"Chitty Chitty Bang Bang." -Oh, with Dick Van Dyke.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.98,0:09:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,影史上最纯正的英音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The owner of one of the most authentic English accents in the history of cinema.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.82,0:09:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想到了什么 -“坏掉的水龙头”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What do you got? -"The Broken Tap."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.15,0:09:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这不是投诉 真叫这个名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. That's not a complaint, that's an actual play name?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.28,0:09:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城会“漏掉”很多进球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think Man City will leak a lot of goals from it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.28,0:09:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好极了 你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh. Nice. Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.58,0:09:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-“洛基的长雪橇” -“颠倒的出租车”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"Loki's Toboggan." -"The Upside-Down Taxi."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.91,0:09:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-“哈德良城墙” -“脏脏马提尼”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-"Hadrian's Wall." -"Dirty Martini."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.16,0:09:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就能喝三杯 我超爱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, I'd love to run that play three times right now. I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.08,0:09:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我个忙 把“拉索特餐” 加上去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do me a favor and toss "Lasso Special" up there
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.04,0:09:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么特别原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just for the heck of it too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.30,0:09:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们 这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, guys. Tell you right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.96,0:09:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就出去 学一学这些战术 听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we're gonna go out there, and we're gonna learn a bunch of these plays, you hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.01,0:09:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等周日一到 我们就用这个“混乱铁锤” 狠狠地揍扁曼城\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come Sunday, we're gonna hit Man City with the chaos hammer!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.93,0:10:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-耶 -我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah! -Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.73,0:10:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 山姆 不要发蜡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Sam, not wax.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.65,0:10:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -用发油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ah, okay. -Pomade. Pomade.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.77,0:10:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 杰米塔特 是你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yo, Jamie Tartt. It's you, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.90,0:10:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来一个群拍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me get an ussie.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.32,0:10:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.20,0:10:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wicked.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.75,0:10:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你被里士满抛弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't believe you got dumped by Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.87,0:10:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太丢脸了 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Super embarrassing for you, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.37,0:10:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被拉索坑了 所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I got fucked by Lasso. So...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.21,0:10:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他现在喜欢你了 他在电视上经常谈起你 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He likes you now though. He talked about you on telly, didn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.67,0:10:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么 你这个时髦的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you on about, you posh twat?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.84,0:10:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《独立报》的特伦特克里姆 你跟杰米塔特有过节吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trent Crimm, The Independent. Any bad blood between you and Jamie Tartt?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.76,0:10:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米没有 他是一个很特别的年轻人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie? No. That's a special young man right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.22,0:10:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有天赋 很努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got talent for days, works hard,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.10,0:10:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他的下巴 像多佛白崖一样棱角分明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and he's got a jawline like the White Cliffs of Dover.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.60,0:10:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远支持他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm always rootin' for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.02,0:10:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么 -很经典的心理游戏 不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-What? -Classic mind games, innit?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.15,0:10:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得对 你可以滚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. You can fuck off.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.32,0:11:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(嗨 基莉 我来市里了 我能过去跟你聊聊吗)
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.37,0:11:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么国际玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're fucking joking.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.71,0:11:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 对了 罗伊 杰米要来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah, Roy, Jamie's coming over.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.71,0:11:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗要我做司康吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, is he? Shall I make scones?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.26,0:11:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢司康\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't like scones.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.42,0:11:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是真的要做 白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not making scones, you idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.22,0:11:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 因为我真的不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good, 'cause I don't even like 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.51,0:11:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.18,0:11:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你煮了咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I made you coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.77,0:11:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, then, what's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.85,0:11:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你带了咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I brought you coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.61,0:11:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 杰米 你想跟我聊什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Jamie, what was it that you wanted to talk about?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.28,0:11:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要在这老家伙面前说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not gonna say it in front of this dry old shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.07,0:11:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他不会说出去的 对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? He won't say anything. Will you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.37,0:11:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没打中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Missed.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.45,0:11:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德拉索想跟我玩心理游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted Lasso is trying to play fucking mind games with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.87,0:11:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在电视上说我的好话 想扰乱我的思绪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Saying nice shit about me on the telly. Trying to get in my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.71,0:11:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他确实喜欢你 -你跟他一样满嘴谎话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-He does like you. -You're as full of shit as he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.13,0:11:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你给我客气点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi. Mind your fucking manners.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.26,0:11:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 机器警察\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, RoboCop.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.46,0:12:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米 不是你人生中的每一个人 都对你有敌意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie, not everyone in your life is out to get you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.80,0:12:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.22,0:12:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了你不是欣赏诚实吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? Thought you respected honesty.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.72,0:12:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.56,0:12:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, that is disgusting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.19,0:12:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 基莉 等你给这个老家伙 喂完豌豆泥了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Keeley. When you're done feeding mushy peas to this old fart,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.61,0:12:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再打给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then you give me a call.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.78,0:12:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待明天的见面 好好欣赏候补席的风景吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look forward to seeing you tomorrow. Enjoy the view from the bench.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.08,0:12:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.83,0:12:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想吃豌豆泥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, now I want mushy peas.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.25,0:12:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我看你在电视上训练足球的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad, when I see you coach soccer on TV,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.38,0:12:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去你什么都没做啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it doesn't look like you're doing anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.17,0:12:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 因为事实如此 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, it's 'cause I'm not. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.05,0:12:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟在家乡当橄榄球教练不一样 孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It ain't like being a football coach back home, kiddo.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.34,0:12:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能掌控的有限 一旦比赛开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a lot less control, 'cause once the game gets going,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.97,0:12:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没办法告诉我的球员应该做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't tell my fellas what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.60,0:12:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我只能希望我教给他们的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I just gotta hope that everything I've been trying to teach 'em
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.89,0:12:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能或多或少影响到他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}made some sort of impact on 'em,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.43,0:12:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望他们在球场上能做出正确的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that they'll make the right decisions when they're out there on their own.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.69,0:12:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟做爸爸挺像的 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, it's kind of like being a dad, I guess, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.15,0:13:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的话你听进去了多少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much did you get of that before you checked out?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.40,0:13:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我画了一个机器人 -真棒 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I drew a robot. -That's cool, bud.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.07,0:13:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满忠实的球迷齐聚在此 今晚至关重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Richmond faithful gather on a crucial night.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.66,0:13:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们与球队共进退\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Win and they stay up. Lose and they go down.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.04,0:13:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们满怀希望而来 但他们心里也很清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They come here full of hope, but as they know all too well,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.25,0:13:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望越大失望越大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's the hope that kills you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.92,0:13:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这项运动啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, this sport.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.00,0:13:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都忘记了当你真正在意时压力有多大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd forgotten how stressful it is when you actually give a shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.63,0:13:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要向你坦白一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have a confession to make.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.47,0:13:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来就不在意足球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never really cared about football.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.30,0:13:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 这听上去很疯狂 但我知道在比赛时该如何装样子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. I know it sounds insane, but I know how to act at a match.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.89,0:13:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“裁判”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Referee!"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.52,0:13:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“越位了 你这蠢货”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Offside, you turnip!"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.48,0:13:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊 你太可怕了 -你相信我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-God, you're awful. -You believed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.40,0:13:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心思就没放在这上面 你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just that my heart has never really been in it, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.86,0:13:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今天...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But today...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.86,0:13:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天 我非常在意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}today, I care very much.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.28,0:13:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是阿尔洛怀特 我和前英国国际台的克里斯鲍威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Arlo White here, with former England international, Chris Powell,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.91,0:13:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在赛狗场 尼尔森路体育馆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}live from the Dogtrack, Nelson Road Stadium,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.75,0:13:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为您现场报道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the home of AFC Richmond,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.54,0:14:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,AFC里士满主场对战曼城\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who tonight host the mighty Manchester City.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.88,0:14:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢我的新衬衫吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yoo-hoo! You like my new shirt?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.30,0:14:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.59,0:14:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是大卫与巨人歌利亚狭路相逢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's David meets Goliath.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.80,0:14:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是这次大卫忘记给弹弓 装石头了 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If David forgot to put his stone in his slingshot, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.64,0:14:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请客\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These are on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.72,0:14:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 梅\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, Mae.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.18,0:14:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拥抱一个求好运 -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good luck group hug? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.64,0:14:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-敬里士满 -敬里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Richmond. -Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.73,0:14:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们来了 希金斯一家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, here we are. Family Higgins.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.02,0:14:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是泰瑞、克里斯、黛娜、史蒂维\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Terry, Kris, Dana, Stevie.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.40,0:14:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底有多少个孩子啊 希金斯 我的天呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many kids do you have, Higgins? Jesus Christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.66,0:14:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的老大 林赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this is our eldest, Lindsay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.91,0:14:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.70,0:14:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请原谅我 神父\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Forgive me, Father.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.33,0:14:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 他是一个很好的牧师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't worry. He's a cool priest.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.79,0:14:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你的父母婚外生下了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When your parents have you out of wedlock,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.46,0:14:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会给你很多空间去探索人生的灰色区域\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it allows you space to explore life's little gray areas.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.50,0:14:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-加油 里士满 -加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Come on, Richmond! -Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.42,0:14:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满的球迷大声欢呼 克里斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With the Richmond fans in full voice, Chris,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.76,0:14:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更衣室里的球员们 对在降级边缘这件事作何感想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}how do the players in the locker room feel to be on the brink of relegation?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.18,0:14:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,压力非常大 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a tremendous amount of pressure, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.52,0:14:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要想得到预期的结果 他们需要老手的领导\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To get the result they need, it will have to start with veteran leadership.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.52,0:15:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾萨克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Isaac.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.40,0:15:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.65,0:15:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(队长)
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.78,0:15:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砸电视不要停\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Never stop breaking TVs.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.50,0:15:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们 大家注意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, now, fellas. Hey, let's focus up, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.68,0:15:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近总听到你们这里常说的一句话 我个人不太喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I've been hearing this phrase y'all got over here that I ain't too crazy about.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.02,0:15:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“希望越大失望越大”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"It's the hope that kills you."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.69,0:15:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都知道吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Y'all know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.15,0:15:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不赞同\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I disagree, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.99,0:15:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为缺少希望才会导致失望\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's the lack of hope that comes and gets you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.16,0:15:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信希望\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See, I believe in hope.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.91,0:15:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信信念\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I believe in belief.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.79,0:16:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我家乡 我们也有一句俗语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, where I'm from, we got a saying too, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.29,0:16:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 是一个问句\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A question, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.55,0:16:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“你相信奇迹吗”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Do you believe in miracles?"
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.38,0:16:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要你们现在回答我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I don't need y'all to answer that question for me...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.26,0:16:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我希望你们能回答自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I do want you to answer that question for yourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.18,0:16:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就现在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.52,0:16:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信奇迹吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you believe in miracles?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.11,0:16:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你相信...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you do...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.28,0:16:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们现在围过来 快来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then I want y'all to circle up with me right now. Come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.61,0:16:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get 'em in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.28,0:16:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 队长 告诉他们吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Captain. Let 'em know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.00,0:16:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了 队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go, Skipper, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.46,0:16:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长 告诉他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Captain. Let 'em know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.84,0:16:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数到12喊“里士满”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond on 12.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.92,0:16:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一、二、三\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One, two, three,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.34,0:16:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四、五、六\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}four, five, six,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.26,0:17:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七、九、十、十一 、十二\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}seven, nine, ten, eleven, twelve!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.64,0:17:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.48,0:17:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.90,0:17:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.44,0:17:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个奇迹是出自电影还是真实生活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that miracle thing from a movie or real life?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.61,0:17:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Both.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.69,0:17:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在诸多次要情节当中 杰米塔特的回归\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Among the many subplots, the return of Jamie Tartt,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.95,0:17:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在出借期间表现很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who enjoyed a successful loan period here,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.20,0:17:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他跟罗伊肯特曾在球场上动过手 后者并未出现在今日的首发阵容中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but had an infamous on-pitch dustup with Roy Kent, who is not starting today.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.08,0:17:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得 罗伊肯特在哪一次重要赛事坐过冷板凳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I really can't remember seeing Roy Kent on the bench for a big match.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.67,0:17:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 杰米祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Jamie! Good luck!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.25,0:17:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的心理游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fucking mind games.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.05,0:17:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是里士满对阵曼城的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Richmond versus Manchester City.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.76,0:17:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we're off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.18,0:17:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.76,0:17:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亨德里克控球 外侧传给柯文\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hendrick takes. Outside for Corwin.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.97,0:17:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让塔特有了进球的空间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, and he puts Tartt through on goal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.27,0:17:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.64,0:17:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可以传给左侧的队友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He has a man open to his left.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.19,0:17:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他要自己来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But he takes it himself!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.07,0:17:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被佐豪接住了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Zoreaux is there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.36,0:17:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.49,0:17:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐罗稳稳地接住了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a solid save from Zorro.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.57,0:17:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯 是念作“佐豪”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, Chris. It's pronounced "Zoreaux."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.87,0:18:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,30分钟过去了 里士满有一个反攻的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thirty minutes gone. Richmond with an opportunity here on the counterattack.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.66,0:18:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥比桑亚一个精准的长传\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obisanya with an inch-perfect through ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.46,0:18:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温彻斯特明显是越位了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Winchester was clearly offside.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.88,0:18:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, now!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.25,0:18:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你给我解释一下怎么就越位了 -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Explain to me how that's offsides. -What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.30,0:18:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是认真的 那怎么就越位了 我到现在都没搞明白 你...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I'm serious. How is that offside? I don't understand that yet. You--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.34,0:18:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索的助理教练在复盘他们的战术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And here comes Lasso's assistant coach to review their tactics.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.43,0:18:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在憋什么大招\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What chess moves do they have in store?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.18,0:18:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当醋在喜力啤酒旁边时 就不算越位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When the vinegar was next to the Heineken, they weren't offside.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.43,0:18:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是醋接到球的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not when the vinegar catches the ball,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.06,0:18:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是番茄酱传球的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's when ketchup passes the ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.73,0:18:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 我懂了 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes, I understand now. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.10,0:18:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪克森起脚射门...哦 踢过了球门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A shot from Dixon-- Pushed over the bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.61,0:18:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,角球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Corner, corner!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.69,0:18:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪克森很不爽 但里士满赢得了一个角球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agony for Dixon, but a corner for Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.98,0:18:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.28,0:18:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,角球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Corner kick, corner kick.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.82,0:18:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-用“沙人” -什么沙人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Go for the Sandman. Call Sandman. -What? Sandman.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.03,0:18:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙人伙计们 沙人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sandman! Guys, the Sandman!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.95,0:18:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沙人 -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Sandman! -Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.49,0:18:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗哈斯踢角球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rojas to take the corner.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.58,0:18:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个假动作 又一个假动作 这是在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a dummy. Oh, and another one. What is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.79,0:18:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪克森再次射门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dixon again!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.42,0:18:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不哈姆林用脚救下了这一球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! Hamlin saves with his foot.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.25,0:18:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.88,0:18:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 宝贝 “沙人”战术差点把他们绕晕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ooh, baby, the Sandman almost rocked 'em to sleep right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.59,0:18:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-泰德拉索的小把戏 -从来没见过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-A bit of trickery from Ted Lasso. -Haven't seen that one before.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.68,0:19:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一招很漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice move though. Nice move.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.18,0:19:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中场时间 比分是零比零\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that's halftime. The score is 0-0.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.93,0:19:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人意外的是 里士满仍然有胜算\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shockingly, Richmond are still in this,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.52,0:19:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了守门员佐豪的出色表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}thanks to the stellar play of Zoreaux in goal.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.69,0:19:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 你必须...加强进攻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, well, you got-- It's Reynolds.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.40,0:19:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你应该巩固防守 你得...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, you got to shore up your defense. You have to--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.28,0:19:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 别管这些了 我要跟着感觉走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, you know what? Never mind. I'm just gonna go with my gut.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.40,0:19:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁去看一眼水晶宫队的比分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somebody check the Crystal Palace score.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.95,0:19:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 绝对不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, no. No, no, no. Absolutely not.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.62,0:19:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听到有关其他任何地方 进行的其他任何比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want to hear about any other game going on any other place.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.58,0:19:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗我们的目标不是平局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay? Look, we are not playing for a tie.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.29,0:19:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁也别想亲自己的姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ain't nobody here gonna kiss their sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.75,0:19:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.71,0:19:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个美国的谚语 看来你们这里没这说法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which is an American phrase that I'm now realizing does not exist here,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.67,0:19:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是好事 因为这太变态了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that's good, 'cause it's creepy,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.34,0:19:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌自己 我不知道为什么要说出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I hate it myself, I don't know why I said it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.34,0:19:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是肾上腺素的关系 神经太紧张了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's just the adrenaline, the nerves and all that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.64,0:19:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们的目标是赢球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we are playing for a win.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.72,0:19:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要赢 留在联赛 明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Win and in. You hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.93,0:19:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我听不见 你们听明白了吗 -是 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I can't hear your nods. Do you hear me? -Yes, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.43,0:19:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 罗伊 下半场你上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, good. All right. Roy, you are starting the second half.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.02,0:19:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去热热身 我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go ahead and start warming up. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.61,0:19:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生们 跟着我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gentlemen, follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.28,0:20:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And here comes Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.61,0:20:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy-o!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.49,0:20:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索的意外之举\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A surprising move from Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.54,0:20:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城的速度已经让里士满难以招架了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Manchester City's speed is causing Richmond problems,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.91,0:20:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他却让很慢的罗伊肯特上场 说很慢已经是客气了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and he brings on Roy Kent, who is, to be polite, very slow.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.33,0:20:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他是个该死的八旬老人 看看他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's 'cause he's a fucking octogenarian. Look at him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.09,0:20:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城这下有机会了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}City with a real opportunity here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.13,0:20:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙库进入禁区了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Scharfenberg into the box.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.92,0:20:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 里士满被罚点球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, it's a penalty against Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.68,0:20:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么会 -他根本没碰他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-How? How? -He didn't touch him!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.68,0:20:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐豪已就位 亨德里克踢这一球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Zoreaux in position. Hendrick to take.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.23,0:20:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他得分了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He scores.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.44,0:20:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城终于越过了佐豪 比分是1-0\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}City finally get past Zoreaux, and it's 1-0.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.98,0:20:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是命中注定的一球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the goal that's been coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.03,0:20:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城领先 赛狗场陷入一片寂静\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}City take the lead, and the Dogtrack falls silent.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.74,0:20:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是落后一分 还有机会 加油 里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're only one goal down. There's still a chance. Come on, Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.74,0:20:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你在意的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you when you give a shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.24,0:20:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.16,0:20:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米塔特带球反攻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jamie Tartt with the breakaway.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.33,0:20:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他得分了 那里士满就命数已尽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he scores here, it could be curtains for Richmond.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.17,0:20:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人能追上他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one can catch him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.51,0:21:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快啊 罗伊 快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, Roy, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.88,0:21:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你能相信吗是肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on. Can you believe it? It's Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.02,0:21:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶好样的 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah! Attaboy, Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.94,0:21:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy! Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.31,0:21:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次 乌龟追上了兔子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once again, the tortoise has stopped the hare.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.02,0:21:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就该这么干 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how you put him down, Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.86,0:21:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.62,0:21:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's not getting up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.74,0:21:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去情况严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now this looks serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.79,0:21:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一次出色的拦截 但肯特也付出了代价\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a fair tackle on Tartt, but Kent may have paid the price.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.25,0:21:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们派出了医生 -起来 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-And they're sending out the physio. -Get up, Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.33,0:21:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊 你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy. Roy, are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.25,0:21:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死 我伤到了膝盖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fuck. I fucked my knee.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.25,0:21:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要我叫担架来吗 罗伊 -不 扶我起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Want me to call for the stretcher, Roy? -No, just help me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.13,0:21:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特 他在这儿 他在那儿...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent! He's here, he's there...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.22,0:21:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the fuck are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.68,0:21:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...他妈的无处不在 罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...he's every-fucking-where. Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.35,0:21:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.43,0:21:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特他在这儿 他在那儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent! He's here, he's there,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.39,0:21:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的无处不在 罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he's every-fucking-where. Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.94,0:21:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特他在这儿 他在那儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent! He's here, he's there,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.90,0:22:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的无处不在 罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he's every-fucking-where. Roy Kent! Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.40,0:22:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在这儿 他在那儿 他妈的无处不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's here, he's there, he's every-fucking-where.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.24,0:22:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.53,0:22:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们很抱歉现场响起了那首 曾响彻英超联赛赛场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, we apologize for the fruity language as the crowd serenades Roy Kent
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.04,0:22:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长达十余年的带有脏话的歌曲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with a song that's echoed through the Premier League for more than a decade.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.96,0:22:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在这儿 他在那儿 他妈的无处不在...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's here, he's there, he's every-fucking-where...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.46,0:22:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他站起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he's getting up.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.38,0:22:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特绝不会躺在担架上离场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent will never leave on a stretcher.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.13,0:22:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特他在这儿 他在那儿 他妈的无处不在罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent! He's here, he's there, he's every-fucking-where! Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.35,0:22:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.27,0:22:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在这儿 他在那儿 他妈的无处不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's here, he's there, he's every-fucking-where!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.02,0:22:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent! Roy Kent!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.81,0:22:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着肯特走下球场 他向球迷鼓掌表达感激\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As Kent comes off, he claps the fans in gratitude.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.98,0:22:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯特是球迷的最爱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kent has been a fan favorite
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.57,0:22:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他总是毫无保留地将一切留在球场上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because he always left everything he had out on the pitch,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.91,0:22:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚亦是如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and he did so tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.41,0:22:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯 这像不像是最终的告别\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chris, does this almost feel like a farewell to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.67,0:23:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, you have to wonder, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.29,0:23:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他这个年纪 还受了伤...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At his age, with that injury...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.76,0:23:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我个人而言 我很遗憾地说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Personally, I'm sorry to say,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.51,0:23:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也许是我们最后一次看到 伟大的罗伊肯特出现在赛场了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think this may be the last time we ever see the great Roy Kent lace up his boots.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.49,0:23:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛时你不能进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not allowed back here during a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.04,0:23:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了 你得出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you, you have to get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.04,0:23:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是认真的 离我远点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean it. Stay the fuck away from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.45,0:24:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the heck is going on--
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.29,0:24:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是两万六千人同时查看手机的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the sound of 26,000 people checking mobiles.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.33,0:24:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天 水晶宫队6-0赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. Palace won 6-0.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.17,0:24:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那意味着...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But then that means...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.21,0:24:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只要打平就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All we need is a tie.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.59,0:24:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们只要打平就行了 伙计们 -我们只要打平就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-We just need a tie, boys! -We just need a tie!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.43,0:24:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.76,0:24:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 里士满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Richmond!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.10,0:24:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满本赛季只剩下三分钟的加时赛了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Three minutes of added time is all that's left in Richmond's season.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.60,0:24:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙特劳跑向左侧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Montlaur runs left.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.48,0:24:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢被沙库撞倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fouled hard by Scharfenberg.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.15,0:24:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好 理查德演得像一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you go, Richard! You sell the crap outta that!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.32,0:24:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙特劳为里士满赢得了一个任意球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Montlaur earns Richmond a late free kick.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.61,0:24:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他有点夸张了 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he's making a meal of it, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.53,0:24:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城球员也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}City players do too.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.49,0:25:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 克里斯 他是真受伤了 不 他绝对没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Chris. He's definitely hurt. No, no, he's absolutely fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.29,0:25:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.66,0:25:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂拉索特餐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oi! Lasso Special! Lasso Special!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.84,0:25:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Holy smokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.63,0:25:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉索特餐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lasso Special!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.80,0:25:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城正忙着冲裁判喊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Manchester City are more worried about yelling at the official
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.22,0:25:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而没有注意到里士满在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}than they are about... whatever it is Richmond are doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.01,0:25:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-等下 -说真的 他们在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hold on, hold on. -Actually, what are they doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.01,0:25:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裁判他们不能这样你们在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ref! They can't do that! What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.06,0:25:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要用了 我甚至没发话 他们就要用了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're gonna run it. I didn't even call it. They're gonna just run it!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.48,0:25:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道这是什么情况 但看上去...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what's going on here, but it looks like...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.23,0:25:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是美国橄榄球吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is this American football?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.81,0:25:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the fuck is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.48,0:25:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's he doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.57,0:25:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没见过这种阵仗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never seen anything like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.24,0:25:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行动 -进入队列\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Motion! -Get in line!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.45,0:25:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥比桑亚动起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obisanya goes in motion.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.78,0:25:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果里士满想把曼城搞糊涂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If Richmond are trying to confuse Manchester City,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.75,0:25:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不说这招奏效了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you have to say it's working.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.12,0:25:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我也奏效了 阿尔洛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's working on me too, Arlo.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.12,0:25:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-蓝色48 -佐豪在喊数字和颜色吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Blue 48! Is Zoreaux yelling numbers and colors?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.38,0:25:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备动起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hut, hut, hut! Hike!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.92,0:25:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一、二、三、四...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One, two, three, four...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.68,0:25:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里士满球员散开了 曼城的防守陷入混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Richmond players fan out. City's defense is in chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.10,0:26:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个长传给奥比桑亚 他无人防守\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And it's a Hail Mary to Obisanya, who is wide open!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.60,0:26:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左侧只有罗哈斯一人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rojas is all alone on the left.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.31,0:26:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-丹尼没有越位 -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Dani's onside. -Yeah, he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.15,0:26:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗哈斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rojas!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.41,0:26:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了 -耶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yes! -Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.04,0:26:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼罗哈斯的伤停补时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The injury time equalizer from Dani Rojas,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.66,0:26:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足以让里士满留在英超联盟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}surely enough to keep Richmond in the Premier League!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.59,0:26:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们打平了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got a tie! We got a tie!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.67,0:26:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-耶 -我们留下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah! -We're staying in!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.02,0:26:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.10,0:26:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一发球 曼城就发起了进攻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Straight from the kickoff, City are back on the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.23,0:26:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是他 塔特轻松地甩掉了温彻斯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There he is again. Tartt loses Winchester with ease.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.48,0:26:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他面前只有守门员了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's only him and the goalkeeper.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.28,0:26:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.32,0:26:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 他又传了一次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, he makes the extra pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.66,0:27:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亨德里克进球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hendrick buries it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.08,0:27:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼城赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Manchester City win,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.33,0:27:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,AFC里士满在英超联赛的时间结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and AFC Richmond's time in the Premier League is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.23,0:27:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(全场 AFC里士满1-曼城2)
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.57,0:27:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以一直懊恼下去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can "woulda, coulda, shoulda" all day long,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.70,0:27:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们输了就是输了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but that's-- it's a tough loss. It's a tough loss.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.37,0:27:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.70,0:27:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要恭喜曼城的胜利 恭喜他们的教练 佩普\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do wanna congratulate Man City on their win though, and their coach, Pep.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.62,0:27:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 他今晚看上去多敏锐 是啊 我的伙计...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Boy, did he look sharp tonight. Yeah, my man...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.01,0:28:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(米歇尔 奇迹机器人5000)
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.48,0:28:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你你以为我大老远跑到伦敦来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You! Do you really think I would've come all the way down to London
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.61,0:28:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是为了看我儿子传球的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to watch my son pass the ball?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.32,0:28:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本来可以进球的 你可以做得更好 该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You could've scored the winner. You're better than that, Jamie. Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.21,0:28:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, look, I--
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.42,0:28:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, I'm good. Thank you. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.09,0:28:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们都踢得很精彩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. Y'all played a heck of a game out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.76,0:28:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们虽然没赢 但你们都成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We may not have won, but y'all definitely succeeded.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.43,0:28:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让冠军队经历了90分钟地狱般的煎熬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, you gave the champs 90 minutes of hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.06,0:28:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐豪 你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Zoreaux, where you at?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.23,0:28:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙“救下”的球 比施洗的牧师救下的灵魂还多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That dude had more saves than a Baptist preacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.86,0:28:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为佐豪鼓鼓掌 就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give it up for Zoreaux. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.28,0:29:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 罗伊呢罗伊追着孙子跑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's right. What about Roy? Roy chased down his grandson.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.49,0:29:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没让他轻松进球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stopped him from getting an easy one.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.66,0:29:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 这是一个悲伤的时刻 对我们所有人都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, look, this is a sad moment right here. For all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.21,0:29:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论我站在这里说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And there ain't nothing I can say,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.17,0:29:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都无法抹掉这份悲伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}standing in front of you right now, that can take that away.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.04,0:29:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 请大家帮我个忙 好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But please do me this favor, will you?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.38,0:29:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抬起头 看看这个更衣室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lift your heads up and look around this locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.13,0:29:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.26,0:29:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这里的每一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at everybody else in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.60,0:29:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你们心怀感激\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I want you to be grateful
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.39,0:29:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是和其他人一起经历这个悲伤时刻的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that you're going through this sad moment with all these other folks.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.56,0:29:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我向你们保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I promise you,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.32,0:29:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有比悲伤更惨的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there is something worse out there than being sad,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.86,0:29:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是孤独地承受着悲伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that is being alone and being sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.62,0:29:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个房间里没有人是孤独的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ain't nobody in this room alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.91,0:29:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆 你还记得哪种动物记忆最短吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sam, do you remember what animal has the shortest memory?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.46,0:29:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A goldfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.67,0:30:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 是金鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's right. It's a goldfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.75,0:30:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆 你觉得我们悲伤完愤怒完之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sam, what do you think we should all do
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.30,0:30:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}once we get done being sad and/or angry about this situation?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.80,0:30:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们应该做一条金鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think we should all be a goldfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.60,0:30:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.31,0:30:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们尽情地悲伤吧 一起悲伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's be sad now. Let's be sad together.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.89,0:30:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就要做一条该死的金鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then we can be a gosh-darn goldfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.86,0:30:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Onward. Forward.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.99,0:30:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(曼城)
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.41,0:30:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.88,0:30:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 杰米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Night, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.17,0:30:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情书吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A love letter?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.60,0:31:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(那个传球很漂亮 泰德)
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.41,0:31:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再讨论一下那件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll have a conversation about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.12,0:31:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, y'all.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.21,0:31:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不打扰你们了 -谢谢 莱斯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'll leave you two to talk. -Thank you, Leslie.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.09,0:31:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱斯莉你叫这个名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Leslie? Is that your first name?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.26,0:31:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我妈妈的名字 我继承了女性的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was my mother's name. I'm what's known as a feminine junior.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.34,0:31:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh. Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.48,0:31:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please. Take a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.94,0:31:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝茶吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tea?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.02,0:31:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 我和茶之间依然有巨大的鸿沟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Tea and I are still on a lifelong hiatus, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.94,0:31:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喝水就好 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll take a little water though, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.86,0:31:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 这是一个令人心碎的结果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Ted. That was certainly a heartbreaking result.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.24,0:31:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 女士 我想了很多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, ma'am. And I've been thinking about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.95,0:31:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得让您开除我很不公平 所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's mighty unfair that you have to fire me, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.33,0:32:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不介意的话 我就不麻烦你了 我自己辞职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it's all the same to you, I'd like to spare you the trouble and just quit.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.21,0:32:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的辞职信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This here is my letter of resignation.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.55,0:32:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在外卖菜单的后面写的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wrote it on the back of a takeout menu,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.30,0:32:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是一个信封 我签了字 所以是有效的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's in an envelope, and I signed it, so, you know, it's legit.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.30,0:32:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说 泰德教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You listen to me, Coach Lasso.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.51,0:32:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哪都不能去 因为我们还要为下一个赛季做准备呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are not going anywhere, 'cause we have work to do next season.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.86,0:32:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, okay. All right, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.53,0:32:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 等下 我有个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. So, wait. Tell me this, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.86,0:32:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然球队可以被降级 那也可以升回来 是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The teams that get relegated, they can get un-relegated, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.16,0:32:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是可以升级的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They can get promoted.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.66,0:32:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那明天我们努力升级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So then, next year we get ourselves a promotion,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.83,0:32:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样会给我的履历增辉\Nwhich looks good on any résumé.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.00,0:32:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就能回到联赛...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then we come back to this league and...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.62,0:32:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要让所有人大吃一惊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we do something that no one believes we could ever do.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.96,0:32:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢个大满贯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Win the whole fucking thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.76,0:32:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.89,0:32:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气泡水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bubbles.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.14,0:32:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我喷到你了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. Did I get you?
