[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.84,0:00:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是丽莎克姆林 很高兴和格雷厄姆保罗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lisa Cramlin here with Graham Paul,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.13,0:00:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为您分析今天下午 里士满对阵阿森纳的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}breaking down this afternoon's Richmond-Arsenal match.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.22,0:00:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-欢迎 格雷厄姆 -很高兴来到这个节目 丽莎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Welcome, Graham. -Pleasure to be here, Lisa.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.47,0:00:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天对于罗伊肯特而言 是连续几次失利后的另一个艰难的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So today was another tough day for Roy Kent in a stretch of bad days.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.97,0:00:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他过去的九场比赛中 肯特已经...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In his last nine games, Kent has had...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.44,0:00:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...而他的失误率几乎翻倍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...while his turnovers have nearly doubled.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.85,0:00:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天 这个丢脸的乌龙球...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And today, it was an ignominious own goal...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.78,0:00:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这儿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.86,0:00:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都走了吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone gone?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.11,0:00:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 除了罗哈斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. Well, except Rojas.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.32,0:00:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子还在球场上做练习呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Darn kid's out on the practice pitch still doing drills.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.24,0:00:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What a fucking asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.58,0:00:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊 -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Right? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.16,0:00:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人点了罗伊加冰块吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somebody order a Roy on the rocks, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.12,0:00:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How we doing in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.04,0:00:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太凉了 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is cold, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.71,0:00:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是看着你泡在水里我都要打哆嗦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just looking at you in there is making me all chilly inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.34,0:00:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能直接说我搞砸了然后离开吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you just tell me I fucked up and then go?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.22,0:00:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会这么做的 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not gonna do that, bud.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.85,0:01:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害我们输了比赛 我是个废物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I lost us the game. I'm a piece of shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.14,0:01:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点 你今天很难熬 没什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Easy now. You had a bad day. Big whoop.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.10,0:01:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“没什么大不了”?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Big whoop"?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.43,0:01:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 没什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, big whoop.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.15,0:01:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自责的样子像是 伍迪艾伦吹了单簧管一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You beating yourself up is like Woody Allen playing the clarinet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.86,0:01:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听 好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna hear it. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.48,0:01:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 别这样了 别太苛责自己了 好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So just, you know, knock it off. Go easy on yourself. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.32,0:01:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我永远支持你 任何事都不会改变这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. I got your back. Ain't nothing gonna change that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.74,0:01:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你这样子 简直像是棕头发的“怨妇奥斯卡”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at you in there, looking like a brunette Oscar the Grouch.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.50,0:01:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开灯还是关掉? -关掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-On or off? -Off.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.42,0:01:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别再这样了 拜托了罗伊 为了我们 为你自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gotta stop holding on, Roy, please, for us, for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.38,0:01:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻过这篇吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.67,0:01:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这就对了 -你好 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-There you go. -Hola, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.18,0:01:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们休息一下 稍候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're taking a break. When we return,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.09,0:01:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来看一下杰米塔特在曼城的优秀表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we'll take a look at Jamie Tartt's brilliant day for Manchester City.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.89,0:01:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(从前有一个老人叫肯特...)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.38,0:02:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 就这样 美极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's it. Right there. Yep. Beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.43,0:02:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕 你要小心点了 凯特摩丝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, snap. Watch your back, Kate Moss.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.18,0:02:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英国模特界出现了一位新星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a new bad girl on the British modeling scene.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.93,0:02:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吧? -好的 我想可以了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Huh? Yeah? -Okay, I think we've got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.73,0:02:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你带了这个 以防你需要一点饼干助力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Brought these in case you need a little biscuit boost. Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.27,0:02:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 你做这些事会紧张吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Man, oh, man. You get nervous doing this kind of stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.03,0:02:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一个描写足球界的女性的文章 没什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a profile on women in football. It's not a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.53,0:02:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们四个人 我、凯伦、迪莉娅 和辣妹维多利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's, like, four of us: me, Karen, Delia and Posh Spice.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.87,0:02:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个偶像可是责任重大的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, now. Being a role model's a huge deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.79,0:02:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许某个角落里会有一个小女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you realize that there's probably a little girl out there somewhere
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着小号的茄子色的有权力意味的套装\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}rocking a tiny eggplant-colored power suit,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.08,0:02:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦想着某一天会成为体育高管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and she's just dreaming about becoming a sports executive someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.13,0:02:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会读到这篇文章 她会想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's gonna read this article and she's gonna think,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.00,0:03:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“天呀 我的梦想是可以实现的”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Holy smokes. My dreams are possible."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.26,0:03:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你设想的情境里 小女孩会读 《足球金融周刊》?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In this scenario of yours, little girls read The Football Financial Quarterly?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.05,0:03:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢?小女孩的心思猜不透\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, who knows? Little girls are mysterious.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.39,0:03:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且愚蠢、充满力量 我很多年前 就放弃猜测她们的心思了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And silly and powerful. I gave up trying to figure them out years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.23,0:03:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望希金斯能看到这一幕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell you what, I wish Higgins was here to see this,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.10,0:03:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他肯定也会为你高兴的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause he'd be real happy for you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.07,0:03:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不一定 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know about that, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯决定辞职的时候 他明确表达了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When Higgins decided to quit, he made it quite clear
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.53,0:03:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我的看法 并不是很正面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what he thought about me, and it wasn't supportive.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.45,0:03:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 你这种想法很消极 好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nope. I'm filing that under stinkin' thinkin' right there. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.03,0:03:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你保证 他会回心转意的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I guarantee you, he'll come around.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.74,0:03:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 我要换个话题了 -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Right. I'm changing the subject. -Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.66,0:03:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入决赛周了 团队的士气如何?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's the team morale going into the final weekend?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.12,0:03:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一次输球 我还很伤心呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, I'm still heartbroken about the last loss.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.50,0:03:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.34,0:03:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.21,0:03:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨 基莉 -嗨 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Hey, Keeley. -Hi, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汤姆福德市场部的人有联系你吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, did those marketing folks from Tom Ford ever get back to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.80,0:03:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 他们联系我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, they did.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.14,0:03:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说会继续用现有的模特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They said they're gonna stick with the models they already have.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.55,0:03:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.56,0:03:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 但他们也说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. But they did say
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.02,0:03:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们做素人广告或是讽刺性的广告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that if they ever do an everyman campaign or something satirical,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.77,0:03:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会考虑你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your name's on their list.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.85,0:03:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好哎 可以嘛 还不赖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. There you go. That's not bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.31,0:03:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能跟你单独聊几句吗 瑞贝卡?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I borrow you for a second, Rebecca?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.03,0:04:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.99,0:04:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呀 这里一股臭脚丫子味\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My God, it smells of feet in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.04,0:04:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道太冲了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, it just hits you immediately, doesn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.37,0:04:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一股热气 脚臭味直往鼻子里钻 你闻到了吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's hot. Like feet funk, right up your nose. Can you smell it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.96,0:04:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是一个言而无信的混蛋 瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're being a right floppy cock, Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.25,0:04:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么还没告诉泰德?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why haven't you told Ted yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.13,0:04:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going to.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.21,0:04:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.63,0:04:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象一下 你对某个无辜的人 做了不可饶恕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Imagine doing something unforgivable to someone who doesn't deserve it
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.22,0:04:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你要看着对方的眼睛 坦白自己所做的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then having to look them in the eye and tell them what you've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.60,0:04:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要想象 我干过这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have to imagine. I've done it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.97,0:04:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八年级的时候 我在乔安娜威灵顿的储物柜里拉了屎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Year Eight, I took a shit in Joanna Wellington's locker.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.27,0:04:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我道歉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I apologized,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.73,0:04:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她邀请我参加她的生日派对 一周后我们就和好如初了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was uninvited to her birthday party, and then we patched it up a week later.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.90,0:04:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just fucking tell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.11,0:04:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你为什么要在她的储物柜里拉屎?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, why did you do a shit in her locker?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.15,0:04:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 我当时13岁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. I was 13.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.24,0:04:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛?青春期的女孩就是又神秘又黑暗 又危险啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? Teenage girls are, like, mysterious and dark and dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.12,0:04:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 -这不是重点!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-All right. -That is not the point!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.62,0:04:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 -天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Okay. -Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.54,0:04:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 哇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.79,0:04:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道女人喜欢鞋 但是 姑娘们 拜托 这太蠢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know women like shoes, but, girls, come on, this is silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.04,0:04:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我这句是性别歧视\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, that was really sexist.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.84,0:05:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是没料到这里会有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wasn't expecting there to be anyone in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.26,0:05:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们在 好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you are in here, and that's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.84,0:05:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们继续 我走了 抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take as long as you need. Yeah. I'll go. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.09,0:05:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在告诉泰德有什么意义呢?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, what would be the point of telling Ted now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.26,0:05:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不会改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't change anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.76,0:05:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会改变我对你的看法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It would change how I feel about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.48,0:05:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫 我们本赛季还有最后一场 对阵曼城的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, David, we got one final game this season against Man City,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.90,0:05:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的目标是像威利奈尔森一样 让大家”嗨”到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and our goal is to go out like Willie Nelson, on a high.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.95,0:05:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.24,0:05:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特伦特克里姆 请问吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about Trent Crimm?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.20,0:05:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我没记错的话 你是《星球日报》的 对吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if memory serves, you're from the Daily Planet, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.45,0:05:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特伦特克里姆 《独立报》的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trent Crimm, The Independent.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.87,0:05:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对 好吧 你有什么问题 特伦特?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. That's the one. Okay. What's your question, Trent?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.41,0:05:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多年轻球员在您执教期间都有所提升\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Many of your young players have improved during your tenure.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.92,0:05:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是路易肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then there's Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.38,0:05:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在上一场比赛中表现欠佳 您对此有什么看法?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He played dismally last match. Thoughts?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.46,0:05:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你可以问罗伊本人 他会告诉你他只是状态不好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I think you could ask Roy himself. He'd tell you it wasn't his best day.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.97,0:05:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我现在可以告诉你的是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'll let you know right now
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.26,0:05:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特是这个队伍的支柱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Roy Kent is the backbone of this team.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.01,0:05:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们换个方式吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's mix it up in here a little.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.60,0:05:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们是内向型的 请举手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're an introvert, I want y'all to raise your hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.52,0:05:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个问题由你们来问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You guys get the next few questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.44,0:05:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上当了吧!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was a trick!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.94,0:06:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们都是内向型 那你们此时 肯定像教堂里的老鼠一样安静\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If y'all were really introverts, you would've been quiet as a church mouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.73,0:06:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非是韦斯特博罗浸信会教堂 那些土耳其人总是喋喋不休\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unless that church was Westboro Baptist. Those turkeys won't shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.24,0:06:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 伙计们 怎么了?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, guys. What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.74,0:06:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please have a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.58,0:06:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.17,0:06:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这样子像是要表演即兴喜剧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I feel like y'all are about to do some improv comedy
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.75,0:06:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是告诉我你们要约会了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or tell me that you're dating each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.34,0:06:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是哪种 我都没意见 因为我们是同盟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Either one's cool with me. 'Cause your suggestion is ally.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.34,0:06:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要把罗伊从首发阵容中除名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to take Roy out of the starting lineup.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.80,0:06:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I see. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.51,0:06:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不仅是一次比赛失利 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It wasn't just one bad game, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.85,0:06:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他年纪大了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's showing his age,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.06,0:06:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的五场比赛中 他都犯了严重的错误\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and he's made significant mistakes in each of the last five matches.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.56,0:06:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是还没有被这些错误“咬到屁股”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just haven't been bitten in the ass by them yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.89,0:06:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但昨天我们的屁股上已经有牙印了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But yesterday our butts had teeth marks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.94,0:06:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很深的那种 你通常需要付钱的那种\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Deep ones. The kind you usually have to pay for.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.15,0:06:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(瑞贝卡 即“老板” 我需要跟你谈谈)
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.41,0:06:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们...我不会让罗伊坐冷板凳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Guys... I'm not benching Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.29,0:06:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我们的队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's our captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.58,0:07:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我希望你们知道 我在乎每一个人的意见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I want you to know that I value each of your opinions.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.96,0:07:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是错误的意见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even when they're wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.05,0:07:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才真心期待这是即兴喜剧的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was really hoping it was going to be improv.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.55,0:07:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm Audi 5000.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.89,0:07:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你花钱让人咬你? -不 当然不是了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You paid someone to bite you? -No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.52,0:07:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. I...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.73,0:07:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是收钱的那个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Been paid.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.32,0:07:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.95,0:07:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.95,0:07:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有件事要告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have something I need to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.41,0:07:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗耳恭听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm all ears.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.96,0:07:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我就不拐弯抹角了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, I'm not gonna beat around the bush.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.96,0:07:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会...直截了当\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just gonna... get straight to the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.26,0:07:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不扯那些有的没的 因为很招人烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No faffing around, 'cause that's just annoying,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.92,0:07:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也绝对不会拖延时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and definitely no procrastinating.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.72,0:07:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖延...这个词挺不错的 是吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Procrast-- Procrast-- That's a good word, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.89,0:07:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖延\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Procrastinating. Procrastinating.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.72,0:07:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道这个词的词源是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wonder what the etymology of that word is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.56,0:08:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然 “Pro”意思是“赞同” 但“crast”?Crast...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously, "pro," very good, but "crast"? Crast...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.15,0:08:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 嘿!我们查查好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have no idea. Hey! Why don't we look it up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.23,0:08:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你有字典吗? -我身上没有 你还好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Have you got a dictionary? -Not on me. Are you doing okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我? -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Me? -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.48,0:08:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好极了!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm brilliant!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.49,0:08:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我好得不能再好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I am top of the pops.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.03,0:08:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 你能晚点再来吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, do you think you could do this later?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.12,0:08:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 没问题 我就按一下快退按钮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, sure. No problem. I'll just hit the rewind button.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.88,0:08:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.89,0:08:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他啊 我是个大人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do it. Just do it. I'm a big girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.68,0:08:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以的...振作起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can fucking just-- Just tidy up your mess.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.80,0:08:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作起来 好了 天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tidy up your mess. Right. Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.89,0:08:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.60,0:08:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-鲁伯特 -你看上去很紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Rupert. -You seem anxious.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.52,0:08:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯去哪了?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's Higgins?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.82,0:08:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把他炒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I fired him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.23,0:08:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么?希金斯可是一流的员工\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? Higgins is first class.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.69,0:08:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他唯一的缺点是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except the only negative about the man
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.82,0:08:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次他跟我借了一支笔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was that whenever he borrowed a pen from me,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.24,0:09:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都会像一只好动的小狗崽一样啃笔头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he would nibble the top like some anxious little puppy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.79,0:09:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖狗狗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.87,0:09:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经不在了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, well, he's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.12,0:09:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜 也许他现在会接住我的橄榄枝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shame. Oh, well. Maybe he'll accept my offer now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.84,0:09:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 鲁伯特 你来这里 是打算买下俱乐部还是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Rupert, are you here to try and buy back the club or--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.50,0:09:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我想亲自告诉你一件事 免得你从其他人那里听到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I wanted to tell you something before you heard it somewhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.01,0:09:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和贝克丝要有孩子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bex and I are having a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.72,0:09:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是一个惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Surprise, again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.85,0:09:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但你不是说... -我以为我们可以成熟地看待这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-But you always said that-- -I thought we could be mature about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.31,0:09:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你够成熟了 好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're mature enough, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.77,0:09:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都快70了 你还要生孩子?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're nearly 70, and you're having a baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.36,0:09:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么 活在《圣经》里的人物吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, what are you, a character from the fucking Bible?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.32,0:09:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你的孩子到了青春期\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When your kid hits puberty,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.03,0:09:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就只剩下一堆灰了 外加一张运通黑卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll be nothing but a pile of dust and a black Amex card.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.78,0:09:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, now, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.95,0:09:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么叫我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't call me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.16,0:09:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人是会变的 我想要孩子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People change. I do want a child.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.41,0:09:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我只是不愿意跟...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just suppose I didn't want one with...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.34,0:09:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Before.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.17,0:09:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底 最重要的是 和对的人在一起 不是吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, in the end, it's just about being with the right person, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.55,0:10:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.64,0:10:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真开心能当面告诉你这个消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so glad I got to tell you this in person.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.27,0:10:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望你从媒体上得知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would have hated for you to read it in the press.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.77,0:10:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你们和曼城的比赛好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck against Man City.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.28,0:10:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有件事要告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have something I need to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.28,0:11:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似曾相识\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Déjà vu.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.16,0:11:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是个贱人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm a fucking bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.95,0:11:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这是头一遭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nope, that's new.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.21,0:11:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 我骗了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, I lied to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.29,0:11:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我雇你是因为我希望这支球队输\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hired you because I wanted this team to lose.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.71,0:11:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你失败\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted you to fail,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.42,0:11:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且只要有机会 我就会搞破坏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I sabotaged you every chance I've had.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.39,0:11:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我找了摄影师偷拍你和基莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was me who hired that photographer to take the photo of you and Keeley.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.35,0:11:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我安排了特伦特克里姆采访你 希望他能够羞辱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I set up the interview with Trent Crimm, hoping that he would humiliate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.15,0:11:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还唆使了杰米塔特的转会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I instigated the transfer of Jamie Tartt,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.11,0:11:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你要我别那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even though you'd asked me not to.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.65,0:11:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个俱乐部是鲁伯特唯一在乎的东西 我想毁掉它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This club is all that Rupert has ever cared about, and I wanted to destroy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.49,0:11:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他带给我的伤害和痛苦如数奉还\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To cause him as much pain and suffering as he has caused me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.42,0:11:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎利用了谁 或是伤害了谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I didn't care who I used or who I hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:12:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这些好人只是一门心思地想做出改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All you good people just trying to make a difference.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.09,0:12:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 我真的很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.52,0:12:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想辞职或是告诉媒体 我完全理解\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you want to quit or call the press, I'll completely understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.74,0:12:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原谅你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I forgive you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.16,0:12:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...什么?为什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You-- What? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.70,0:12:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离婚是很难过的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Divorce is hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.79,0:12:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论你是离开的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter if you're the one leaving
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.62,0:12:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是被抛弃的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or if... you're the one who got left.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.92,0:12:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离婚会让人做出疯狂的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It makes folks do crazy things.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.30,0:12:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天 我现在给足球队当教练 在伦敦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hell, I'm coaching soccer for heaven's sake. In London.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.88,0:12:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这够疯狂的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, that's nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.64,0:12:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.52,0:12:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你给我的这份工作改变了我的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But this job you gave me has changed my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.02,0:12:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给了我足够远的距离 让来让我审视 我的生活究竟发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It gave me the distance I needed to see what was really going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.03,0:13:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 但是你和我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, but you and me...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.28,0:13:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之间没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.74,0:13:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.83,0:13:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来嘛 握个手 我胳膊都酸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, just shake this hand. My arm's starting to get--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.84,0:13:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直认为如果你还有在乎的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I think that if you care about someone
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.42,0:13:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那说明你的心中依然有爱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you got a little love in your heart,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.68,0:13:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要心在一起就没有过不去的坎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there ain't nothing you can't get through together.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.14,0:13:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白我的意思吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what I'm saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.81,0:13:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不仅在说我们俩的事 对吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not just talking about us now, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.06,0:13:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是 也许不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe. Maybe not.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.61,0:13:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.99,0:13:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要换衣服去训练了 不对 是练习\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna go change for practice-- training.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.78,0:13:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便了 管他呢?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever. Who cares?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.70,0:13:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴看到你 老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice seeing you down here, boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.58,0:13:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让这里蓬荜生辉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You liven up the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.37,0:13:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's get it going, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.29,0:14:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来 集合 快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go. Gather up. Come on, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.75,0:14:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们 你们要记住 你们的身体就像隔夜的米饭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, fellas, you gotta remember, your body is like day-old rice.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.38,0:14:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没好好加热 就会出现严重后果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it ain't warmed up properly, something real bad could happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.76,0:14:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物中毒可不是开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Food poisoning is no joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.51,0:14:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次 我呕吐不止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One time, I was being sick,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.39,0:14:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与此同时 我还拉肚子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and at the same time, I was having diarrhea.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.81,0:14:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是会有这种情况 还有人想分享吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yep. That'll happen. Anybody else wanna share?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.02,0:14:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人可以同时呕吐和拉稀吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To be able to do both those things at the same time?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.89,0:14:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的身体真是个奇迹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The body is a miracle.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.98,0:14:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 很好的视角 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Good perspective. I appreciate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.02,0:14:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我们都知道速度很关键\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, fellas, we all know speed is important.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.65,0:14:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但能够迅速停下并转换方向呢?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But being able to stop and change directions quickly?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.28,0:14:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就像是肯伊的专辑《808秒和心碎》\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, that's like Kanye's 808s & Heartbreak.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.16,0:14:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全被低估了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It don't get nearly enough credit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.78,0:14:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家在内特放置锥形桶 的位置站好 快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, so let's line up on these cones Nate put out. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.49,0:14:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, here's the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.58,0:14:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一个完成往返跑的人是烂番茄 开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last one to start, stop, then start again is a rotten egg. Let's do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.54,0:14:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 我今早洗澡的时候想到了一个笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Coach, I thought of a joke this morning in the shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.30,0:14:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英国猫头鹰会说什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does a British owl say?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.64,0:14:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 英国猫头鹰会...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, what does a British owl--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.22,0:14:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才说...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was saying earlier that--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.98,0:15:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样子好像我拿着鼻屎 在追你一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're acting like I'm chasing you with a booger or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.10,0:15:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我知道怎么回事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. All right. I see what's going on here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.27,0:15:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为罗伊吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is about Roy, ain't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.48,0:15:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你打算不理我 对我冷处理 这是一个套餐啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you gonna give me the cold shoulder and the silent treatment. That's a combo.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.99,0:15:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送不送中杯饮料?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does it come with a medium drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.32,0:15:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.91,0:15:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 内特 英国猫头鹰说什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Nate, what does a British owl say?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.04,0:15:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要假装你没听见我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gonna do that move where you act like you don't hear me
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.46,0:15:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后走开 是吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then you just walk away, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.92,0:15:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.96,0:15:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你至于跑那么远吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's like that now, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.04,0:15:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可去你们的吧 我要专注于训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Heck with both of you guys. I'm just gonna focus up here on practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.71,0:15:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 丹尼 坚持住 加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you go, Dani. Dig in, baby. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.34,0:15:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死 -没关系 罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fuck. -It's all right, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.89,0:15:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死! -跟上 罗伊!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fuck! -Keep up, Roy!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.81,0:15:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你可以的 罗伊 -该死!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-You got this, Roy. -Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.56,0:15:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 都发泄出来 罗伊 发泄出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's it. Swear it out, Roy. Swear it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.57,0:15:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.99,0:15:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.23,0:16:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.45,0:16:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这儿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.95,0:16:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(里士满)
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.50,0:16:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.59,0:16:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有这么多椅子呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a lot of other seats.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.05,0:16:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 但我买的是这个座位的票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, yeah, this is what my ticket says.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.64,0:16:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗 罗伊?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How you doing, Roy?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.85,0:16:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好 你呢?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. You?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.52,0:17:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good, good, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.14,0:17:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在网上看了一个视频\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I saw this video online
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.10,0:17:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只小猫和一只小鸡成了朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of a kitten and a little baby chicken becoming friends
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.31,0:17:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起玩的视频\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and just hanging out together.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.07,0:17:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺逗的...我给你看 我存在手机里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was-- Well, here, let me show it to you. I got it right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.15,0:17:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想说什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's this about?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.70,0:17:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好笑的 因为我妈每次有什么 难以启齿的话要对我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's funny, 'cause whenever my mom has something tough to talk about with me,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.58,0:17:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她都会...先说些其他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she'll... you know, she'll start it off saying something
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.50,0:17:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些奇怪的 平常不会说的好话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about, I don't know, something weird, something overtly nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.58,0:17:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚想到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, yeah, I just thought the idea
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.80,0:17:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫和鸟成为朋友这个想法挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of a cat and a bird being all simpatico was nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.05,0:17:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 罗伊 我们最近在讨论 对阵曼城的首发阵容...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Roy, we've been talking about the starting lineup against Man City--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.93,0:17:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢 你不准让我坐冷板凳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you dare. You're not fucking benching me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.69,0:17:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是 我就是跟你聊聊 罗伊 我... -是啊 聊聊 你就只会这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Well, no. I'm just talking here, Roy. I-- -Yeah, talking. That's all you do is talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.52,0:17:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说你永远支持我的屁话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Talking all that bullshit about how you've got my back.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.65,0:17:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 我是支持你的 -胡说!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. Hey, I do have your back. -Bullshit!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.90,0:17:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你假装是一个守信的人 其实你谎话连篇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You pretended to be a man of your word. You're fucking full of shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.44,0:17:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去死吧 去你大爷的!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can go fuck yourself. Fuck you!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.38,0:18:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在你身上看到了很多惊喜的变化\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are a lot of surprises happening here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.63,0:18:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说你的小胡子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like that tiny little beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.93,0:18:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫凡戴克山羊胡 以那个十七世纪的弗拉芒画家命名的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's called a Van Dyke after the 17th century Flemish painter.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.47,0:18:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -我认为这能代表我现在的感受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Right. -And I think it makes me look how I feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.02,0:18:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chill.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.35,0:18:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希金斯夫人是什么感受?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How does Mrs. Higgins feel about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.61,0:18:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她讨厌死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She hates it with a white-hot intensity.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.40,0:18:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 听着...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Look...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.20,0:18:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟泰德坦白了 我全都告诉他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I came clean to Ted. I told him everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.78,0:18:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果如何?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did that go?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.87,0:18:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那家伙做了什么吗?他原谅我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what the little shit did? He forgave me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.16,0:18:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真是个混蛋 -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Fucking asshole. -I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.54,0:18:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不是为这个来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But that's not actually why I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.80,0:18:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟你道歉...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to apologize to you for...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.30,0:18:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你的态度太恶劣了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}treating you so poorly
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.55,0:19:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还强迫你参与我那愚蠢幼稚的把戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and forcing you to be an accomplice in my moronically childish scheme.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.60,0:19:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很抱歉 希金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am truly sorry, Higgins.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.52,0:19:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.94,0:19:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 瑞贝卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Rebecca.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.23,0:19:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我迷失了一阵子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I lost my way for a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.40,0:19:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.03,0:19:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我已经回到正轨上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'm on the road back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.78,0:19:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看得出来 这很适合你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can tell. You know what, it suits you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.87,0:19:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像你的胡子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unlike that beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.58,0:19:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 没忍住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. Had to.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.25,0:19:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家里从来没有过小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think I've ever had a child in my house before.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.17,0:19:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰米呢?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Jamie?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.09,0:19:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我们不能让她随意乱翻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't let her go snooping around though.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.17,0:19:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想让她找到我的震动棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want her to find my vibrator.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.30,0:19:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那是个问题 她妈说不准碰电子产品\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's gonna be a problem. Her mum said no electronics.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.18,0:19:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最近还好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, how are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.35,0:19:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.52,0:19:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得小孩子挺神奇的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do kind of think kids are pretty incredible.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.07,0:20:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的新牙齿会把旧牙齿顶掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, she's got new teeth that push out her old teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.28,0:20:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类身体是个奇迹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The body is a miracle.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.07,0:20:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上次坐冷板凳的时候...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, the last time I was on the bench...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.78,0:20:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备好谈论重要的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are ready to talk about real stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.37,0:20:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.41,0:20:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.79,0:20:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come sit here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.84,0:20:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱着这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.72,0:20:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 咱俩都准备好了 说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, we're both ready. Lay it on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.30,0:20:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伊肯特从小到大一直是每个队伍里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roy Kent has been the best player on every team he's been on
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.56,0:20:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最优秀的球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}since he was a kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.97,0:20:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢成为罗伊肯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I like being Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.39,0:20:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道能不能接受自己 只是一个叫“肯特”的废物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know if I can handle just being some loser has-been called Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.90,0:20:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“你好吗 罗伊” 挺好的 “你最近在忙什么?” 无所事事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"All right, Roy?" Yeah. "What you been up to?" Fuck all.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.57,0:20:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 顾影自怜的男人太性感了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}God. I think men who feel sorry for themselves are so sexy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.53,0:20:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别闹了 -不 我是认真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Stop it. -No, seriously. I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.16,0:20:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你开始跟我讲 以打比赛为生有多难的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you start telling me how hard it is playing a game for a living,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.33,0:20:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能会高潮哦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think I might come.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.37,0:20:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我而言不仅是比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not just a game to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.04,0:20:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只会做这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all I've ever known.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.25,0:20:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's who I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.92,0:20:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的全部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.51,0:21:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲比?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Phoebe? Phoebe?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.09,0:21:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能过来一下吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you come here for a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.97,0:21:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对 齐柏林飞船乐队太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were right. Zeppelin is amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.72,0:21:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你听了奶油乐队再说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait till you hear Cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.14,0:21:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是首先 我需要你闭上眼睛 好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But first, I need you to close your eyes for me, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.15,0:21:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 你能描述一下你的罗伊叔叔吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Can you describe your Uncle Roy?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.73,0:21:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何你能想到的事情 开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything that you can think of. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.19,0:21:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我叔叔 他的胡子很扎人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, he's my uncle. His beard is scratchy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.07,0:21:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他给我买冰淇淋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He buys me ice cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.45,0:21:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他经常骂人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He swears a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.83,0:21:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真的很好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's really funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.20,0:21:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I love him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.75,0:21:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好 菲比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well done, Phoebe.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.42,0:21:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗?我没听到任何 与足球运动员相关的描述\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See? I didn't hear anything about being a footballer.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.13,0:21:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在乎她怎么说啊?她才六岁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who gives a shit what she has to say? She's six.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.47,0:21:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键是 你根本不知道 人们是怎么看待罗伊肯特的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The point is, you don't know what people think about Roy Kent.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.31,0:21:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其次 罗伊肯特 重要的是 你是如何看待罗伊的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Secondly, all that matters, Roy Kent, is what you think about Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.61,0:22:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的前男友在跟别的男人下棋?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That your old girl playing chess with some other bloke?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.32,0:22:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -太残忍了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yep. -That's fucking brutal.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.37,0:22:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是在玩游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's just playing her game.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.54,0:22:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要坚强 听到了吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You stay strong, you hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.12,0:22:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个帅气的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a beautiful man.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.00,0:22:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.42,0:22:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就咱俩喝有点多了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, that's a lot of pints just for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.93,0:22:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你跟罗伊之间不会太愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you might've had a tough time with Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.14,0:22:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练 你天生就这么善解人意 就像《飞越疯人院》里那个院长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach, you are a natural-born caregiver. Like Chief from Cuckoo's Nest.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.02,0:22:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更像是泰伯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was always more of a Taber guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.90,0:22:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是说实话 我其实没跟罗伊说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if I'm being honest, I actually never got around to telling Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.57,0:22:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么看我 他自己猜出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, don't give me those eyes. He figured it out all on his own.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.74,0:22:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看出来你现在高兴了 但是先别高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can see you're happy now, but don't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.99,0:22:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我仔细想了一下...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause I've been thinking about it and...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.29,0:22:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定让罗伊作为对阵曼城的首发球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}well, I'm starting Roy against Man City and that's that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.04,0:22:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 让他坐冷板凳不仅是对他的侮辱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, putting him on the bench wouldn't just be humiliating to him,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.00,0:23:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这其实会影响到他的生计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it could actually affect his livelihood.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比任何人都清楚 对我来说 输赢不是最重要的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you know better than anyone that all this ain't about winning to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.71,0:23:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那并不能决定成功与否 对吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause that ain't how we measure success, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.47,0:23:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的 当然是了!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it, it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.35,0:23:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 谁把爆竹塞你屁股里然后点炸了?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. Who put a firecracker up your butt and lit it?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.93,0:23:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你!我受够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You did! And I'm sick of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.85,0:23:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我们在堪萨斯的时候 我理解你的这种使命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I understood this mission when we were in Kansas.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.11,0:23:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那些只是孩子 而这些是职业球员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But those were kids and these are professionals
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.94,0:23:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输赢对他们很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and winning does matter to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.53,0:23:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我也很重要 这没什么不妥的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And it matters to me. And that's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.40,0:23:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对吗 梅? -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Ain't that right, Mae? -A-fucking-men it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.08,0:23:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不明白呢?输球会引发一系列后果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do you not get it? Losing has repercussions.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.04,0:23:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们输了就会被降级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We lose, we get relegated.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.58,0:23:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被降级了 那一切就结束了 我们什么成就都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We get relegated, this is over and we will have built nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.79,0:23:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你选择顾及一个球员的感受 而不是履行教练的职责...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you wanna pick a player's feelings over a coach's duty to make a point...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.01,0:23:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想跟这么自私的人喝酒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna drink with someone that selfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.22,0:23:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我这辈子见过的最性感的画面了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was the sexiest fucking thing I've ever seen in my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.81,0:23:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿好东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get your things.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.52,0:24:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她玩你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's been toying with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.94,0:24:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将军 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Checkmate, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.06,0:24:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不用了 -你对坚果过敏?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-I'm good. -You got a nut allergy?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.73,0:24:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对手指过敏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a finger allergy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.86,0:24:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看还有什么 有红酒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What else have I got to offer you here? We got red wine.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.74,0:24:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有茶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.41,0:24:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两天前的煮面水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two-day-old pasta water.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.95,0:24:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喝茶吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tea's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.33,0:24:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我很抱歉叫你去死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I'm sorry I told you to go fuck yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.29,0:25:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我通常更善于隐藏自己的愤怒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm usually better at hiding my anger.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.83,0:25:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么认为?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think so, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.38,0:25:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Know thyself.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.96,0:25:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安息吧 苏格拉底\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rest in peace, Socrates.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.22,0:25:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟我侄女说 我可能不会再踢球了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Told my niece I might not be playing.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.59,0:25:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她问我能不能给她买冰淇淋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She asked if we could go get ice cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.01,0:25:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 至少你有可以聊聊天的人 对吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, hey, at least you had someone you could talk to, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.27,0:25:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰淇淋好吃吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How was the ice cream?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.35,0:25:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃 很美味的冰淇淋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. It's fucking ice cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.14,0:25:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧?冰淇淋最好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, right? Ice cream's the best.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.27,0:25:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像看比利乔的现场 你知道吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's kinda like seeing Billy Joel perform live, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.61,0:25:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不会失望\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It never disappoints.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.98,0:25:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我会胃胀气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It does give me the toots though.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.11,0:25:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说冰淇淋 不是比利乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The ice cream, not Billy Joel.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.86,0:25:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问她如果我不踢球了 她还会不会看比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I asked her if she was still gonna watch the match if I wasn't playing.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.78,0:25:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么说?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.87,0:25:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小混蛋说会看 眼睛都没眨一下 就看着我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Little shit said yes. Didn't even blink. Just straight into my face.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.21,0:25:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 演艺圈就这样 不是吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, hey. That's showbiz, ain't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.96,0:25:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《茶煲表哥》里维芙姨妈换人的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I promised myself I was never gonna watch Fresh Prince again
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.38,0:25:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓绝对不会再看这部电视剧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when they swapped out Aunt Vivs.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.88,0:25:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但老实说 只要他们还留着卡尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But truth be told, as long as they let Carlton do his thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.84,0:25:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还会抽时间坐下来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was always gonna take a minute and just sit right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.22,0:25:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花絮:阿方索里贝罗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sidebar: Alfonso Ribeiro,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.43,0:26:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,19世纪、20世纪、21世纪 最伟大的肢体喜剧演员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the greatest physical comedian of the 19th, 20th and 21st century.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.56,0:26:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恰当举例\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Case in point right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.06,0:26:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很经典的动作 是吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Iconic, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.69,0:26:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来不知道一个成年人在我面前 学卡尔顿我该作何反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never know how to react when a grown man does the Carlton in front of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.73,0:26:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你光是看到影子就应该在干嘛了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You could see a silhouette doing this, you know exactly what it is,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.23,0:26:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这是谁的招牌动作 这是绝无仅有的阿方索...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you know exactly who's doing it. It is the one, the only, Alfonso--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.45,0:26:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别吵了! -抱歉 希普利夫人!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Knock it off! -Sorry, Ms. Shipley!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.07,0:26:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们因为这事吵了一周了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It has been a whole thing this last week.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.87,0:26:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 你知道我们能怎么做吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anyway. You know what we could do?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.04,0:26:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个赛季大伤小伤不断\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've been hurt off and on all season.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.45,0:26:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们就说你受伤了不能上场怎么样? 没必要觉得丢脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't we just say you're injured, you can't play? No shame in that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.42,0:26:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我还想进入下个赛季的话 这能保护我的价值\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That would help protect my stock if I wanna move next season.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.71,0:26:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许可以去一个愿意首发我的俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe to a club that actually wants to start me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.80,0:26:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.88,0:26:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我最终只能去该死的美国踢球\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if, God forbid, I end up having to play in fucking America,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.89,0:26:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一说 我肯定是一枝独秀了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where I'd dominate, by the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.72,0:26:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会说:“噢 这就是足球?”\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They'd be like, "Oh, is this football then?"
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.43,0:26:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然 我是希望你上场的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, obviously, my preference would be to have you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.02,0:26:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是明天的训练 还是比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At practice tomorrow and the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.15,0:26:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你要做正确的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But hey, you gotta do what's right for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.49,0:26:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能考虑一下吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I think about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.45,0:27:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不考虑的话 我会说你是一个傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd call you a big dummy, poo-poo face if you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.17,0:27:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说实话 这是恶作剧吧?我是说茶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be honest with me. It's a prank, right? The tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.34,0:27:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我们这些游客不在的时候 你们都知道这玩意难喝得要死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like, when us tourist folks aren't around, y'all know this tastes like garbage.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.80,0:27:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我很喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.09,0:27:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才不爱呢 这是鸽子汗液\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't love it. It's pigeon sweat.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.39,0:27:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太可怕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Horrible. Horrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.23,0:27:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.65,0:27:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要小的 把大的加回来 他手小\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, get rid of the small one and bring back the tall one. He's got bigger hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.77,0:27:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饼干时间到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's biscuits o'clock.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.44,0:27:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-希金斯!你回来了! -是啊!\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Higgins! You're back! -Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.57,0:27:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 我知道我可能 对一些人而言太守旧了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Well, hey, I know I may be a little too old-school for some folks,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.57,0:27:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是要说 噢耶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I'm gonna say it anyway. Hell to the yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.95,0:27:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很高兴见到你 -我也很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Good to see you. -Nice to see you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.04,0:27:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-给你 老板 这是你的 -谢谢 泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Here you go, boss. Those are yours. -Thank you, Ted.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.71,0:27:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要尝尝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've got to try one of these.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.33,0:27:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才不要 分享是美德 但我给希金斯带了一份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, he does not. Caring is sharing, but I brought Higgins his own.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.92,0:27:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.34,0:27:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道我会回来?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.38,0:27:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有预感会看到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I had a hunch you were gonna be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.17,0:28:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -哇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.93,0:28:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 这是给特伦特克里姆女儿的 她今天三岁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, those were for Trent Crimm's daughter. She turns three today.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.68,0:28:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但如果你能收下 对我而言意义更重大 -什么?不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-But it means more to me if you had 'em. -What? No. No, no. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.27,0:28:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 她不会记得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. It's okay. She won't remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.73,0:28:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德 你已经告诉她了?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, you've already told her?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.48,0:28:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 几周之前就说了 她一直很期待\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, weeks ago. She's been looking forward to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.19,0:28:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她才三岁 她不会记挂太久的 没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But she's three. She'll bounce right back. It'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.31,0:28:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不行 -不 我坚持让你收下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No way. -No, no. I insist. I insist.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.07,0:28:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我逗你呢 我开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm screwing with you. I'm just messing around.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.03,0:28:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我预料到你会回来 我亲自为你做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I predicted this whole thing, and I made those myself for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.24,0:28:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.32,0:28:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 两位 一会见 好吗? 加油 灰狗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, y'all. I'll see you in a little bit, okay? Let's go, Greyhounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.66,0:28:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绝对是给小女孩的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, these are definitely for a little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.79,0:28:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他认为你又傻又爱玩又神秘呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe he thinks you're silly and playful and mysterious.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.29,0:28:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.42,0:28:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(肯特)
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.02,0:28:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们!大家都听好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, fellas! Need y'all to listen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.56,0:28:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.65,0:29:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在... -我知道现在可能不是时候 教练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Now-- -I know now's not the best time, Coach,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.91,0:29:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那天我丢下你走开后 一直觉得身体不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I have been feeling physically sick since walking away from you the other day.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.62,0:29:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且昨天晚上 我做了一个可怕的噩梦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Plus last night, I had a horrible nightmare
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.24,0:29:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦见我像乌鸦一样把你啄死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I was pecking you to death like a crow.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.37,0:29:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.04,0:29:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 内特 我们没事了 好吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay, Nate. We're all good in the hood, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.13,0:29:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好 -但是 嘿 帮我个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. -But hey, but do me a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.79,0:29:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得在梦里跟我道歉 这样两边都和解了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Try to apologize to me in your dream so we're good on that side of things too.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.34,0:29:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 当然 -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-Yeah. Of course. -Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.01,0:29:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我们面临一场艰难的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, fellas, we got ourselves a heck of a match comin' up, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.89,0:29:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你们...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And what I'm gonna need from all of y'all--
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.77,0:29:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.32,0:29:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我六岁的侄女找到了我女朋友的震动棒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My six-year-old niece found my girlfriend's vibrator.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.11,0:29:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我得带她去扎个耳洞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I had to take her to get her ears pierced
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.74,0:29:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来删掉这段记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in an attempt to erase the memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.58,0:29:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也经历过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Been there.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.74,0:29:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能说两句吗?\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I say something?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.83,0:29:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舞台是你的 队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Floor is yours, Captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.33,0:30:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二级球队今天要踢爆一级球队的屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Second team's gonna kick first team's fucking asses today.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.43,0:30:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙计们!做好准备 然后我们就照队长说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, fellas! Finish getting ready, and then we'll do what the man says.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.56,0:30:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们球场见分晓 出发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll settle this out on the pitch. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.15,0:31:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(相信)
